{
  "uniqueId": "9",
  "showDictionaryLink": true,
  "name": "JLPT N1 Reading Quiz",
  "category": "JLPT",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "cards": [
    {"meaning":"useless,no good,hopeless","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"駄目","answer":["だめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be, to have (used for people and animals)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居る","answer":["いる","おる"]},
    {"meaning":"together, mutually, fellow","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相","answer":["あい"]},
    {"meaning":"as ever, as usual, the same","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相変わらず","answer":["あいかわらず"]},
    {"meaning":"civility, courtesy, compliments, sociability, graces","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛想","answer":["あいそ"]},
    {"meaning":"confrontation, facing, between ourselves, no third party, tete-a-tete","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相対","answer":["あいたい"]},
    {"meaning":"relation(ship)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"間柄","answer":["あいだがら"]},
    {"meaning":"likes and dislikes","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"愛憎","answer":["あいにく","あいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"interval","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合間","answer":["あいま"]},
    {"meaning":"dare (to do), challenge (to do)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"敢えて","answer":["あえて"]},
    {"meaning":"to look up (to), to respect, to depend on, to ask for, to seek, to revere, to drink, to take","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仰ぐ","answer":["あおぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"suborder, subfamily","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"亜科","answer":["あか"]},
    {"meaning":"copper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"銅","answer":["どう","あかがね"]},
    {"meaning":"proof, evidence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"証","answer":["あかし"]},
    {"meaning":"deficit, go in the red","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"赤字","answer":["あかじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass, spend, to reveal, to divulge","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明かす","answer":["あかす"]},
    {"meaning":"baby, infant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"赤ちゃん","answer":["あかちゃん"]},
    {"meaning":"obvious, overt, plainly, frankly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明白","answer":["あからさま","めいはく"]},
    {"meaning":"to become red, to redden, to blush","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"赤らむ","answer":["あからむ"]},
    {"meaning":"bright, cheerful","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明るい","answer":["あかるい"]},
    {"meaning":"trader,shopkeeper,merchant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商人","answer":["しょうにん","あきうど"]},
    {"meaning":"vacancy, room for rent or lease (あきま); space, room (くうかん)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空間","answer":["あきま","くうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"evil, wickedness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪","answer":["あく"]},
    {"meaning":"ash","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰","answer":["はい","あく"]},
    {"meaning":"unlucky day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪日","answer":["あくび","あくにち"]},
    {"meaning":"next, following","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明くる","answer":["あくる"]},
    {"meaning":"yearning, longing, aspiration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"憧れ","answer":["あこがれ"]},
    {"meaning":"day after tomorrow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明後日","answer":["みょうごにち","あさって"]},
    {"meaning":"wretched, miserable, shameful, mean, despicable, abject","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"浅ましい","answer":["あさましい"]},
    {"meaning":"character","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"字","answer":["じ","あざ"]},
    {"meaning":"to deceive","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"欺く","answer":["あざむく"]},
    {"meaning":"to sneer at, to ridicule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"あざ笑う","answer":["あざわらう"]},
    {"meaning":"flavour, meaning, significance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"味わい","answer":["あじわい"]},
    {"meaning":"east","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"東","answer":["ひがし","あずま"]},
    {"meaning":"to be in a hurry, to be impatient","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"焦る","answer":["あせる"]},
    {"meaning":"1. (uk) there, over there, that place, 2. (X) (col) genitals","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"彼処","answer":["あそこ"]},
    {"meaning":"value,price,cost","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値","answer":["ね","あたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be worth, to deserve, to merit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値する","answer":["あたいする"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) I,myself","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"私","answer":["わたくし","わたし","あたし"]},
    {"meaning":"hit, success, reaching the mark, per ..., vicinity, neighborhood","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当たり","answer":["あたり"]},
    {"meaning":"usual, common, ordinary, natural, reasonable, obvious","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当たり前","answer":["あたりまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"another person,unrelated person,outsider,stranger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他人","answer":["たにん","あだびと"]},
    {"meaning":"1. there, yonder, that","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"彼方","answer":["あちら","かなた"]},
    {"meaning":"deterioration, growing worse, aggravation, degeneration, corruption","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"悪化","answer":["あっか"]},
    {"meaning":"abuse,insult,slander,evil speaking","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪口","answer":["わるくち","わるぐち","あっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"pressure, coercion, oppression","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"圧迫","answer":["あっぱく"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment, service","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扱い","answer":["あつかい"]},
    {"meaning":"stress, pressure","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"圧力","answer":["あつりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"object, aim, end, hopes, expectations","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当て","answer":["あて"]},
    {"meaning":"phonetic-equivalent character, substitute character","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当て字","answer":["あてじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to apply (a rule)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当てはまる","answer":["あてはまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to apply, to adapt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当てはめる","answer":["あてはめる"]},
    {"meaning":"heir, successor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"跡継ぎ","answer":["あとつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"putting off, postponing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"後回し","answer":["あとまわし"]},
    {"meaning":"you, lady","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貴女","answer":["あなた"]},
    {"meaning":"that over there","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"彼の","answer":["あの"]},
    {"meaning":"oil painting","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"油絵","answer":["あぶらえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to behave like a spoiled child, to fawn on","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"甘える","answer":["あまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"sweet flavour, mildness, flattery, stupidity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"甘口","answer":["あまくち"]},
    {"meaning":"rain gear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"雨具","answer":["あまぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"heavenly, imperial","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"天","answer":["あまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"net, network","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"網","answer":["あみ"]},
    {"meaning":"heaven and earth, the universe, nature, top and bottom, realm, sphere, world","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"天地","answer":["あめつち"]},
    {"meaning":"to manipulate, to operate, to pull strings","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"操る","answer":["あやつる"]},
    {"meaning":"to fear, to have misgivings, to be doubtful, to mistrust","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危ぶむ","answer":["あやぶむ"]},
    {"meaning":"fault, error, indiscretion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過ち","answer":["あやまち"]},
    {"meaning":"to make a mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤る","answer":["あやまる"]},
    {"meaning":"walking","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"歩み","answer":["あゆみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to walk, to go on foot","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"歩む","answer":["あゆむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to lay waste, to devastate, to damage, to invade, to break into","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荒らす","answer":["あらす"]},
    {"meaning":"dispute, strife, quarrel, dissension, conflict, rivalry, contest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"争い","answer":["あらそい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be renewed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改まる","answer":["あらたまる"]},
    {"meaning":"rough, rude","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荒っぽい","answer":["あらっぽい"]},
    {"meaning":"embodiment, materialization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現われ","answer":["あらわれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to appear, to come in sight, to become visible, to come out, to embody, to materialize, to express oneself","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現われる","answer":["あらわれる"]},
    {"meaning":"Thank you","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有難う","answer":["ありがとう"]},
    {"meaning":"state, condition, circumstances, the way things are or should be, truth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有様","answer":["ありさま"]},
    {"meaning":"the truth, fact, as it is, frankly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有りのまま","answer":["ありのまま"]},
    {"meaning":"to join together, to face, to unite, to be opposite, to combine, to connect, to add up, to mix, to match, to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合わす","answer":["あわす"]},
    {"meaning":"joint together, opposite, facing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合わせ","answer":["あわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"assassination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暗殺","answer":["あんさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"mental arithmetic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暗算","answer":["あんざん"]},
    {"meaning":"hint, suggestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暗示","answer":["あんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be anxious, to ponder","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"案じる","answer":["あんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"rest","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"安静","answer":["あんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"sure enough, as usual","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"案の定","answer":["あんのじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"not very (used as adverb),not much","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余り","answer":["あまり","あんまり"]},
    {"meaning":"depending on","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"依","answer":["い"]},
    {"meaning":"moderate, right, random, not thorough, vague, irresponsible, halfhearted","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"いい加減","answer":["いいかげん"]},
    {"meaning":"excuse, explanation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"言い訳","answer":["いいわけ"]},
    {"meaning":"running away from home, leaving home","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家出","answer":["いえで"]},
    {"meaning":"landlord","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家主","answer":["やぬし","いえぬし"]},
    {"meaning":"to revive, to resuscitate, to make use of","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生かす","answer":["いかす"]},
    {"meaning":"anger, hatred","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"怒り","answer":["いかり"]},
    {"meaning":"to get angry,to be angry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"怒る","answer":["おこる","いかる"]},
    {"meaning":"chic, style, purity, essence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"粋","answer":["いき"]},
    {"meaning":"outside the area","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"域外","answer":["いきがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be enthusiastic about","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"意気込む","answer":["いきごむ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. details, whole story, sequence of events, particulars, how it started, how things got this way, 2. c","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"経緯","answer":["いきさつ","けいい"]},
    {"meaning":"misunderstanding, estrangement, disagreement, crossing without meeting, going astray","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"行き違い","answer":["いきちがい"]},
    {"meaning":"objection, dissent, protest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異議","answer":["いぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"army,force,troops","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍","answer":["ぐん","いくさ"]},
    {"meaning":"war, battle, campaign, fight","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦","answer":["いくさ"]},
    {"meaning":"rearing, training, nurture, cultivation, promotion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"育成","answer":["いくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"many, numerous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幾多","answer":["いくた"]},
    {"meaning":"to arrange (flowers)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活ける","answer":["いける"]},
    {"meaning":"different opinion, objection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異見","answer":["いけん"]},
    {"meaning":"intention, idea, inclination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"意向","answer":["いこう"]},
    {"meaning":"switching over to","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移行","answer":["いこう"]},
    {"meaning":"stone monument bearing an inscription","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"碑","answer":["いしぶみ"]},
    {"meaning":"clothing, costume, outfit, garment, dress","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"衣装","answer":["いしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"disposition, spirit, willpower, obstinacy, backbone, appetite","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意地","answer":["いじ"]},
    {"meaning":"migration, immigration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移住","answer":["いじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"the opposite sex","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異性","answer":["いせい"]},
    {"meaning":"historic ruins (remains relics)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遺跡","answer":["いせき"]},
    {"meaning":"still, as yet","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"依然","answer":["いぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"dependence, dependent, reliance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"依存","answer":["いそん"]},
    {"meaning":"consign (goods (for sale) to a firm), entrust (person with something), commit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"委託","answer":["いたく"]},
    {"meaning":"tease, prank, trick, practical joke, mischief","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"悪戯","answer":["いたずら"]},
    {"meaning":"very much, exceedingly, extremely","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"至って","answer":["いたって"]},
    {"meaning":"to hurt, to feel a pain, to be injured","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛む","answer":["いたむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to hurt, to injure, to cause pain, to worry, to bother, to afflict, to be grieved over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛める","answer":["いためる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pity, to sympathize with, to console, to care for, to be kind to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"労る","answer":["いたわる"]},
    {"meaning":"city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市","answer":["し","いち"]},
    {"meaning":"place, situation, position, location","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"位地","answer":["いち"]},
    {"meaning":"one by one, separately","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一々","answer":["いちいち"]},
    {"meaning":"unconditionally, as a rule","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一概に","answer":["いちがいに"]},
    {"meaning":"unfamiliar, never before met","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一見","answer":["いちげん","いっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"single word","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一言","answer":["ひとこと","いちげん"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed,settled,definite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一定","answer":["いってい","いちじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"remarkable, considerable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著しい","answer":["いちじるしい"]},
    {"meaning":"all present, all concerned, all of us","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一同","answer":["いちどう"]},
    {"meaning":"1. one copy e.g. of a document, 2. a part, partly, some","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一部","answer":["いちぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"parting","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一別","answer":["いちべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"one side, one phase, front page, the other hand, the whole surface","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一面","answer":["いちめん"]},
    {"meaning":"a glance, a look, a glimpse","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一目","answer":["いちもく"]},
    {"meaning":"uniformity, evenness, similarity, equality, impartiality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一様","answer":["いちよう"]},
    {"meaning":"evenness, uniformity, monotony, equality","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"一律","answer":["いちりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"a series, a chain, a ream (of paper)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一連","answer":["いちれん"]},
    {"meaning":"all together, batch, one lump, one bundle, summing up","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一括","answer":["いっかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"drink!(said repeatedly as a party cheer)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一気","answer":["いっき"]},
    {"meaning":"at a stroke, with a single swoop","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一挙に","answer":["いっきょに"]},
    {"meaning":"all, everything, without exception, the whole, entirely, absolutely","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一切","answer":["いっさい"]},
    {"meaning":"one mind, wholeheartedness, the whole heart","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一心","answer":["いっしん"]},
    {"meaning":"a region, a zone, the whole place","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"一帯","answer":["いったい"]},
    {"meaning":"one defeat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一敗","answer":["いっぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"complete change, about-face","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一変","answer":["いっぺん"]},
    {"meaning":"intention, aim, design","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意図","answer":["いと"]},
    {"meaning":"to carry on (e.g. in ceremony), to run a business","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"営む","answer":["いとなむ"]},
    {"meaning":"free time, leisure, leave, spare time, farewell","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暇","answer":["いとま","ひま"]},
    {"meaning":"a change","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異動","answer":["いどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to challenge, to contend for, to make love to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"挑む","answer":["いどむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(flash of) lightning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"稲光","answer":["いなびかり"]},
    {"meaning":"antiquity, ancient times","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"古","answer":["いにしえ"]},
    {"meaning":"prayer, supplication","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"祈り","answer":["いのり"]},
    {"meaning":"now, at this late hour","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"今更","answer":["いまさら"]},
    {"meaning":"emigration, immigration, emigrant, immigrant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"移民","answer":["いみん"]},
    {"meaning":"greedy, vulgar, shabby, humble, base, mean, vile","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"卑しい","answer":["いやしい"]},
    {"meaning":"will, desire, ambition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"意欲","answer":["いよく"]},
    {"meaning":"entrance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入口","answer":["いりぐち","いりくち"]},
    {"meaning":"clothing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"衣料","answer":["いりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"power, might, authority, influence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"威力","answer":["いりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to enter,to contain","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"入る","answer":["はいる","いる"]},
    {"meaning":"clothes, clothing, garments","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"衣類","answer":["いるい"]},
    {"meaning":"various","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"色々","answer":["いろいろ"]},
    {"meaning":"different opinion, objection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異論","answer":["いろん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) mark,(2) symbol,(3) evidence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"印","answer":["しるし","いん"]},
    {"meaning":"member","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"員","answer":["いん"]},
    {"meaning":"stamp, seal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"印鑑","answer":["いんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"gloom, melancholy","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"陰気","answer":["いんき"]},
    {"meaning":"retirement, retired person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"隠居","answer":["いんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"high and low,up and down,unloading and loading,praising and blaming","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上下","answer":["じょうげ","うえした"]},
    {"meaning":"to float, to rise to surface, to come to mind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮かぶ","answer":["うかぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass (examination)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受かる","answer":["うかる"]},
    {"meaning":"receiving, acceptance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け入れ","answer":["うけいれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to accept, to receive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け入れる","answer":["うけいれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to inherit, to succeed, to take over","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"受け継ぐ","answer":["うけつぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be accepted, to receive (an application)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け付ける","answer":["うけつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to catch, to stop the blow, to react to, to take","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け止める","answer":["うけとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け取り","answer":["うけとり"]},
    {"meaning":"movement, activity, trend, development, change","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"動き","answer":["うごき"]},
    {"meaning":"tide","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"潮","answer":["うしお","しお"]},
    {"meaning":"family name","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"氏","answer":["うじ","し"]},
    {"meaning":"swirl","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"渦","answer":["うず"]},
    {"meaning":"to be buried, to be surrounded, to overflow, to be filled","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"埋まる","answer":["うずまる","うまる"]},
    {"meaning":"business meeting, previous arrangement, appointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち合わせ","answer":["うちあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to knock together, to arrange","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち合わせる","answer":["うちあわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop, to abort, to discontinue, to close","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち切る","answer":["うちきる"]},
    {"meaning":"negation, denial, negative","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち消し","answer":["うちけし"]},
    {"meaning":"to drive in (e.g. nail stake), to devote oneself to, to shoot into, to smash, to throw into, to cast int","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打ち込む","answer":["うちこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"the items, breakdown, classification","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"内訳","answer":["うちわけ"]},
    {"meaning":"lawsuit, complaint","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"訴え","answer":["うったえ"]},
    {"meaning":"copy, duplicate, facsimile, transcript","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"写し","answer":["うつし"]},
    {"meaning":"blank, cavity, hollow, empty (space)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空ろ","answer":["うつろ"]},
    {"meaning":"bowl, vessel, container","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"器","answer":["うつわ"]},
    {"meaning":"rainy weather","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"雨天","answer":["うてん"]},
    {"meaning":"ability, skill, facility","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"腕前","answer":["うでまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to urge, to press, to suggest, to demand, to stimulate, to quicken, to incite, to invite (attention to)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"促す","answer":["うながす"]},
    {"meaning":"sweet","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"甘い","answer":["あまい","うまい"]},
    {"meaning":"by nature, by birth, native","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生まれつき","answer":["うまれつき"]},
    {"meaning":"sea route","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"海路","answer":["うみじ","かいろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to give birth, to deliver, to produce","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産む","answer":["うむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bury","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"埋め込む","answer":["うめこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"dried plum","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"梅干","answer":["うめぼし"]},
    {"meaning":"the end of,powder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"末","answer":["すえ","うら"]},
    {"meaning":"inside out, upside down","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"裏返し","answer":["うらがえし"]},
    {"meaning":"(bargain) sale","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売り出し","answer":["うりだし"]},
    {"meaning":"to put on sale, to market, to become popular","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売り出す","answer":["うりだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be moist, to be damp, to get wet, to profit by, to be watered, to receive benefits, to favor, to charm, t","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"潤う","answer":["うるおう"]},
    {"meaning":"sales","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売れ行き","answer":["うれゆき"]},
    {"meaning":"flighty, fickle, wanton, unfaithful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮気","answer":["うわき"]},
    {"meaning":"Skillful","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"上手","answer":["じょうず","うわて"]},
    {"meaning":"to exceed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上回る","answer":["うわまわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be planted","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植わる","answer":["うわる"]},
    {"meaning":"management, administration, operation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"運営","answer":["うんえい"]},
    {"meaning":"shipping, marine transportation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"運送","answer":["うんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"freight rates, shipping expenses, fare","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"運賃","answer":["うんちん"]},
    {"meaning":"transport, carriage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"運搬","answer":["うんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"fate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"運命","answer":["うんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"transportation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"運輸","answer":["うんゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"making use of, application, investment, practical use","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"運用","answer":["うんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"projection","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"映写","answer":["えいしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"English letter (character)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"英字","answer":["えいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"health, hygiene, sanitation, medical","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衛生","answer":["えいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection, image","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"映像","answer":["えいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"hero, great man","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"英雄","answer":["えいゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"liquid, fluid","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"液","answer":["えき"]},
    {"meaning":"use,service,role,position","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役","answer":["やく","えき"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection, reading","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"閲覧","answer":["えつらん"]},
    {"meaning":"game, spoils, trophy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"獲物","answer":["えもの"]},
    {"meaning":"neck, collar, lapel, neckband","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"襟","answer":["えり"]},
    {"meaning":"chance, fate, destiny, relation, bonds, connection, karma","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縁","answer":["えん","ふち"]},
    {"meaning":"Salt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"塩","answer":["しお","えん"]},
    {"meaning":"charming, fascinating, voluptuous","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"艶","answer":["えん","つや"]},
    {"meaning":"garden (esp. man-made)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"園","answer":["えん","その"]},
    {"meaning":"harmony, smoothness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"円滑","answer":["えんかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"veranda, porch, balcony, open corridor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縁側","answer":["えんがわ"]},
    {"meaning":"coast, shore","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沿岸","answer":["えんがん"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, exercises, manoeuvers","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"演習","answer":["えんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"production (e.g. play), direction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"演出","answer":["えんしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to perform (a play), to play (a part), to act (a part), to commit (a blunder)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"演じる","answer":["えんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to perform, to play","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"演ずる","answer":["えんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"along railway line","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沿線","answer":["えんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"marriage proposal, engagement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縁談","answer":["えんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"long way, distant place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠方","answer":["えんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"perfection, harmony, peace, smoothness, completeness, satisfaction, integrity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"円満","answer":["えんまん"]},
    {"meaning":"tail, ridge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尾","answer":["お"]},
    {"meaning":"to herd, to corner, to drive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い込む","answer":["おいこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"delicious, tasty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美味しい","answer":["おいしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to expel, to drive out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い出す","answer":["おいだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to age, to grow old","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"老いる","answer":["おいる"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear, to owe","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"負う","answer":["おう"]},
    {"meaning":"emergency","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応急","answer":["おうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"gold","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"黄金","answer":["おうごん"]},
    {"meaning":"yellow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"黄色","answer":["きいろ","おうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"subscription, application","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応募","answer":["おうぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"perhaps, almost all, majority","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大方","answer":["おおかた"]},
    {"meaning":"large build, large pattern","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大柄","answer":["おおがら"]},
    {"meaning":"grandiose, exaggerated","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大げさ","answer":["おおげさ"]},
    {"meaning":"important,valuable,serious matter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大事","answer":["だいじ","おおごと"]},
    {"meaning":"rough (as in not precise), broad, sketchy","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大ざっぱ","answer":["おおざっぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"outline, summary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大筋","answer":["おおすじ"]},
    {"meaning":"heaven, firmament, the sky","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大空","answer":["おおぞら"]},
    {"meaning":"full width, large scale, drastic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"大幅","answer":["おおはば"]},
    {"meaning":"flood","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大水","answer":["おおみず"]},
    {"meaning":"official, public, formal, open, governmental","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"公","answer":["おおやけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to commit, to perpetrate, to violate, to rape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"犯す","answer":["おかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to invade, to raid, to trespass, to violate, to intrude on","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"侵す","answer":["おかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to retard, to delay","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅らす","answer":["おくらす"]},
    {"meaning":"delay, lag","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅れ","answer":["おくれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to raise, to cause, to wake someone","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"起こす","answer":["おこす"]},
    {"meaning":"deed, conduct, behavior, action, asceticism","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"行い","answer":["おこない"]},
    {"meaning":"austere, majestic, dignified, stately, awful, impressive","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"厳か","answer":["おごそか"]},
    {"meaning":"chief, head","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"長","answer":["おさ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop, to restrain, to seize, to repress, to suppress, to press down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押さえる","answer":["おさえる"]},
    {"meaning":"before, ahead, previously","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"お先に","answer":["おさきに"]},
    {"meaning":"to be obtained, to end, to settle into, to fit into, to be settled, to be paid, to be delivered","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収まる","answer":["おさまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be obtained, to end, to settle into, to fit into, to be settled, to be paid, to be delivered","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"納まる","answer":["おさまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be at peace, to clamp down, to lessen (storm terror anger)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治まる","answer":["おさまる"]},
    {"meaning":"(giving) birth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お産","answer":["おさん"]},
    {"meaning":"teachings, precept, lesson, doctrine","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"教え","answer":["おしえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to push into, to crowd into","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押し込む","answer":["おしこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be frugal, to value, to regret","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"惜しむ","answer":["おしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to push aside, to advance on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押し寄せる","answer":["おしよせる"]},
    {"meaning":"flattery, compliment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お世辞","answer":["おせじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to attack","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"襲う","answer":["おそう"]},
    {"meaning":"at the latest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅くとも","answer":["おそくとも"]},
    {"meaning":"perhaps","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐らく","answer":["おそらく"]},
    {"meaning":"fear, horror","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐れ","answer":["おそれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be filled with awe, to feel small, to be amazed, to be surprised, to be disconcerted, to be sorry, to b","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐れ入る","answer":["おそれいる"]},
    {"meaning":"Take care of yourself","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お大事に","answer":["おだいじに"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall into, to feel down (sad)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落ち込む","answer":["おちこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"calm, composure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落ち着き","answer":["おちつき"]},
    {"meaning":"fallen leaves, leaf litter, defoliation, shedding leaves","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落ち葉","answer":["おちば"]},
    {"meaning":"to say, to speak, to tell, to talk","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仰っしゃる","answer":["おっしゃる"]},
    {"meaning":"1. strange, quaint, stylish, chic, spicy, queer, witty, tasty, romantic, 2. 2nd in rank, second sign of the","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"乙","answer":["おつ"]},
    {"meaning":"errand","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お使い","answer":["おつかい"]},
    {"meaning":"all over, given in, given up hope, bring to knees","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お手上げ","answer":["おてあげ"]},
    {"meaning":"toilet, restroom, lavatory, bathroom (US)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御手洗い","answer":["おてあらい"]},
    {"meaning":"younger brother","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"弟","answer":["おとうと","おと"]},
    {"meaning":"to drop","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落とす","answer":["おとす"]},
    {"meaning":"to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"訪れる","answer":["おとずれる"]},
    {"meaning":"obedient, docile, quiet","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大人しい","answer":["おとなしい"]},
    {"meaning":"daughter,young lady,virgin,maiden,little girl","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少女","answer":["しょうじょ","おとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"attendant, companion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お供","answer":["おとも"]},
    {"meaning":"to become weak, to decline, to wear, to abate, to decay, to wither, to waste away","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衰える","answer":["おとろえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to threaten, to coerce","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脅かす","answer":["おどかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to threaten, to menace","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脅す","answer":["おどす"]},
    {"meaning":"of the same age","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同い年","answer":["おないどし"]},
    {"meaning":"woman,girl","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"女子","answer":["じょし","おなご"]},
    {"meaning":"grandmother, female senior-citizen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お祖母さん","answer":["おばあさん"]},
    {"meaning":"to wear, to carry, to be entrusted, to have, to take on, to have a trace of, to be tinged with","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"帯びる","answer":["おびる"]},
    {"meaning":"memory, sense, experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"覚え","answer":["おぼえ"]},
    {"meaning":"policeman (friendly term)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"お巡りさん","answer":["おまわりさん"]},
    {"meaning":"Shinto shrine","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"お宮","answer":["おみや"]},
    {"meaning":"plan, idea, suggestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思い付き","answer":["おもいつき"]},
    {"meaning":"interesting, amusing","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"面白い","answer":["おもしろい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be piled up,lie on top of one another,overlap each other","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重なる","answer":["かさなる","おもなる"]},
    {"meaning":"meaning, tenor, gist, effect, appearance, taste, grace, charm, refinement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"趣","answer":["おもむき"]},
    {"meaning":"to go, to proceed, to repair to, to become","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"赴く","answer":["おもむく"]},
    {"meaning":"director,high executive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重役","answer":["じゅうやく","おもやく"]},
    {"meaning":"to respect, to honor, to esteem, to prize","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重んじる","answer":["おもんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to honor, to respect, to esteem, to prize","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重んずる","answer":["おもんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"holiday, absence, rest, Good night","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"お休み","answer":["おやすみ"]},
    {"meaning":"and, as well as","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"及び","answer":["および"]},
    {"meaning":"to reach, to come up to, to amount to, to befall, to happen to, to extend, to match, to equal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"及ぶ","answer":["およぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"weave, weaving, woven item","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"織","answer":["おり"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn up, to fold back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"折り返す","answer":["おりかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"textile, fabric","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"織物","answer":["おりもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to weave","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"織る","answer":["おる"]},
    {"meaning":"foolish, stupid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"愚か","answer":["おろか"]},
    {"meaning":"tone color, tone quality, timbre, synthesizer patch","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"音色","answer":["ねいろ","おんしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"gentle, mild, moderate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"温和","answer":["おんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"tentative, provisional","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仮","answer":["かり"]},
    {"meaning":"department, section","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"科","answer":["か"]},
    {"meaning":"article counter","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個","answer":["か"]},
    {"meaning":"low rank, subordinate, lower order (e.g. byte)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下位","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"deterioration, changing for the worse","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改悪","answer":["かいあく"]},
    {"meaning":"maritime, marine transportation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"海運","answer":["かいうん"]},
    {"meaning":"reform, reformation, innovation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改革","answer":["かいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"shell","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貝殻","answer":["かいがら"]},
    {"meaning":"class, rank, grade","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"階級","answer":["かいきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"channel","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"海峡","answer":["かいきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"interview, audience","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会見","answer":["かいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"介護","answer":["かいご"]},
    {"meaning":"holding a meeting, open an exhibition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"開催","answer":["かいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"collection, recovery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回収","answer":["かいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"repair, improvement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"改修","answer":["かいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"monster","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怪獣","answer":["かいじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"cancellation, rescinding, release, calling off","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解除","answer":["かいじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"forwarding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回送","answer":["かいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"class, level, stratum, hierarchy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"階層","answer":["かいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"reclamation (of wasteland), cultivation, pioneer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"開拓","answer":["かいたく"]},
    {"meaning":"conversation, conference, discussion, interview","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会談","answer":["かいだん"]},
    {"meaning":"reform","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改定","answer":["かいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"revision","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"改訂","answer":["かいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"highway","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"街道","answer":["かいどう"]},
    {"meaning":"intervention","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"介入","answer":["かいにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"development, exploitation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"開発","answer":["かいはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"height above sea level","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"海抜","answer":["かいばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing, looking after","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"介抱","answer":["かいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"dissection, autopsy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"解剖","answer":["かいぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"circulation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"回覧","answer":["かいらん"]},
    {"meaning":"ocean current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"海流","answer":["かいりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"improvement, reform","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"改良","answer":["かいりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"circuit (electric)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回路","answer":["かいろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to reflect","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"省みる","answer":["かえりみる"]},
    {"meaning":"to return, to come back, to go back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"返る","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"(outward) looks, features, face, countenance, expression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"顔付き","answer":["かおつき"]},
    {"meaning":"to publish, to print, to carry (an article), to put up, to hang out, to hoist, to fly (a sail), to float (a","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"掲げる","answer":["かかげる"]},
    {"meaning":"official, duty, person in charge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"係り","answer":["かかり"]},
    {"meaning":"extracurricular","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課外","answer":["かがい"]},
    {"meaning":"dictation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書き取り","answer":["かきとり"]},
    {"meaning":"to write down, to take dictation, to take notes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書き取る","answer":["かきとる"]},
    {"meaning":"to lack, to break, to crack, to chip","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠く","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"horn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"角","answer":["すみ","かど","かく"]},
    {"meaning":"nucleus, kernel","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"核","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"status, character, case","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"格","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"beautiful passage of literature","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"佳句","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"stroke","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"画","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"qualitative difference, disparity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"格差","answer":["かくさ"]},
    {"meaning":"scattering, diffusion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拡散","answer":["かくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"every kind, all sorts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各種","answer":["かくしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"every other week","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"隔週","answer":["かくしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"conviction, confidence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確信","answer":["かくしん"]},
    {"meaning":"reform, innovation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"革新","answer":["かくしん"]},
    {"meaning":"definition (math), decision, settlement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確定","answer":["かくてい"]},
    {"meaning":"acquisition, possession","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"獲得","answer":["かくとく"]},
    {"meaning":"guarantee, ensure, maintain, insure, secure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"確保","answer":["かくほ"]},
    {"meaning":"revolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"革命","answer":["かくめい"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確立","answer":["かくりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"credit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"掛け","answer":["かけ"]},
    {"meaning":"running fast, double time","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"駆け足","answer":["かけあし"]},
    {"meaning":"household economy, family finances","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家計","answer":["かけい"]},
    {"meaning":"#NAME?","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"ヶ月","answer":["かげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacturing, processing, treatment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加工","answer":["かこう"]},
    {"meaning":"chemical combination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"化合","answer":["かごう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be bulky, to be unwieldy, to grow voluminous","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嵩張る","answer":["かさばる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pile up, to increase","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嵩む","answer":["かさむ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. windmill, 2. pinwheel","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"風車","answer":["かざぐるま","ふうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"passage, place, point, part","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"箇所","answer":["かしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"burn, scald","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"火傷","answer":["かしょう","やけど"]},
    {"meaning":"itemized form, itemization","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"箇条書き","answer":["かじょうがき"]},
    {"meaning":"faint, dim, weak, indistinct, hazy, poor, wretched","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"微か","answer":["かすか"]},
    {"meaning":"to change into, to convert into, to transform, to be reduced, to influence, to improve (someone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"化する","answer":["かする"]},
    {"meaning":"to touch lightly, to take a percentage (from)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"擦る","answer":["かする","こする"]},
    {"meaning":"Mars (planet)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"火星","answer":["かせい"]},
    {"meaning":"fossil, petrifaction, fossilization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"化石","answer":["かせき"]},
    {"meaning":"rivers","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"河川","answer":["かせん"]},
    {"meaning":"synthetic fibres","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"化繊","answer":["かせん"]},
    {"meaning":"depopulation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"過疎","answer":["かそ"]},
    {"meaning":"excess, superabundance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過多","answer":["かた"]},
    {"meaning":"unrequited love","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片思い","answer":["かたおもい"]},
    {"meaning":"enemy, rival","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"敵","answer":["かたき","てき"]},
    {"meaning":"spirit, character, trait, temperament, disposition","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気質","answer":["かたぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"a smattering, talk like a baby, speak haltingly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片言","answer":["かたこと"]},
    {"meaning":"tidying up, finishing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"片付け","answer":["かたづけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to incline toward,to slant,to lurch","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"傾く","answer":["かたむく","かたぶく"]},
    {"meaning":"to incline, to list, to bend, to lean, to tip, to tilt, to slant, to concentrate on, to ruin (a country), to","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"傾ける","answer":["かたむける"]},
    {"meaning":"to harden, to freeze, to fortify","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固める","answer":["かためる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be one-sided, to incline, to be partial, to be prejudiced, to lean, to be biased","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"偏る","answer":["かたよる"]},
    {"meaning":"beside(s), while, nearby","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"傍ら","answer":["かたわら"]},
    {"meaning":"subject, theme, task","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"課題","answer":["かだい"]},
    {"meaning":"flower bed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"花壇","answer":["かだん"]},
    {"meaning":"domestic animals, livestock, cattle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"家畜","answer":["かちく"]},
    {"meaning":"epoch-making","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"画期","answer":["かっき"]},
    {"meaning":"vigor, active","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活発","answer":["かっぱつ"]},
    {"meaning":"divide, cut, halve, separate, split, rip, break, crack, smash, dilute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割","answer":["かつ"]},
    {"meaning":"date,dating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日付","answer":["ひづけ","かづけ"]},
    {"meaning":"gate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"門","answer":["もん","かど"]},
    {"meaning":"to come true (wish)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"叶う","answer":["かなう"]},
    {"meaning":"to grant (request wish)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"叶える","answer":["かなえる"]},
    {"meaning":"iron rod, crowbar, horizontal bar (gymnastics)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉄棒","answer":["かなぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"becoming a member, joining, entry, admission, subscription, affiliation, adherence, signing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加入","answer":["かにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"safe,vault,treasury,provider of funds","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"金庫","answer":["きんこ","かねぐら"]},
    {"meaning":"prediction, promise, prognostication","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予言","answer":["かねごと"]},
    {"meaning":"simultaneously","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"兼ねて","answer":["かねて"]},
    {"meaning":"going off duty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下番","answer":["かばん"]},
    {"meaning":"vulgarity,meanness,indecency,coarseness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"下品","answer":["げひん","かひん"]},
    {"meaning":"pomp, splendor, gaudiness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"華美","answer":["かび"]},
    {"meaning":"pollen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"花粉","answer":["かふん"]},
    {"meaning":"stock (company)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"株式","answer":["かぶしき"]},
    {"meaning":"money, currency, coinage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貨幣","answer":["かへい"]},
    {"meaning":"posture, pose, style","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構え","answer":["かまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to set up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構える","answer":["かまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"seasoning, flavoring","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加味","answer":["かみ"]},
    {"meaning":"crowded","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"過密","answer":["かみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"bottle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"瓶","answer":["びん","かめ"]},
    {"meaning":"may, might, perhaps, may be, possibly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"かも知れない","answer":["かもしれない"]},
    {"meaning":"body build, figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体付き","answer":["からだつき"]},
    {"meaning":"to entangle, to entwine","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"絡む","answer":["からむ"]},
    {"meaning":"borrowing, debt, loan","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"借り","answer":["かり"]},
    {"meaning":"lower official","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"下吏","answer":["かり"]},
    {"meaning":"(pt:) (n) playing cards (pt: carta)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加留多","answer":["かるた"]},
    {"meaning":"overwork, strain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過労","answer":["かろう"]},
    {"meaning":"barely, narrowly, just manage to do st","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辛うじて","answer":["かろうじて"]},
    {"meaning":"side,edge,third person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"側","answer":["そば","かわ","がわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to exchange (messages), to dodge, to parry, to avoid, to turn aside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交わす","answer":["かわす"]},
    {"meaning":"to take the place of, to relieve, to be substituted for, to be exchanged, to change places with, to take","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代わる","answer":["かわる"]},
    {"meaning":"alternately","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代わる代わる","answer":["かわるがわる"]},
    {"meaning":"pipe,tube","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"管","answer":["くだ","かん"]},
    {"meaning":"(tree) trunk","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幹","answer":["かん"]},
    {"meaning":"crown, diadem, first, best, peerless, cap, naming, designating, initiating on coming of age, top character ra","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冠","answer":["かん","かんむり"]},
    {"meaning":"look, appearance, spectacle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観","answer":["かん"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, easiness, quasi-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"簡易","answer":["かんい"]},
    {"meaning":"strong feelings, deep emotion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"感慨","answer":["かんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"cold, frost, chill","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寒気","answer":["かんき"]},
    {"meaning":"brevity, conciseness, simplicity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"簡潔","answer":["かんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"resolution, reduction, return to origins","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"還元","answer":["かんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"publication, issue","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刊行","answer":["かんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"customary practice, habit, traditional event","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣行","answer":["かんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"advice, counsel, remonstrance, recommendation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勧告","answer":["かんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing, (army) nurse","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"看護","answer":["かんご"]},
    {"meaning":"Chinese word, Sino-Japanese word","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"漢語","answer":["かんご"]},
    {"meaning":"conversion, change, exchange","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"換算","answer":["かんさん"]},
    {"meaning":"observation, guarding, inspection, surveillance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"監視","answer":["かんし"]},
    {"meaning":"usual (historical) custom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣習","answer":["かんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"spectators, onlookers, members of the audience","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"観衆","answer":["かんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"interference, intervention","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"干渉","answer":["かんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sense of touch, feeling, sensation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"感触","answer":["かんしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"essential, fundamental, crucial, vital, main","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"肝心","answer":["かんじん"]},
    {"meaning":"cheer, shout of joy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"歓声","answer":["かんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"infection, contagion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"感染","answer":["かんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"main line, trunk line","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幹線","answer":["かんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"customs, duty, tariff","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"関税","answer":["かんぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, plain","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"簡素","answer":["かんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"point of view","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観点","answer":["かんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"sensitivity, severity (quake)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感度","answer":["かんど"]},
    {"meaning":"management, (executive) staff, leaders","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幹部","answer":["かんぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"pardon, forgiveness, forbearance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勘弁","answer":["かんべん"]},
    {"meaning":"invitation, solicitation, canvassing, inducement, persuasion, encouragement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勧誘","answer":["かんゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"participation, taking part in, participating in, being concerned in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関与","answer":["かんよ"]},
    {"meaning":"common, customary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣用","answer":["かんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"forbearance, tolerance, generosity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"寛容","answer":["かんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"viewing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"観覧","answer":["かんらん"]},
    {"meaning":"bureaucrat, bureaucracy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"官僚","answer":["かんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"custom, precedent, of convention","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣例","answer":["かんれい"]},
    {"meaning":"60th birthday","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"還暦","answer":["かんれき"]},
    {"meaning":"presence, dignity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貫禄","answer":["かんろく"]},
    {"meaning":"relief, mitigation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緩和","answer":["かんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"~street, ~quarters","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"街","answer":["がい","まち"]},
    {"meaning":"imported goods, foreign money","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"外貨","answer":["がいか"]},
    {"meaning":"appearance, exterior, facade","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外観","answer":["がいかん"]},
    {"meaning":"Foreign Minister","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外相","answer":["がいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to injure, to damage, to harm, to kill, to hinder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"害する","answer":["がいする"]},
    {"meaning":"general statement, outline","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"概説","answer":["がいせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"corresponding, answering to, coming under","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"該当","answer":["がいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"in the street","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"街頭","answer":["がいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"general idea, concept, notion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"概念","answer":["がいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"imported, outpatient clinic","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外来","answer":["がいらい"]},
    {"meaning":"outline, summary, gist, in brief","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"概略","answer":["がいりゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"arts and sciences, liberal arts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"学芸","answer":["がくげい"]},
    {"meaning":"university graduate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"学士","answer":["がくし"]},
    {"meaning":"theory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学説","answer":["がくせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"score (music)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"楽譜","answer":["がくふ"]},
    {"meaning":"academic background","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"学歴","answer":["がくれき"]},
    {"meaning":"artistry, good taste, elegance, grace","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"雅致","answer":["がち"]},
    {"meaning":"chorus, singing in a chorus","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"合唱","answer":["がっしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement, concurrence, conforming to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"合致","answer":["がっち"]},
    {"meaning":"time,years,days","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"月日","answer":["つきひ","がっぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"combination, union, amalgamation, consolidation, merger, coalition, fusion, annexation, affiliation, incorpor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"合併","answer":["がっぺい"]},
    {"meaning":"ophthalmology","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"眼科","answer":["がんか"]},
    {"meaning":"eyeball","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"眼球","answer":["がんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"spectacles, glasses","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"眼鏡","answer":["がんきょう","めがね"]},
    {"meaning":"stubbornness, obstinacy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"頑固","answer":["がんこ"]},
    {"meaning":"written application or petition","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"願書","answer":["がんしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"rock","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"岩石","answer":["がんせき"]},
    {"meaning":"first year (of a specific reign)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"元年","answer":["がんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"originally, primarily, essentially, logically, naturally","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"元来","answer":["がんらい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) draft (beer),(2) raw,unprocessed","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生","answer":["せい","なま","き"]},
    {"meaning":"period, time","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期","answer":["き"]},
    {"meaning":"planning, project","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"企画","answer":["きかく"]},
    {"meaning":"standard, norm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"規格","answer":["きかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dress up","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着飾る","answer":["きかざる"]},
    {"meaning":"organ (of body), instrument","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"器官","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"quarterly (e.g. magazine)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"季刊","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"injury, harm, danger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危害","answer":["きがい"]},
    {"meaning":"hesitance, diffidence, feeling constraint, fear of troubling someone, having scruples about doing someth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"気兼ね","answer":["きがね"]},
    {"meaning":"cheerful, buoyant, lighthearted","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気軽","answer":["きがる"]},
    {"meaning":"crisis","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危機","answer":["きき"]},
    {"meaning":"listening comprehension","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"聞き取り","answer":["ききとり"]},
    {"meaning":"effect, virtue, efficacy, impression","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"効き目","answer":["ききめ"]},
    {"meaning":"returning to Tokyo","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"帰京","answer":["ききょう"]},
    {"meaning":"fund, foundation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基金","answer":["ききん"]},
    {"meaning":"abstain from voting, renunciation of a right","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"棄権","answer":["きけん"]},
    {"meaning":"comedy, funny show","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"喜劇","answer":["きげき"]},
    {"meaning":"origin, beginning, rise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"起源","answer":["きげん"]},
    {"meaning":"mechanism, organization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機構","answer":["きこう"]},
    {"meaning":"marriage, married","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"既婚","answer":["きこん"]},
    {"meaning":"mention, entry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"記載","answer":["きさい"]},
    {"meaning":"affectation, conceit, snobbery","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"気障","answer":["きざ"]},
    {"meaning":"signs, omen, symptoms","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"兆し","answer":["きざし"]},
    {"meaning":"signs, omen, symptoms","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"兆","answer":["きざし"]},
    {"meaning":"weather, climate","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"気象","answer":["きしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed date, settlement date","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期日","answer":["きじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"describing, descriptor","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"記述","answer":["きじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"odd number","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奇数","answer":["きすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to build, to pile up, to amass","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"築く","answer":["きずく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be hurt, to be wounded, to get injured","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"傷付く","answer":["きずつく"]},
    {"meaning":"regulation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"規制","answer":["きせい"]},
    {"meaning":"steamship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"汽船","answer":["きせん"]},
    {"meaning":"donation, presentation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"寄贈","answer":["きそう"]},
    {"meaning":"noble, aristocrat","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貴族","answer":["きぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"to forge, to drill, to temper, to train, to discipline","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鍛える","answer":["きたえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to come","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"来る","answer":["くる","きたる"]},
    {"meaning":"disposition, nature","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気立て","answer":["きだて"]},
    {"meaning":"chance, start, cue, excuse, motive, impetus, occasion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"切っ掛け","answer":["きっかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"tea drinking, tea house","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"喫茶","answer":["きっさ"]},
    {"meaning":"regulation, provisions","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"規定","answer":["きてい"]},
    {"meaning":"starting point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"起点","answer":["きてん"]},
    {"meaning":"orbit, railroad track","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"軌道","answer":["きどう"]},
    {"meaning":"1st in rank, first sign of the Chinese calendar, shell, instep, grade A (きのえ); carapace, shell (こう)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"甲","answer":["きのえ","こう"]},
    {"meaning":"indication,market trend,worry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気配","answer":["けはい","きはい"]},
    {"meaning":"model, standard, pattern, norm, criterion, example","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"規範","answer":["きはん"]},
    {"meaning":"aroma","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気品","answer":["きひん"]},
    {"meaning":"character, traits, ethos","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"気風","answer":["きふう"]},
    {"meaning":"undulation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"起伏","answer":["きふく"]},
    {"meaning":"scale, scope, plan, structure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"規模","answer":["きぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"whim, caprice, whimsy, fickle, moody, uneven temper","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"気まぐれ","answer":["きまぐれ"]},
    {"meaning":"too serious, person who is too serious, honesty, sincerity","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生真面目","answer":["きまじめ"]},
    {"meaning":"end of term","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期末","answer":["きまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"feeling awkward, being ashamed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決まり悪い","answer":["きまりわるい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be decided, to be settled, to look good in (clothes)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決まる","answer":["きまる"]},
    {"meaning":"signature, register","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記名","answer":["きめい"]},
    {"meaning":"dramatization (e.g. film)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脚色","answer":["きゃくしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"scenario","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脚本","answer":["きゃくほん"]},
    {"meaning":"objective","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"客観","answer":["きゃっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement, rules, code","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"規約","answer":["きやく"]},
    {"meaning":"relief, rescue, reinforcement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"救援","answer":["きゅうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"temporary absence from school, suspension","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"休学","answer":["きゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"ultimate, final, eventual","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"究極","answer":["きゅうきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"narrow, tight, stiff, rigid, uneasy, formal, constrained","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"窮屈","answer":["きゅうくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(plant) bulb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"球根","answer":["きゅうこん"]},
    {"meaning":"relief, aid, rescue, salvation, help","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"救済","answer":["きゅうさい"]},
    {"meaning":"school lunch, providing a meal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給食","answer":["きゅうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"office boy (girl), page, waiter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給仕","answer":["きゅうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"truce, armistice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"休戦","answer":["きゅうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"old friend, old friendship","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"旧知","answer":["きゅうち"]},
    {"meaning":"palace","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宮殿","answer":["きゅうでん"]},
    {"meaning":"poverty","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"窮乏","answer":["きゅうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"hill","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"丘陵","answer":["きゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"both, neither (neg), all, and, as well as, including, with, together with, plural ending","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共","answer":["きょう"]},
    {"meaning":"offer, present, submit, serve (a meal), supply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"供","answer":["きょう"]},
    {"meaning":"wonder, miracle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"驚異","answer":["きょうい"]},
    {"meaning":"teaching staff","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"教員","answer":["きょういん"]},
    {"meaning":"subject, curriculum","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教科","answer":["きょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"association, society, organization","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"協会","answer":["きょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"sympathy, response","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共感","answer":["きょうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"coeducation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共学","answer":["きょうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"conference, consultation, discussion, negotiation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"協議","answer":["きょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"lesson, precept, moral instruction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"教訓","answer":["きょうくん"]},
    {"meaning":"environment, circumstances","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"境遇","answer":["きょうぐう"]},
    {"meaning":"forcing, enforcement","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強行","answer":["きょうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"firm, vigorous, unbending, unyielding, strong, stubborn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"強硬","answer":["きょうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"bad harvest, poor crop","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"凶作","answer":["きょうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"communism","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共産","answer":["きょうさん"]},
    {"meaning":"teaching materials","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"教材","answer":["きょうざい"]},
    {"meaning":"training, instruction","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"教習","answer":["きょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"nostalgia, homesickness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"郷愁","answer":["きょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"teaching certificate, the teaching profession","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教職","answer":["きょうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"reception, acceptance, enjoyment, being given","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"享受","answer":["きょうじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"to amuse oneself, to make merry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"興じる","answer":["きょうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"obligation, coercion, compulsion, enforcement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強制","answer":["きょうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"coexistence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共存","answer":["きょうそん","きょうぞん"]},
    {"meaning":"sisters","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"姉妹","answer":["しまい","きょうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"co-operation, conciliation, harmony, firm (market) tone","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"協調","answer":["きょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement, pact, agreement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"協定","answer":["きょうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"threat, menace, coercion, terrorism","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脅迫","answer":["きょうはく"]},
    {"meaning":"resonance, sympathy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共鳴","answer":["きょうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"strong, intense, severe","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"強烈","answer":["きょうれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"republicanism, cooperation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共和","answer":["きょうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"tune, piece of music","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"曲","answer":["きょく"]},
    {"meaning":"limit, localize","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"局限","answer":["きょくげん"]},
    {"meaning":"extreme, extremity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"極端","answer":["きょくたん"]},
    {"meaning":"residence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居住","answer":["きょじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"refusal, rejection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拒絶","answer":["きょぜつ"]},
    {"meaning":"denial, veto, rejection, refusal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拒否","answer":["きょひ"]},
    {"meaning":"permission, pardon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"許容","answer":["きょよう"]},
    {"meaning":"distance, range","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"距離","answer":["きょり"]},
    {"meaning":"contribution, service","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄与","answer":["きよ"]},
    {"meaning":"clean, pure, chaste","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清らか","answer":["きよらか"]},
    {"meaning":"at ease, comfortable","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気楽","answer":["きらく"]},
    {"meaning":"limits, end, bounds, period, place to leave off, closing sentence, all there is, only, since","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切り","answer":["きり"]},
    {"meaning":"paulownia tree","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"桐","answer":["きり"]},
    {"meaning":"to change, to exchange, to convert, to renew, to throw a switch, to replace, to switch over","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"切り替える","answer":["きりかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"atmospheric current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気流","answer":["きりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"pretty, clean, nice, tidy, beautiful, fair","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奇麗","answer":["きれい"]},
    {"meaning":"break, pause, gap, end, rift, interruption, cut, section, notch, incision, end (of a task)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切れ目","answer":["きれめ"]},
    {"meaning":"cotton","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"木綿","answer":["もめん","きわた"]},
    {"meaning":"exceedingly, extremely","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"極めて","answer":["きわめて"]},
    {"meaning":"nearsightedness, shortsightedness, myopia","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"近眼","answer":["きんがん"]},
    {"meaning":"urgent, pressing, emergency","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緊急","answer":["きんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"nearness,before long","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"近々","answer":["ちかぢか","きんきん"]},
    {"meaning":"suburbs, outskirts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"近郊","answer":["きんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"equilibrium, balance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"均衡","answer":["きんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"shortsightedness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"近視","answer":["きんし"]},
    {"meaning":"to prohibit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"禁じる","answer":["きんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to forbid, to suppress","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"禁ずる","answer":["きんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"industry, diligence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤勉","answer":["きんべん"]},
    {"meaning":"service, duty, work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤務","answer":["きんむ"]},
    {"meaning":"taboo, forbidden thing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"禁物","answer":["きんもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"labor, exertion, diligent service","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤労","answer":["きんろう"]},
    {"meaning":"legislative bill","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"議案","answer":["ぎあん"]},
    {"meaning":"play, drama","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"戯曲","answer":["ぎきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"resolution, decision, vote","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議決","answer":["ぎけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"Diet building","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議事堂","answer":["ぎじどう"]},
    {"meaning":"sacrifice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"犠牲","answer":["ぎせい"]},
    {"meaning":"forgery, falsification, fabrication, counterfeiting","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"偽造","answer":["ぎぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"topic of discussion, agenda","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議題","answer":["ぎだい"]},
    {"meaning":"technical skill, ability, capacity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"技能","answer":["ぎのう"]},
    {"meaning":"(sudden) change, reversal, turn-around, coming from behind (baseball)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆転","answer":["ぎゃくてん"]},
    {"meaning":"line, row, verse","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"行","answer":["ぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"trader, merchant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"業者","answer":["ぎょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"administration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"行政","answer":["ぎょうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"achievement, performance, results, work, contribution","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"業績","answer":["ぎょうせき"]},
    {"meaning":"business, affairs, duties, work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"業務","answer":["ぎょうむ"]},
    {"meaning":"ball,sphere,coin","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"玉","answer":["たま","ぎょく"]},
    {"meaning":"fishing boat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"漁船","answer":["ぎょせん"]},
    {"meaning":"fishing village","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"漁村","answer":["ぎょそん"]},
    {"meaning":"duty, sense of duty, honor, decency, courtesy, debt of gratitude, social obligation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"義理","answer":["ぎり"]},
    {"meaning":"doubt, misgivings, distrust, suspicion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"疑惑","answer":["ぎわく"]},
    {"meaning":"testing, scrutiny, careful investigation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"吟味","answer":["ぎんみ"]},
    {"meaning":"ward, district, section","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区","answer":["く"]},
    {"meaning":"to cross each other, to run counter to, to differ, to clash, to go awry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"食い違う","answer":["くいちがう"]},
    {"meaning":"hunger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"空腹","answer":["くうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"division, section, compartment, boundary, area, block","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区画","answer":["くかく"]},
    {"meaning":"section (of track etc)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区間","answer":["くかん"]},
    {"meaning":"stalk","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"茎","answer":["くき"]},
    {"meaning":"an end, a stop, punctuation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"区切り","answer":["くぎり"]},
    {"meaning":"1. to drive, to pass through, 2. to evade, to hide, 3. to dive (into or under water), to go undergro","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"潜る","answer":["くぐる","もぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"variety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"種々","answer":["くさぐさ","しゅじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"past events, bygones","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"旧事","answer":["くじ","きゅうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"good-for-nothing, stupid, trivial, worthless","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下らない","answer":["くだらない"]},
    {"meaning":"example, precedent, the usual, the said, the above-mentioned, (man) in question","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"件","answer":["くだん"]},
    {"meaning":"to hum something, to sing to oneself","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"口ずさむ","answer":["くちずさむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to rot","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"朽ちる","answer":["くちる"]},
    {"meaning":"bending, indentation, refraction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"屈折","answer":["くっせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to overturn, to upset, to overthrow, to undermine","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"覆す","answer":["くつがえす"]},
    {"meaning":"national or state border","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"国境","answer":["こっきょう","くにざかい"]},
    {"meaning":"necklace, choker","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"首輪","answer":["くびわ"]},
    {"meaning":"combination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組み合わせ","answer":["くみあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to join together, to combine, to join up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組み合わせる","answer":["くみあわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"to insert, to include, to cut in (printing)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組み込む","answer":["くみこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"warehouse, cellar, magazine, granary, godown, depository, treasury, elevator","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蔵","answer":["くら"]},
    {"meaning":"to torment, to harass, to inflict pain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦しめる","answer":["くるしめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to wrap","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"包む","answer":["つつむ","くるむ"]},
    {"meaning":"expert, professional, geisha, prostitute","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"玄人","answer":["くろうと"]},
    {"meaning":"balance (figure) in the black","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"黒字","answer":["くろじ"]},
    {"meaning":"ruler, monarch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"君主","answer":["くんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"idle complaint, grumble","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"愚痴","answer":["ぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"group (math)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"群","answer":["ぐん"]},
    {"meaning":"warship, battleship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"軍艦","answer":["ぐんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"(social) group, crowd, throng, mob, multitude","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"群集","answer":["ぐんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"military affairs","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍事","answer":["ぐんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"armaments, military preparations","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍備","answer":["ぐんび"]},
    {"meaning":"military or naval uniform","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軍服","answer":["ぐんぷく"]},
    {"meaning":"penalty, sentence, punishment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刑","answer":["けい"]},
    {"meaning":"system, lineage, group","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"系","answer":["けい"]},
    {"meaning":"passage, expiration, progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経過","answer":["けいか"]},
    {"meaning":"rhythmical (e.g. melody), casual (e.g. dress), light, nimble","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軽快","answer":["けいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"warning, admonition, vigilance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"警戒","answer":["けいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"meter, gauge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"計器","answer":["けいき"]},
    {"meaning":"opportunity, chance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"契機","answer":["けいき"]},
    {"meaning":"Sincerely yours","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"敬具","answer":["けいぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"abatement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軽減","answer":["けいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"appearance (e.g. article in paper)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"掲載","answer":["けいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"inclination, slant, slope, bevel, list, dip","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"傾斜","answer":["けいしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"formation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"形成","answer":["けいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"condition, situation, prospects","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"形勢","answer":["けいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"rash, thoughtless, careless, hasty","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"軽率","answer":["けいそつ"]},
    {"meaning":"carrying something","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"携帯","answer":["けいたい"]},
    {"meaning":"form, shape, figure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"形態","answer":["けいたい"]},
    {"meaning":"judgement, penalty, punishment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刑罰","answer":["けいばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"expenses, cost, outlay","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経費","answer":["けいひ"]},
    {"meaning":"police inspector","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警部","answer":["けいぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"personal history, career","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"経歴","answer":["けいれき"]},
    {"meaning":"course, route, channel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経路","answer":["けいろ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to disgrace,to dishonour,(2) to pollute,to contaminate,to soil,to make dirty,to stain","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚す","answer":["よごす","けがす"]},
    {"meaning":"filthy, unfair","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚らわしい","answer":["けがらわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"uncleanness, impurity, disgrace","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚れ","answer":["けがれ","よごれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to get dirty","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"汚れる","answer":["よごれる","けがれる"]},
    {"meaning":"beast, brute","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"獣","answer":["けだもの"]},
    {"meaning":"tuberculosis, tubercule","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結核","answer":["けっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"blood vessel","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"血管","answer":["けっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"doing (with resolve), carrying out (i.e. a plan)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決行","answer":["けっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"balance sheet, settlement of accounts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"決算","answer":["けっさん"]},
    {"meaning":"decision of a contest, finals (in sports)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決勝","answer":["けっしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"crystal, crystallization","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結晶","answer":["けっしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"formation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結成","answer":["けっせい"]},
    {"meaning":"union, unity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結束","answer":["けっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"decision, determination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決意","answer":["けつい"]},
    {"meaning":"resolution, vote, decision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決議","answer":["けつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"combination, union","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結合","answer":["けつごう"]},
    {"meaning":"decision, determination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決断","answer":["けつだん"]},
    {"meaning":"want, shortage, famine","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"欠乏","answer":["けつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"smoky, feeling awkward","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙たい","answer":["けむたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to smoke (e.g. fire)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙る","answer":["けむる"]},
    {"meaning":"retainer, retinue, servant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家来","answer":["けらい"]},
    {"meaning":"sphere, circle, range","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"圏","answer":["けん"]},
    {"meaning":"authority, the right (to do something)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"権","answer":["けん"]},
    {"meaning":"authority, power, influence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"権威","answer":["けんい"]},
    {"meaning":"side line, second business","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"兼業","answer":["けんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"power, authority, jurisdiction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"権限","answer":["けんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"in good health, well","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"健在","answer":["けんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"offering prizes, winning, reward","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"懸賞","answer":["けんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"public prosecutor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"検事","answer":["けんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"health, soundness, wholesome","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"健全","answer":["けんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"point of view","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見地","answer":["けんち"]},
    {"meaning":"wisdom, intelligence, prudence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"賢明","answer":["けんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"thrift, economy, frugality","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"倹約","answer":["けんやく"]},
    {"meaning":"multi-use, combined use, combination, serving two purposes","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"兼用","answer":["けんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"power, authority, influence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"権力","answer":["けんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"troupe, theatrical company","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"劇団","answer":["げきだん"]},
    {"meaning":"encouragement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"激励","answer":["げきれい"]},
    {"meaning":"monthly tuition fee","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"月謝","answer":["げっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"monthly installment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"月賦","answer":["げっぷ"]},
    {"meaning":"diarrhoea","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"下痢","answer":["げり"]},
    {"meaning":"field,plain,prairie,tundra,moor,wilderness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原","answer":["はら","げん"]},
    {"meaning":"original form, base form","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原形","answer":["げんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"present, current, in operation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現行","answer":["げんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"original work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原作","answer":["げんさく"]},
    {"meaning":"atom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原子","answer":["げんし"]},
    {"meaning":"ruler, sovereign","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"元首","answer":["げんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"original document","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原書","answer":["げんしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"decrease, reduction, decline","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"減少","answer":["げんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"actual spot,scene,scene of the crime","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現場","answer":["げんば","げんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"chemical element","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"元素","answer":["げんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"principle, general rule","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"原則","answer":["げんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"developing (film)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"現像","answer":["げんぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"actual place, local","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現地","answer":["げんち"]},
    {"meaning":"limit, restriction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"限定","answer":["げんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"origin (coordinates), starting point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原点","answer":["げんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"original (text)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"原典","answer":["げんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"subtract, give a demerit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"減点","answer":["げんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"atomic bomb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"原爆","answer":["げんばく"]},
    {"meaning":"the text, original","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原文","answer":["げんぶん"]},
    {"meaning":"strict, close","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"厳密","answer":["げんみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"crude oil","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"原油","answer":["げんゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"言論","answer":["げんろん"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese style door","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"戸","answer":["と","こ"]},
    {"meaning":"child, the young of animals","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"児","answer":["こ"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall in love with, to love","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"恋する","answer":["こいする"]},
    {"meaning":"10^38, hundred undecillion, hundred sextillion (こう), ditch, drain, gutter, trench (みぞ)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"溝","answer":["こう","みぞ"]},
    {"meaning":"-school, proof","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"校","answer":["こう"]},
    {"meaning":"good will, favor, courtesy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好意","answer":["こうい"]},
    {"meaning":"act, deed, conduct","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"行為","answer":["こうい"]},
    {"meaning":"bank clerk","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"行員","answer":["こういん"]},
    {"meaning":"trade, commerce","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交易","answer":["こうえき"]},
    {"meaning":"public performance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公演","answer":["こうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"regret, repentance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"後悔","answer":["こうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"presenting to the public","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"公開","answer":["こうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"sail, voyage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"航海","answer":["こうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"engineering","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"工学","answer":["こうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"Imperial Palace","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"皇居","answer":["こうきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"prosperous conditions, healthy economy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"好況","answer":["こうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"protest, objection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抗議","answer":["こうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"mining industry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉱業","answer":["こうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"industrial enterprise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"興業","answer":["こうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"tableland, plateau","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高原","answer":["こうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"archaeology","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"考古学","answer":["こうこがく"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual, reciprocal, alternate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交互","answer":["こうご"]},
    {"meaning":"work, construction, handicraft, maneuvering","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"工作","answer":["こうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"cultivation, farming","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"耕作","answer":["こうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"mine (ore)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉱山","answer":["こうざん"]},
    {"meaning":"short course, training","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講習","answer":["こうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"negotiations, discussions, connection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"交渉","answer":["こうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"high, noble, refined, advanced","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"高尚","answer":["こうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"march, parade","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"行進","answer":["こうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"spices","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"香辛料","answer":["こうしんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"verbal statement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"口述","answer":["こうじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"subsidy, deduction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"控除","answer":["こうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"elevation, rise, improvement, advancement, progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向上","answer":["こうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"rainfall, precipitation","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"降水","answer":["こうすい"]},
    {"meaning":"flood","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"洪水","answer":["こうずい"]},
    {"meaning":"open (e.g. secret), public, official","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公然","answer":["こうぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"dispute, resistance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抗争","answer":["こうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"plan, plot, idea, conception","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構想","answer":["こうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"restriction, restraint","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拘束","answer":["こうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"retreat, backspace (BS)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"後退","answer":["こうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"brilliance, polish, lustre, glossy finish (of photographs)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"光沢","answer":["こうたく"]},
    {"meaning":"public corporation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"公団","answer":["こうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"favourable, promising, satisfactory, in good shape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好調","answer":["こうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"oral","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"口頭","answer":["こうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"reading, translation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"講読","answer":["こうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"subscription (e.g. magazine)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"購読","answer":["こうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"purchase, buy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"購入","answer":["こうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"official recognition, authorization, licence, accreditation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公認","answer":["こうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"cost of fuel and light","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"光熱費","answer":["こうねつひ"]},
    {"meaning":"ruin","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"荒廃","answer":["こうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"purchase, buy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"購買","answer":["こうばい"]},
    {"meaning":"popularity, favorable reputation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"好評","answer":["こうひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"delivering, furnishing (with copies)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交付","answer":["こうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"capitulation, surrender, submission","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"降伏","answer":["こうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"excitement, stimulation, agitation, arousal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"興奮","answer":["こうふん"]},
    {"meaning":"public appeal, public contribution","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"公募","answer":["こうぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"ingenious, skillful, clever, deft","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"巧妙","answer":["こうみょう"]},
    {"meaning":"government business, public use, public expense","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"公用","answer":["こうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"retail","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"小売","answer":["こうり"]},
    {"meaning":"efficiency","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"効率","answer":["こうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"public (institution)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"公立","answer":["こうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"short (build)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"小柄","answer":["こがら"]},
    {"meaning":"cheque, check","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"小切手","answer":["こぎって"]},
    {"meaning":"domestic products","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国産","answer":["こくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"state-sponsored, national","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国定","answer":["こくてい"]},
    {"meaning":"realm","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"国土","answer":["こくど"]},
    {"meaning":"confession, acknowledgement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"告白","answer":["こくはく"]},
    {"meaning":"national defence","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"国防","answer":["こくぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"national ownership","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"国有","answer":["こくゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"U.N., United Nations","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国連","answer":["こくれん"]},
    {"meaning":"black tea","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"焦げ茶","answer":["こげちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"individual, one by one","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個々","answer":["ここ"]},
    {"meaning":"individual, separate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"箇箇","answer":["ここ"]},
    {"meaning":"feeling, sensation, mood","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"心地","answer":["ここち"]},
    {"meaning":"knowledge, information","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心得","answer":["こころえ"]},
    {"meaning":"readiness, intention, aim","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心掛け","answer":["こころがけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear in mind, to aim to do","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心掛ける","answer":["こころがける"]},
    {"meaning":"will, intention, motive","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"志","answer":["こころざし"]},
    {"meaning":"to plan, to intend, to aspire to, to set aims (sights on)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"志す","answer":["こころざす"]},
    {"meaning":"heartening, reassuring","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"心強い","answer":["こころづよい"]},
    {"meaning":"helpless, forlorn, hopeless, unpromising, lonely, discouraging, disheartening","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"心細い","answer":["こころぼそい"]},
    {"meaning":"trial, experiment","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"試み","answer":["こころみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to try, to test","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"試みる","answer":["こころみる"]},
    {"meaning":"pleasant, agreeable","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"快い","answer":["こころよい"]},
    {"meaning":"to freeze, to congeal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"凝らす","answer":["こごらす","こらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to congeal, to freeze","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"凝る","answer":["こごる"]},
    {"meaning":"orphan","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"孤児","answer":["こじ"]},
    {"meaning":"the deceased, old friend","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"故人","answer":["こじん"]},
    {"meaning":"treetop","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"梢","answer":["こずえ"]},
    {"meaning":"individuality, personality, idiosyncrasy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個性","answer":["こせい"]},
    {"meaning":"census, family register","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"戸籍","answer":["こせき"]},
    {"meaning":"coins, small change","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"小銭","answer":["こぜに"]},
    {"meaning":"solid (body)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固体","answer":["こたい"]},
    {"meaning":"answer, response","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"答え","answer":["こたえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear, to stand, to endure, to put up with, to support, to withstand, to resist, to brave, to be fit for, t","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"堪える","answer":["こたえる","こらえる","たえる"]},
    {"meaning":"ancient times","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"古代","answer":["こだい"]},
    {"meaning":"exaggeration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誇張","answer":["こちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"diplomatic relations","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国交","answer":["こっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"fixation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固定","answer":["こてい"]},
    {"meaning":"matter, thing, affair, circumstance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"事柄","answer":["ことがら"]},
    {"meaning":"declaration, hearsay","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"言伝","answer":["ことづて"]},
    {"meaning":"especially, above all","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"殊に","answer":["ことに"]},
    {"meaning":"depending on the circumstances","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"事によると","answer":["ことによると"]},
    {"meaning":"isolation, loneliness, solitude","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"孤独","answer":["こどく"]},
    {"meaning":"in very small pieces","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"粉々","answer":["こなごな"]},
    {"meaning":"the other day, lately, recently","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"この間","answer":["このあいだ"]},
    {"meaning":"nice, likeable, desirable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好ましい","answer":["このましい"]},
    {"meaning":"particular case","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"個別","answer":["こべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"friendly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"細やか","answer":["こまやか","ささやか"]},
    {"meaning":"to be crowded","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混む","answer":["こむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to include, to put into","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"込める","answer":["こめる"]},
    {"meaning":"characteristic, tradition, peculiar, inherent, eigen-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"固有","answer":["こゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"employment (long term), hire","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"雇用","answer":["こよう"]},
    {"meaning":"calendar, almanac","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暦","answer":["こよみ"]},
    {"meaning":"isolation, helplessness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"孤立","answer":["こりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to learn by experience, to be disgusted with","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"懲りる","answer":["こりる"]},
    {"meaning":"patience, perseverance, energy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"根気","answer":["こんき"]},
    {"meaning":"basis, foundation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"根拠","answer":["こんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"mixed race, mixed parentage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混血","answer":["こんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"insect, bug","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"昆虫","answer":["こんちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"root, basis, foundation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"根底","answer":["こんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"confusion, mixing, merger","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"混同","answer":["こんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"hello, good day (daytime greeting id)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今日は","answer":["こんにちは"]},
    {"meaning":"good evening","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"今晩は","answer":["こんばんは"]},
    {"meaning":"origin, source, foundation, root, base, principle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"根本","answer":["こんぽん"]},
    {"meaning":"honourable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御","answer":["お","ご"]},
    {"meaning":"Buddhist karma, actions committed in a former life","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"業","answer":["ごう"]},
    {"meaning":"number, issue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"号","answer":["ごう"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement, consent, mutual understanding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合意","answer":["ごうい"]},
    {"meaning":"consultation, conference","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合議","answer":["ごうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"firm,strong","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強気","answer":["つよき","ごうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"synthesis, composition, synthetic, composite, mixed, combined, compound","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合成","answer":["ごうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"guard, convoy, escort","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"護衛","answer":["ごえい"]},
    {"meaning":"words, phrases","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"語句","answer":["ごく"]},
    {"meaning":"paradise","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"極楽","answer":["ごくらく"]},
    {"meaning":"Thank you very much for your....","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"ご苦労様","answer":["ごくろうさま"]},
    {"meaning":"word root, word derivation, etymology","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"語源","answer":["ごげん"]},
    {"meaning":"error","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤差","answer":["ごさ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be (polite), to exist","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"ご座います","answer":["ございます"]},
    {"meaning":"feast, treating (someone)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"ご馳走","answer":["ごちそう"]},
    {"meaning":"feast","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"ご馳走さま","answer":["ごちそうさま"]},
    {"meaning":"each respectively","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"毎","answer":["ごと"]},
    {"meaning":"Go board","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"碁盤","answer":["ごばん"]},
    {"meaning":"to deceive, to falsify, to misrepresent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤魔化す","answer":["ごまかす"]},
    {"meaning":"I beg your pardon, excuse me","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"御免なさい","answer":["ごめんなさい"]},
    {"meaning":"(please) look, (please) try to do","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"御覧なさい","answer":["ごらんなさい"]},
    {"meaning":"help","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"佐","answer":["さ"]},
    {"meaning":"re-, again, repeated","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再","answer":["さい"]},
    {"meaning":"difference, disparity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"差異","answer":["さい"]},
    {"meaning":"#NAME?","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歳","answer":["さい"]},
    {"meaning":"another meeting, meeting again, reunion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再会","answer":["さいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"calamity, disaster, misfortune","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"災害","answer":["さいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"bacillus, bacterium, germ","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"細菌","answer":["さいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"work, craftsmanship, tactics, trick","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"細工","answer":["さいく"]},
    {"meaning":"mining","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採掘","answer":["さいくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"vote, roll call","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採決","answer":["さいけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"rebuilding, reconstruction, rehabilitation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再建","answer":["さいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"reappearance, reproduction, return, revival","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再現","answer":["さいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"profit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採算","answer":["さいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"collecting, gathering","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採集","answer":["さいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"playback, regeneration, resuscitation, return to life, rebirth, reincarnation, narrow escape, reclamation, r","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再生","answer":["さいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"the very best","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"最善","answer":["さいぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"adoption, selection, choice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"採択","answer":["さいたく"]},
    {"meaning":"return, relapse, reoccurrence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"再発","answer":["さいはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"cultivation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"栽培","answer":["さいばい"]},
    {"meaning":"cell (biology)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"細胞","answer":["さいぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"use, adopt","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"採用","answer":["さいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to interrupt, to intercept, to obstruct","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遮る","answer":["さえぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be clear, to be serene, to be cold, to be skillful","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冴える","answer":["さえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to prosper, to flourish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"栄える","answer":["さかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"wine cups","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"杯","answer":["さかずき"]},
    {"meaning":"handstand, headstand","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆立ち","answer":["さかだち"]},
    {"meaning":"to go back, to go upstream, to make retroactive","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"逆上る","answer":["さかのぼる"]},
    {"meaning":"to prosper, to flourish, to copulate (animals)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盛る","answer":["さかる","もる"]},
    {"meaning":"balance, difference, margin","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差額","answer":["さがく"]},
    {"meaning":"to hang down, to abate, to retire, to fall, to step back","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下がる","answer":["さがる"]},
    {"meaning":"two days before yesterday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一昨昨日","answer":["さきおととい"]},
    {"meaning":"before, earlier than, ahead, beyond, away, previously, recently","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先に","answer":["さきに"]},
    {"meaning":"fraud, swindle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"詐欺","answer":["さぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"a work, a harvest","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作","answer":["さく"]},
    {"meaning":"plan, policy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"策","answer":["さく"]},
    {"meaning":"cut, reduction, curtailment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"削減","answer":["さくげん"]},
    {"meaning":"mistake","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"錯誤","answer":["さくご"]},
    {"meaning":"military or naval operations, tactics, strategy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作戦","answer":["さくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"produce (e.g. agricultural),crops","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作物","answer":["さくもつ","さくぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"shout, scream, outcry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"叫び","answer":["さけび"]},
    {"meaning":"to split, to tear, to burst","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裂ける","answer":["さける"]},
    {"meaning":"to come near to, to approach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し掛かる","answer":["さしかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"instruction, mandate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指図","answer":["さしず"]},
    {"meaning":"to present, to submit, to tender, to hold out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し出す","answer":["さしだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to interfere, to hinder, to become impeded","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し支える","answer":["さしつかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to deduct","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し引く","answer":["さしひく"]},
    {"meaning":"to grant, to award, to teach","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"授ける","answer":["さずける"]},
    {"meaning":"to become settled, to be fixed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定まる","answer":["さだまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to decide, to establish, to determine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定める","answer":["さだめる"]},
    {"meaning":"optical illusion, hallucination","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"錯覚","answer":["さっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"urgent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"早急","answer":["さっきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to guess, to sense, to presume, to judge, to sympathize with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"察する","answer":["さっする"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for books","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"冊","answer":["さつ"]},
    {"meaning":"murder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"殺人","answer":["さつじん"]},
    {"meaning":"to attain enlightenment, to perceive, to understand, to discern","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"悟る","answer":["さとる"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真実","answer":["しんじつ","さな","さね"]},
    {"meaning":"to judge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裁く","answer":["さばく"]},
    {"meaning":"(not) very, (not) much","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"左程","answer":["さほど"]},
    {"meaning":"way,manner,kind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様","answer":["よう","さま"]},
    {"meaning":"three-stringed Japanese guitar, shamisen","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"三味線","answer":["さみせん"]},
    {"meaning":"Samurai, warrior","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"侍","answer":["さむらい"]},
    {"meaning":"action, operation, effect, function","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作用","answer":["さよう"]},
    {"meaning":"good-bye","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"左様なら","answer":["さようなら"]},
    {"meaning":"fresh, refreshing, invigorating, clear, fluent, eloquent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"爽やか","answer":["さわやか"]},
    {"meaning":"acid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酸","answer":["さん"]},
    {"meaning":"oxidation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酸化","answer":["さんか"]},
    {"meaning":"mountains","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"山岳","answer":["さんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"maternity leave","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産休","answer":["さんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"wharf, bridge, jetty, pier","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"桟橋","answer":["さんきょう","さんばし"]},
    {"meaning":"House of Councillors","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参議院","answer":["さんぎいん"]},
    {"meaning":"postpartum, after childbirth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産後","answer":["さんご"]},
    {"meaning":"yield, produce","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産出","answer":["さんしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"reference, consultation, consultation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"参照","answer":["さんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"calling on, visiting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参上","answer":["さんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"approval, agreement, support, favour","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"賛成","answer":["さんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"praise, adoration, glorification","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"賛美","answer":["さんび"]},
    {"meaning":"maternity and gynecology department","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産婦人科","answer":["さんふじんか"]},
    {"meaning":"product, result, fruit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産物","answer":["さんぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"hillside, mountainside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"山腹","answer":["さんぷく"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain range","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"山脈","answer":["さんみゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"fortune, riches","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"財","answer":["ざい"]},
    {"meaning":"source of funds, resources, finances","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"財源","answer":["ざいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"stockpile, stock","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"在庫","answer":["ざいこ"]},
    {"meaning":"economy, financial affairs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"財政","answer":["ざいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"symposium, round-table discussion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"座談会","answer":["ざだんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"miscellaneous goods, general goods, sundries","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"雑貨","answer":["ざっか"]},
    {"meaning":"chatting, idle talk","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"雑談","answer":["ざつだん"]},
    {"meaning":"various kinds of small trees, assorted trees","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"雑木","answer":["ざつぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"coordinate(s)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"座標","answer":["ざひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"remaining money","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残金","answer":["ざんきん"]},
    {"meaning":"cruelty, harshness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"残酷","answer":["ざんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"(bank) balance, remainder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残高","answer":["ざんだか"]},
    {"meaning":"death, decease","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"死","answer":["し"]},
    {"meaning":"next","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次","answer":["つぎ","し"]},
    {"meaning":"finish, end, completion","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕上がり","answer":["しあがり"]},
    {"meaning":"end, finishing touches, being finished","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕上げ","answer":["しあげ"]},
    {"meaning":"to finish up, to complete","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕上げる","answer":["しあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"two days after tomorrow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明々後日","answer":["しあさって"]},
    {"meaning":"breeding, raising, rearing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飼育","answer":["しいく"]},
    {"meaning":"by force","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強いて","answer":["しいて"]},
    {"meaning":"to force, to compel, to coerce","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強いる","answer":["しいる"]},
    {"meaning":"to lay in stock, to replenish stock, to procure","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕入れる","answer":["しいれる"]},
    {"meaning":"dentistry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歯科","answer":["しか"]},
    {"meaning":"qualifications, requirements, capabilities","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資格","answer":["しかく"]},
    {"meaning":"sense of sight, vision","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"視覚","answer":["しかく"]},
    {"meaning":"device, trick, mechanism, gadget, (small) scale, half finished, commencement, set up, challenge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"仕掛け","answer":["しかけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to commence, to lay (mines), to set (traps), to wage (war), to challenge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"仕掛ける","answer":["しかける"]},
    {"meaning":"nevertheless, however","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"然しながら","answer":["しかしながら"]},
    {"meaning":"urban areas, the streets, town, city","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"市街","answer":["しがい"]},
    {"meaning":"command, direction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"指揮","answer":["しき"]},
    {"meaning":"colour, hue, tints","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"色彩","answer":["しきさい"]},
    {"meaning":"ceremonial hall, place of ceremony (e.g. marriage)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"式場","answer":["しきじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to partition, to divide, to mark off, to settle accounts, to toe the mark","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕切る","answer":["しきる"]},
    {"meaning":"funds, capital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資金","answer":["しきん"]},
    {"meaning":"1. execution, enforcing, carrying out","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"施行","answer":["しぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"devising, plan, plot, contrivance, construction, arrangement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"仕組み","answer":["しくみ"]},
    {"meaning":"death penalty, capital punishment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"死刑","answer":["しけい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be damp, to be moist","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"湿気る","answer":["しける"]},
    {"meaning":"thought","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"思考","answer":["しこう"]},
    {"meaning":"intention, aim","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"志向","answer":["しこう"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection, observation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"視察","answer":["しさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"property, fortune, means, assets","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資産","answer":["しさん"]},
    {"meaning":"support, maintenance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支持","answer":["しじ"]},
    {"meaning":"indication, instruction, directions","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指示","answer":["しじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to sink, to submerge","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沈める","answer":["しずめる"]},
    {"meaning":"institution, establishment, facility, (army) engineer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"施設","answer":["しせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"son","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"子息","answer":["しそく"]},
    {"meaning":"to yearn for, to miss, to adore, to love dearly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"慕う","answer":["したう"]},
    {"meaning":"therefore, consequently, in accordance with","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従って","answer":["したがって"]},
    {"meaning":"secret intention, motive","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"下心","answer":["したごころ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be intimate with, to befriend","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"親しむ","answer":["したしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"preliminary investigation, preparation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下調べ","answer":["したしらべ"]},
    {"meaning":"groundwork, foundation, inclination, aptitude, elementary knowledge of, grounding in, prearrangement, spade","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"下地","answer":["したじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to recognize,to appreciate,to approve,to admit,to notice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"認める","answer":["みとめる","したためる"]},
    {"meaning":"to tailor, to make, to prepare, to train, to send (a messenger)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕立てる","answer":["したてる"]},
    {"meaning":"trade in, part exchange","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下取り","answer":["したどり"]},
    {"meaning":"burning low, waning, declining","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下火","answer":["したび"]},
    {"meaning":"disqualification, elimination, incapacity (legal)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失格","answer":["しっかく"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, modesty, frugality","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"質素","answer":["しっそ"]},
    {"meaning":"lack of harmony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失調","answer":["しっちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"room","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"室","answer":["しつ"]},
    {"meaning":"question","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"質疑","answer":["しつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be used to a job, to begin to do, to baste, to tack, to plant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"仕付ける","answer":["しつける"]},
    {"meaning":"pointing out, identification","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"指摘","answer":["してき"]},
    {"meaning":"opinion, point of view, visual point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"視点","answer":["してん"]},
    {"meaning":"to outdo, to surpass, to endure, to keep out (rain), to stave off, to tide over, to pull through, to defy, t","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"凌ぐ","answer":["しのぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"first train","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"始発","answer":["しはつ"]},
    {"meaning":"lawn, sod, turf","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"芝","answer":["しば"]},
    {"meaning":"little while","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暫く","answer":["しばらく"]},
    {"meaning":"1. tasteful (clothing), cool, an aura of refined masculinity, 2. astringent, sullen, bitter (taste), 3","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"渋い","answer":["しぶい"]},
    {"meaning":"private property, personal effects","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"私物","answer":["しぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"administration of justice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"司法","answer":["しほう"]},
    {"meaning":"fat, grease, blubber","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脂肪","answer":["しぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"wish, desire, ambition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"志望","answer":["しぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"end, termination, informal (Noh play)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"仕舞","answer":["しまい"]},
    {"meaning":"management, dealing, settlement, cleaning up afterwards","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"始末","answer":["しまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"keenly, deeply, heartily","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"泌み泌み","answer":["しみじみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pierce, to permeate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"染みる","answer":["しみる"]},
    {"meaning":"mission, errand, message","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"使命","answer":["しめい"]},
    {"meaning":"closing, cut-off, end, deadline, Closed, No Entrance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"締め切り","answer":["しめきり"]},
    {"meaning":"manservant, servant (of God)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"僕","answer":["しもべ","ぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"social life, social intercourse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"社交","answer":["しゃこう"]},
    {"meaning":"refusal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"謝絶","answer":["しゃぜつ"]},
    {"meaning":"company owned house","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"社宅","answer":["しゃたく"]},
    {"meaning":"slope, slanting surface, bevel","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"斜面","answer":["しゃめん"]},
    {"meaning":"field of vision, outlook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"視野","answer":["しや"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) seed,(2) material,(3) cause,source","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"種","answer":["たね","しゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"masses, great number, the people","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衆","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"circuit, lap, circumference, vicinity, Chou (dynasty)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"周","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"earnings, proceeds, returns","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"収益","answer":["しゅうえき"]},
    {"meaning":"learning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修学","answer":["しゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"cycle, period","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"周期","answer":["しゅうき"]},
    {"meaning":"Lower House, House of Representatives","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衆議院","answer":["しゅうぎいん"]},
    {"meaning":"employment, starting work","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"就業","answer":["しゅうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pursuit of knowledge, studying, learning, training, ascetic practice, discipline","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修行","answer":["しゅうぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"totalization, aggregate","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"集計","answer":["しゅうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"attack, charge, raid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"襲撃","answer":["しゅうげき"]},
    {"meaning":"income and expenditure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収支","answer":["しゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"beginning and end, from beginning to end, doing a thing from beginning to end","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"終始","answer":["しゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"Masters degree program","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修士","answer":["しゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"gathering up, collection, accumulation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収集","answer":["しゅうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ornamentation, embellishment, decoration, adornment, polish up (writing), modification (gram)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修飾","answer":["しゅうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"all day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"終日","answer":["しゅうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"attachment, adhesion, tenacity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"執着","answer":["しゅうじゃく","しゅうちゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"accommodation, reception, seating, housing, custody, admission, entering (in a dictionary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収容","answer":["しゅうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"completion (of a course)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修了","answer":["しゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"security guard, doorkeeper","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"守衛","answer":["しゅえい"]},
    {"meaning":"starring, playing the leading part","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主演","answer":["しゅえん"]},
    {"meaning":"subjectivity, subject, ego","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主観","answer":["しゅかん"]},
    {"meaning":"celebration, congratulations","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"祝賀","answer":["しゅくが"]},
    {"meaning":"fate, destiny, predestination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"宿命","answer":["しゅくめい"]},
    {"meaning":"sovereignty, supremacy, dominion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主権","answer":["しゅけん"]},
    {"meaning":"handicrafts","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"手芸","answer":["しゅげい"]},
    {"meaning":"organization, sponsorship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"主催","answer":["しゅさい"]},
    {"meaning":"choice of subject, collecting data","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"取材","answer":["しゅざい"]},
    {"meaning":"object, meaning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"趣旨","answer":["しゅし"]},
    {"meaning":"staple food","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主食","answer":["しゅしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"protagonist, main character, hero(ine) (of a story), head of household","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主人公","answer":["しゅじんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"subject, main constituent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主体","answer":["しゅたい"]},
    {"meaning":"subject, theme, motif","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主題","answer":["しゅだい"]},
    {"meaning":"bleeding, haemorrhage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"出血","answer":["しゅっけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(child)birth, delivery, production (of goods)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出産","answer":["しゅっさん"]},
    {"meaning":"arrival (in a country at work etc.)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出社","answer":["しゅっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"birth","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出生","answer":["しゅっしょう","しゅっせい"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion, successful career, eminence","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出世","answer":["しゅっせ"]},
    {"meaning":"expenses, disbursements","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出費","answer":["しゅっぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibit, display","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出品","answer":["しゅっぴん"]},
    {"meaning":"performance, stage appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出演","answer":["しゅつえん"]},
    {"meaning":"proposing a question","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出題","answer":["しゅつだい"]},
    {"meaning":"sailing, marching, going out","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出動","answer":["しゅつどう"]},
    {"meaning":"main leadership","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"主導","answer":["しゅどう"]},
    {"meaning":"person in charge, responsible official","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主任","answer":["しゅにん"]},
    {"meaning":"head, brains","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"首脳","answer":["しゅのう"]},
    {"meaning":"defense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"守備","answer":["しゅび"]},
    {"meaning":"technique","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手法","answer":["しゅほう"]},
    {"meaning":"private ownership","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"私有","answer":["しゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"various, many, several","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"諸","answer":["しょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be burdened with,to carry on back or shoulder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背負う","answer":["せおう","しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"elephant","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"象","answer":["ぞう","しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"illness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"症","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"wound, injury, hurt, cut, gash, bruise, scratch, scar, weak point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"傷","answer":["しょう","きず"]},
    {"meaning":"quotient","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"elimination, erasing, dying out, melting away","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消去","answer":["しょうきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"shock, crash, impact, ballistic","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衝撃","answer":["しょうげき"]},
    {"meaning":"evidence, testimony","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"証言","answer":["しょうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"evidence, proof","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"証拠","answer":["しょうこ"]},
    {"meaning":"exhaustion, consumption","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"消耗","answer":["しょうこう","しょうもう"]},
    {"meaning":"collation, comparison","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照合","answer":["しょうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"detail, particulars","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"詳細","answer":["しょうさい"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"昇進","answer":["しょうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"minority, few","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"少数","answer":["しょうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"to pretend, to take the name of, to feign, to purport","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"称する","answer":["しょうする"]},
    {"meaning":"news, letter, circumstances","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消息","answer":["しょうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"consent, acquiescence, agreement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"承諾","answer":["しょうだく"]},
    {"meaning":"symbol","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"象徴","answer":["しょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pediatrics","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"小児科","answer":["しょうにか"]},
    {"meaning":"witness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"証人","answer":["しょうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"illumination","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照明","answer":["しょうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"victory, triumph, conquest, success, win","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝利","answer":["しょうり"]},
    {"meaning":"encouragement, promotion, message, address","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奨励","answer":["しょうれい"]},
    {"meaning":"staff member, personnel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職員","answer":["しょくいん"]},
    {"meaning":"colony","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"植民地","answer":["しょくみんち"]},
    {"meaning":"professional duties","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職務","answer":["しょくむ"]},
    {"meaning":"Gentlemen!, Ladies!","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"諸君","answer":["しょくん"]},
    {"meaning":"whereabouts","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所在","answer":["しょざい"]},
    {"meaning":"here and there,some parts (of something)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所々","answer":["ところどころ","しょしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"possession, owning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所持","answer":["しょじ"]},
    {"meaning":"attached to, belong to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"所属","answer":["しょぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"処置","answer":["しょち"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed, prescribed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所定","answer":["しょてい"]},
    {"meaning":"income, earnings","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所得","answer":["しょとく"]},
    {"meaning":"first edition","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"初版","answer":["しょはん"]},
    {"meaning":"punishment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"処罰","answer":["しょばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"book review","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"書評","answer":["しょひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"masses, common people","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"庶民","answer":["しょみん"]},
    {"meaning":"general affairs","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"庶務","answer":["しょむ"]},
    {"meaning":"personal use, private business","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"私用","answer":["しよう"]},
    {"meaning":"way, method, resource, remedy, (technical) specification","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"仕様","answer":["しよう"]},
    {"meaning":"employee, servant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"使用人","answer":["しようにん"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation, investigation, inspection","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調べ","answer":["しらべ"]},
    {"meaning":"acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知り合い","answer":["しりあい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to retreat,to recede,to withdraw","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退く","answer":["どく","しりぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove,to take away,to dislodge,to put something out of the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退ける","answer":["どける","しりぞける","のける"]},
    {"meaning":"to note, to write down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記す","answer":["しるす"]},
    {"meaning":"orders, instructions, directive","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"指令","answer":["しれい"]},
    {"meaning":"price, materials, substitution","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代","answer":["しろ"]},
    {"meaning":"new","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"新","answer":["しん"]},
    {"meaning":"evolution, progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進化","answer":["しんか"]},
    {"meaning":"rear, rear unit guard","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"殿","answer":["しんがり"]},
    {"meaning":"deliberation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"審議","answer":["しんぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"advance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進行","answer":["しんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"rising, developing, emergent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"新興","answer":["しんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion, encouragement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振興","answer":["しんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"report, statement, filing a return, notification","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申告","answer":["しんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"newly-wed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"新婚","answer":["しんこん"]},
    {"meaning":"judging, inspection, examination, investigation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"審査","answer":["しんさ"]},
    {"meaning":"gentleman","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紳士","answer":["しんし"]},
    {"meaning":"advance, step forward","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進出","answer":["しんしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"believer, adherent, devotee, Christian","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信者","answer":["しんじゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"pearl","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"真珠","answer":["しんじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"double suicide, lovers suicide","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"心中","answer":["しんじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"mentality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心情","answer":["しんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"new face, newcomer","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"新人","answer":["しんじん"]},
    {"meaning":"holiness, sacredness, dignity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"神聖","answer":["しんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"friendship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"親善","answer":["しんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, real situation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真相","answer":["しんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"new building, new construction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"新築","answer":["しんちく"]},
    {"meaning":"presentation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"進呈","answer":["しんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"progress, development","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"進展","answer":["しんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"temple, sacred place","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"神殿","answer":["しんでん"]},
    {"meaning":"progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進度","answer":["しんど"]},
    {"meaning":"oscillation, vibration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振動","answer":["しんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"freshman, first-year student","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"新入生","answer":["しんにゅうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"trust, confidence, credence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信任","answer":["しんにん"]},
    {"meaning":"refereeing, trial, judgement, umpire, referee","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"審判","answer":["しんばん","しんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"mystery","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"神秘","answer":["しんぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"patience, endurance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辛抱","answer":["しんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"truth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真理","answer":["しんり"]},
    {"meaning":"aggression, invasion, raid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"侵略","answer":["しんりゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"medical examination and treatment, diagnosis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"診療","answer":["しんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"course, route","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進路","answer":["しんろ"]},
    {"meaning":"self-conscious","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自覚","answer":["じかく"]},
    {"meaning":"area,locality,district,region,the coast","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地方","answer":["ちほう","じかた"]},
    {"meaning":"self, the ego","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"自我","answer":["じが"]},
    {"meaning":"magnetism","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"磁気","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"porcelain, china","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"磁器","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"project, enterprise, business, industry, operations","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"事業","answer":["じぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"terrain, geographical features, topography","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地形","answer":["じぎょう","ちけい"]},
    {"meaning":"axis, stem, shaft, axle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"軸","answer":["じく"]},
    {"meaning":"self, oneself","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"自己","answer":["じこ"]},
    {"meaning":"matter, item, facts","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"事項","answer":["じこう"]},
    {"meaning":"table, diagram, chart, timetable, schedule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時刻表","answer":["じこくひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"hell","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"地獄","answer":["じごく"]},
    {"meaning":"time difference","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時差","answer":["じさ"]},
    {"meaning":"freely, at will","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自在","answer":["じざい"]},
    {"meaning":"independence, autonomy","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自主","answer":["じしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"surrender, give oneself up","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自首","answer":["じしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"resignation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"辞職","answer":["じしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"self-confidence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自信","answer":["じしん"]},
    {"meaning":"prior, beforehand, in advance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"事前","answer":["じぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"self-respect, conceit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"自尊心","answer":["じそんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"continuation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"持続","answer":["じぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"type, font, lettering","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"字体","answer":["じたい"]},
    {"meaning":"refusal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"辞退","answer":["じたい"]},
    {"meaning":"substance, essence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実質","answer":["じっしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, put into practice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"実践","answer":["じっせん"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, fact","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"実態","answer":["じったい"]},
    {"meaning":"actual expense, cost price","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実費","answer":["じっぴ"]},
    {"meaning":"fruit,nut,seed,content,good result","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実","answer":["み","じつ"]},
    {"meaning":"industrialist, businessman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実業家","answer":["じつぎょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"real condition, actual circumstances, actual state of affairs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実情","answer":["じつじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"rotation, spin","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自転","answer":["じてん"]},
    {"meaning":"intransitive verb (no direct obj)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"自動詞","answer":["じどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"landlord","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地主","answer":["じぬし"]},
    {"meaning":"otolaryngology","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"耳鼻科","answer":["じびか"]},
    {"meaning":"local","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地元","answer":["じもと"]},
    {"meaning":"weakness, the weak, little less then","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱","answer":["じゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"some, few, number of","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"若干","answer":["じゃっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"gravel, ballast, pebbles","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"砂利","answer":["じゃり"]},
    {"meaning":"rock-scissors-paper game","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"じゃん拳","answer":["じゃんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"dwelling, living","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"住","answer":["じゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"employee, worker","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従業員","answer":["じゅうぎょういん"]},
    {"meaning":"engaging, pursuing, following","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従事","answer":["じゅうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"fullness, completion, perfection, substantiality, enrichment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"充実","answer":["じゅうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"crossroads","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"十字路","answer":["じゅうじろ"]},
    {"meaning":"flexible, lithe","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"柔軟","answer":["じゅうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"duplication, repetition, overlapping, redundancy, restoration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"重複","answer":["じゅうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"priceless treasure, convenience, usefulness","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"重宝","answer":["じゅうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"up to now, so far, traditional","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従来","answer":["じゅうらい"]},
    {"meaning":"coaching school, lessons","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"塾","answer":["じゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"trees and shrubs, arbour","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"樹木","answer":["じゅもく"]},
    {"meaning":"establish, create","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"樹立","answer":["じゅりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"local express (train slower than an express)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"準急","answer":["じゅんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to follow, to conform, to apply to","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"準じる","answer":["じゅんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to apply correspondingly, to correspond to, to be proportionate to, to conform to","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"準ずる","answer":["じゅんずる"]},
    {"meaning":"feelings, emotion, passion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情","answer":["じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese straw mat","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"畳","answer":["たたみ","じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"jailer, old man, rank, company officer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尉","answer":["じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"young woman","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嬢","answer":["じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"shape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"状","answer":["じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"superior (rank not class), higher order (e.g. byte), host computer (of connected device)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上位","answer":["じょうい"]},
    {"meaning":"performance (e.g. music)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上演","answer":["じょうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"land near the castle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"城下","answer":["じょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"passenger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗客","answer":["じょうきゃく","じょうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"sky, the skies, high-altitude sky, upper air","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"上空","answer":["じょうくう"]},
    {"meaning":"superior authorities, boss","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"上司","answer":["じょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"emotion, feeling","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情緒","answer":["じょうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"rising, ascending, climbing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"上昇","answer":["じょうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"state of things, condition, situation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"情勢","answer":["じょうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"passion, enthusiasm, zeal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情熱","answer":["じょうねつ"]},
    {"meaning":"concession, conciliation, compromise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"譲歩","answer":["じょうほ"]},
    {"meaning":"treaty, pact","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"条約","answer":["じょうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"landing, disembarkation","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上陸","answer":["じょうりく"]},
    {"meaning":"distillation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蒸留","answer":["じょうりゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"exception, exclusion","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"除外","answer":["じょがい"]},
    {"meaning":"advice, suggestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助言","answer":["じょげん"]},
    {"meaning":"going slowly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徐行","answer":["じょこう"]},
    {"meaning":"Ms.","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"女史","answer":["じょし"]},
    {"meaning":"particle, postposition","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"助詞","answer":["じょし"]},
    {"meaning":"auxiliary verb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"助動詞","answer":["じょどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"independence, self-reliance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自立","answer":["じりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"personality, character, individuality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人格","answer":["じんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"man of talent","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"人材","answer":["じんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"quick, fast, rapid, swift, prompt","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"迅速","answer":["じんそく"]},
    {"meaning":"human body","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人体","answer":["じんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"people, public","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人民","answer":["じんみん"]},
    {"meaning":"glimpse, public gaze","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人目","answer":["じんもく"]},
    {"meaning":"1. moisture, dampness, vapor, 2. dropsy, edema","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"水気","answer":["すいき"]},
    {"meaning":"source of river, fountainhead","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"水源","answer":["すいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"propulsion, driving force","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"推進","answer":["すいしん"]},
    {"meaning":"flushing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水洗","answer":["すいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"playing wind instruments","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"吹奏","answer":["すいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"guess, conjecture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"推測","answer":["すいそく"]},
    {"meaning":"(water-filled) paddy field","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"水田","answer":["すいでん"]},
    {"meaning":"reasoning, inference, mystery or detective genre (movie novel etc.)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"推理","answer":["すいり"]},
    {"meaning":"numeral","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"数詞","answer":["すうし"]},
    {"meaning":"worship, adoration, admiration, cult","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"崇拝","answer":["すうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"to install, to equip, to mount","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"据え付ける","answer":["すえつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to set (table), to lay (foundation), to place (gun), to apply (moxa)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"据える","answer":["すえる"]},
    {"meaning":"past, after","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過ぎ","answer":["すぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"help, aid, relief","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"救い","answer":["すくい"]},
    {"meaning":"at least","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少なくとも","answer":["すくなくとも"]},
    {"meaning":"immediately, soon, easily, right (near), honest, upright","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直ぐ","answer":["すぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"vigorous, healthy, sound","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"健やか","answer":["すこやか"]},
    {"meaning":"progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進み","answer":["すすみ"]},
    {"meaning":"recommendation, advice, encouragement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勧め","answer":["すすめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to go out of use, to become obsolete, to die out, to go out of fashion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"廃れる","answer":["すたれる"]},
    {"meaning":"sour, acid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酸っぱい","answer":["すっぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"lovely, dreamy, beautiful, great, fantastic, superb, cool, capital","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素敵","answer":["すてき"]},
    {"meaning":"fast, quick, prompt, agile","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素早い","answer":["すばやい"]},
    {"meaning":"to finish, to get it over with, to settle, to conclude, to pay back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"済ます","answer":["すます"]},
    {"meaning":"to clear, to make clear, to be unruffled, to look unconcerned, to look demure, look prim, put on airs","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"澄ます","answer":["すます"]},
    {"meaning":"Emperor of Japan","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"天皇","answer":["すめらぎ","てんのう"]},
    {"meaning":"printing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刷り","answer":["すり"]},
    {"meaning":"chance encounter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"擦れ違い","answer":["すれちがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass by one another, to disagree, to miss each other","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"すれ違う","answer":["すれちがう"]},
    {"meaning":"to rub, to chafe, to wear, to become sophisticated","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"擦れる","answer":["すれる"]},
    {"meaning":"impudent, shameless","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"図々しい","answer":["ずうずうしい"]},
    {"meaning":"system, organization, imperial command, laws, regulation, control, government, suppression, restraint, holdin","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"-made, make","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"製","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"growth, development, breeding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生育","answer":["せいいく"]},
    {"meaning":"results, fruits","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成果","answer":["せいか"]},
    {"meaning":"correct, right, correct interpretation (answer solution)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正解","answer":["せいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"regular, legal, formal, established, legitimate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正規","answer":["せいき"]},
    {"meaning":"justice, right, righteousness, correct meaning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"正義","answer":["せいぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"livelihood, living","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生計","answer":["せいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"administration, political power","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"政権","answer":["せいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"elaborate, delicate, exquisite","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"精巧","answer":["せいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"restraint, sanctions, punishment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"制裁","answer":["せいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"political measures, policy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"政策","answer":["せいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"liquidation, settlement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清算","answer":["せいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"constellation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"星座","answer":["せいざ"]},
    {"meaning":"life and death","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生死","answer":["せいし"]},
    {"meaning":"stillness, repose, standing still","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"静止","answer":["せいし"]},
    {"meaning":"youth, springtime of life, adolescent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"青春","answer":["せいしゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"Bible, scriptures","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"聖書","answer":["せいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"sincere, honest, faithful","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誠実","answer":["せいじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"maturity, ripeness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"成熟","answer":["せいじゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"purity, innocence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"清純","answer":["せいじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"normalcy, normality, normal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正常","answer":["せいじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to control, to command, to get the better of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制する","answer":["せいする"]},
    {"meaning":"orderly, regular, well-organized, trim, accurate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整然","answer":["せいぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"be dressed up, wear rich clothes","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盛装","answer":["せいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"grand, prosperous, magnificent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盛大","answer":["せいだい"]},
    {"meaning":"good and evil, purity and impurity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"清濁","answer":["せいだく"]},
    {"meaning":"enactment, establishment, creation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制定","answer":["せいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"iron manufacture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"製鉄","answer":["せいてつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fine weather","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"晴天","answer":["せいてん"]},
    {"meaning":"just, justifiable, right, due, proper, equitable, reasonable, legitimate, lawful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正当","answer":["せいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"majority, adult age","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成年","answer":["せいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"uniform","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制服","answer":["せいふく"]},
    {"meaning":"conquest, subjugation, overcoming","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"征服","answer":["せいふく"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacturing method, recipe, formula","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"製法","answer":["せいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"precise, exact, detailed, minute, close","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"精密","answer":["せいみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"declaration, statement, proclamation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"声明","answer":["せいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"full name","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"姓名","answer":["せいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"limitation, restriction, condition, constraints","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制約","answer":["せいやく"]},
    {"meaning":"physiology, menses","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生理","answer":["せいり"]},
    {"meaning":"influence, power, might, strength, potency, force, energy","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"勢力","answer":["せいりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"stand in a row, form a line","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整列","answer":["せいれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to hurry, to urge on","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"急かす","answer":["せかす"]},
    {"meaning":"duty, obligation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"責務","answer":["せきむ"]},
    {"meaning":"flattery, compliment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"世辞","answer":["せじ"]},
    {"meaning":"household","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"世帯","answer":["せたい"]},
    {"meaning":"generation, the world, the age","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世代","answer":["せだい"]},
    {"meaning":"clearing (land), opening up, cutting through","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切開","answer":["せっかい"]},
    {"meaning":"touch, contact","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接触","answer":["せっしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, institution","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設置","answer":["せっち"]},
    {"meaning":"compromise, cross, blending, eclecticism","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"折衷","answer":["せっちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, creation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設定","answer":["せってい"]},
    {"meaning":"persuasion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"説得","answer":["せっとく"]},
    {"meaning":"node, section, occasion, time","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"節","answer":["せつ","ふし"]},
    {"meaning":"compelling, serious, severe, acute, earnest, pressing, urgent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"切実","answer":["せつじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"conjunction","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接続詞","answer":["せつぞくし"]},
    {"meaning":"painful, trying, oppressive, suffocating","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切ない","answer":["せつない"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, foundation, institution","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設立","answer":["せつりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"attack, offence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"攻め","answer":["せめ"]},
    {"meaning":"public opinion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"世論","answer":["せろん"]},
    {"meaning":"hermit, wizard","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仙","answer":["せん"]},
    {"meaning":"fibre, fiber, textile","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"繊維","answer":["せんい"]},
    {"meaning":"election","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"選挙","answer":["せんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"religious mission","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宣教","answer":["せんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"declaration, proclamation, announcement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宣言","answer":["せんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"preceding, going first","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先行","answer":["せんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"selection, screening","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"選考","answer":["せんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"war damage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"戦災","answer":["せんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"specialization","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"専修","answer":["せんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"tactics","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦術","answer":["せんじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"diving","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"潜水","answer":["せんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"month before last","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先先月","answer":["せんせんげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"week before last","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"先先週","answer":["せんせんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"family predecessor, previous age, previous generation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"先代","answer":["せんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"recently, the other day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先だって","answer":["せんだって"]},
    {"meaning":"first arrival","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"先着","answer":["せんちゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"battle, fight, combat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦闘","answer":["せんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"infiltration, sneaking in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"潜入","answer":["せんにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"船舶","answer":["せんぱく"]},
    {"meaning":"exclusive use, personal use","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"専用","answer":["せんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"occupation, capture, possession, have a room to oneself","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"占領","answer":["せんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"war potential","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦力","answer":["せんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"tax office","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"税務署","answer":["ぜいむしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"correction, revision","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"是正","answer":["ぜせい"]},
    {"meaning":"out of print","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"絶版","answer":["ぜっぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"despair, hopelessness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶望","answer":["ぜつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"Zen (Buddhism)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"禅","answer":["ぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"complete recovery of health","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"全快","answer":["ぜんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"height of prosperity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"全盛","answer":["ぜんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"preamble, premise, reason, prerequisite","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"前提","answer":["ぜんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"future prospects, outlook, the journey ahead","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"前途","answer":["ぜんと"]},
    {"meaning":"annihilation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"全滅","answer":["ぜんめつ"]},
    {"meaning":"goodness, excellence, virtue","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"善良","answer":["ぜんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"precedent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"前例","answer":["ぜんれい"]},
    {"meaning":"monk, priest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"僧","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"to run along, to follow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沿う","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"to accompany, to become married, to comply with","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"添う","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"whole, all, general, gross","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"総","answer":["そう"]},
    {"meaning":"suitability, fitness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"相応","answer":["そうおう"]},
    {"meaning":"general meeting","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"総会","answer":["そうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"launching (e.g. newspaper), first issue","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"創刊","answer":["そうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"remittance, sending money","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"送金","answer":["そうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"running a wheeled vehicle (e.g. car), traveling","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"走行","answer":["そうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"synthesis, coordination, putting together, integration, composite","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"総合","answer":["そうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"search (esp. in criminal investigations), investigation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"捜査","answer":["そうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"search (esp. for someone or something missing), investigation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"捜索","answer":["そうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"and, like that","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"然うして","answer":["そうして"]},
    {"meaning":"ornament","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"装飾","answer":["そうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"management, handling, control, manipulation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"操縦","answer":["そうじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"creation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"創造","answer":["そうぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"magnificent, grand, majestic, splendid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"壮大","answer":["そうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"strife, riot, rebellion","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"騒動","answer":["そうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"disaster, shipwreck, accident","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遭難","answer":["そうなん"]},
    {"meaning":"market price, speculation, estimation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相場","answer":["そうば"]},
    {"meaning":"equipment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"装備","answer":["そうび"]},
    {"meaning":"establishment, founding, organization","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"創立","answer":["そうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to add to, to attach, to append, to accompany, to garnish, to imitate, to annex","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"添える","answer":["そえる"]},
    {"meaning":"immediately, right away","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"即座に","answer":["そくざに"]},
    {"meaning":"promotion, acceleration, encouragement, facilitation, spurring on","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"促進","answer":["そくしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to conform to, to agree with, to be adapted to, to be based on","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"即する","answer":["そくする"]},
    {"meaning":"restraint, shackles, restriction, confinement, binding","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"束縛","answer":["そくばく"]},
    {"meaning":"side, flank, sidelight, lateral","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"側面","answer":["そくめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to harm, to hurt, to injure, to damage, to fail in doing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損なう","answer":["そこなう"]},
    {"meaning":"raw materials, subject matter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素材","answer":["そざい"]},
    {"meaning":"obstruction, check, hindrance, prevention, interdiction","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"阻止","answer":["そし"]},
    {"meaning":"litigation, lawsuit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"訴訟","answer":["そしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"breeding, growth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"育ち","answer":["そだち"]},
    {"meaning":"measure, step","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"措置","answer":["そち"]},
    {"meaning":"cold, short, curt, blunt","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素っ気ない","answer":["そっけない"]},
    {"meaning":"frankness, candour, openheartedness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"率直","answer":["そっちょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to provide, to furnish, to equip, to install","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"備え付ける","answer":["そなえつける"]},
    {"meaning":"to be furnished with, to be endowed with, to possess, to be among, to be one of, to be possessed of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"備わる","answer":["そなわる"]},
    {"meaning":"simplicity, artlessness, naivete","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素朴","answer":["そぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dye","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"染まる","answer":["そまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to run counter to, to go against, to disobey, to infringe","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背く","answer":["そむく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dye, to colour","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"染める","answer":["そめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn away, to avert","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"逸らす","answer":["そらす"]},
    {"meaning":"warp, curvature, curve, arch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反り","answer":["そり"]},
    {"meaning":"each,every,either,respectively,severally","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"各々","answer":["おのおの","それぞれ"]},
    {"meaning":"gradually, steadily, quietly, slowly, soon","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徐々","answer":["じょじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"loss","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"損失","answer":["そんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"duration, continuance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存続","answer":["そんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"along","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沿い","answer":["ぞい"]},
    {"meaning":"statue, image, figure, picture, portrait","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"像","answer":["ぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"augment, reinforce, increase","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増強","answer":["ぞうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Minister of Finance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"蔵相","answer":["ぞうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"promoting, increase, advance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増進","answer":["ぞうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"ill will, malice, another intention, secret purpose, ulterior motive, fickleness, double-mindedness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他意","answer":["たい"]},
    {"meaning":"interaction, correspondence, coping with, dealing with","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"対応","answer":["たいおう"]},
    {"meaning":"degeneration, retrogression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退化","answer":["たいか"]},
    {"meaning":"physique, constitution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体格","answer":["たいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"in general, mainly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大概","answer":["たいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"dropping out of school","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退学","answer":["たいがく"]},
    {"meaning":"great cost","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大金","answer":["たいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment, reception","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"待遇","answer":["たいぐう"]},
    {"meaning":"confrontation, showdown","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対決","answer":["たいけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"personal experience","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"体験","answer":["たいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"opposition, antagonism","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"対抗","answer":["たいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"for, in regard to, per","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対して","answer":["たいして"]},
    {"meaning":"general public","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大衆","answer":["たいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"deal with, cope","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対処","answer":["たいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"retirement (from office)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退職","answer":["たいしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"extermination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退治","answer":["たいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"attitude, conditions, preparations","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"態勢","answer":["たいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"talk, dialogue, conversation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対談","answer":["たいだん"]},
    {"meaning":"equivalent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対等","answer":["たいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"non-payment, default","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滞納","answer":["たいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"contrast, comparison","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"対比","answer":["たいひ"]},
    {"meaning":"most (e.g. most part), greater, fairly, a good deal, much","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大部","answer":["たいぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"(geometrical) opposite side","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"対辺","answer":["たいへん"]},
    {"meaning":"expectant waiting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待望","answer":["たいぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"negligence, procrastination, carelessness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怠慢","answer":["たいまん"]},
    {"meaning":"interview, meeting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対面","answer":["たいめん"]},
    {"meaning":"confrontation, opposition, antagonism","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対立","answer":["たいりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"physical strength","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"体力","answer":["たいりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"interactive, interaction, conversation, dialogue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対話","answer":["たいわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bear, to endure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"耐える","answer":["たえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to die out, to peter out, to become extinct","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶える","answer":["たえる"]},
    {"meaning":"many, a lot, much","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沢山","answer":["たくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"skill, cleverness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"巧み","answer":["たくみ"]},
    {"meaning":"addition","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"足し算","answer":["たしざん"]},
    {"meaning":"majority rule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"多数決","answer":["たすうけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"assistance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助け","answer":["たすけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to participate, to take part","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"携わる","answer":["たずさわる"]},
    {"meaning":"to drift about, to float, to hang in air","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漂う","answer":["ただよう"]},
    {"meaning":"dancing (geisha)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立方","answer":["たちかた"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop by, to drop in for a short visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"立ち寄る","answer":["たちよる"]},
    {"meaning":"skillful, in good health","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"達者","answer":["たっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"achievement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"達成","answer":["たっせい"]},
    {"meaning":"precious, valuable, priceless, noble, exalted, sacred","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"尊い","answer":["たっとい"]},
    {"meaning":"precious, valuable, priceless, noble, exalted, sacred","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貴い","answer":["たっとい"]},
    {"meaning":"to value, to prize, to esteem","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貴ぶ","answer":["たっとぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to sever, to cut off, to suppress, to abstain (from)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶つ","answer":["たつ"]},
    {"meaning":"shield, buckler, escutcheon, pretext","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盾","answer":["たて"]},
    {"meaning":"face, official stance, public position or attitude (as opposed to private thoughts)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"建前","answer":["たてまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to offer, to present, to revere, to do respectfully","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奉る","answer":["たてまつる"]},
    {"meaning":"example, even if, if, though, although","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例え","answer":["たとえ"]},
    {"meaning":"example, even if, if, though, although","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仮令","answer":["たとえ"]},
    {"meaning":"transitive verb (direct obj)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"他動詞","answer":["たどうし"]},
    {"meaning":"the palm","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"掌","answer":["たなごころ","てのひら"]},
    {"meaning":"to enjoy oneself","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"楽しむ","answer":["たのしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"often, repeatedly, frequently","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"度々","answer":["たびたび"]},
    {"meaning":"another side, different direction, (on) the other hand","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他方","answer":["たほう"]},
    {"meaning":"busy, pressure of work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"多忙","answer":["たぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"to receive, to grant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給う","answer":["たまう"]},
    {"meaning":"intolerable, unbearable, unendurable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"堪らない","answer":["たまらない"]},
    {"meaning":"to grant, to bestow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"賜る","answer":["たまわる"]},
    {"meaning":"instance,example,case","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例","answer":["れい","ためし"]},
    {"meaning":"to keep, to preserve, to hold, to retain, to maintain, to support, to sustain, to last, to endure, to keep we","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保つ","answer":["たもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"easy, simple, light","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"容易い","answer":["たやすい"]},
    {"meaning":"diversity, variety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"多様","answer":["たよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to hang, to droop, to drop, to lower, to pull down, to dangle, to sag, to drip, to ooze, to trickle, to leave","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"垂れる","answer":["たれる"]},
    {"meaning":"roll of cloth (c. 10 yds.), .245 acres, 300 tsubo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反","answer":["はん"]},
    {"meaning":"single, simple, sole, individual, unitory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単一","answer":["たんいつ"]},
    {"meaning":"tanka, 31-syllable Japanese poem","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短歌","answer":["たんか"]},
    {"meaning":"stretcher, litter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"担架","answer":["たんか"]},
    {"meaning":"quick temper","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短気","answer":["たんき"]},
    {"meaning":"exploration, expedition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"探検","answer":["たんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"shortening, abbreviation, reduction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"短縮","answer":["たんしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"carbon (C)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"炭素","answer":["たんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"junior college","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短大","answer":["たんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"monotony, monotone, dullness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単調","answer":["たんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sole, independence, single, solo (flight)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"単独","answer":["たんどく"]},
    {"meaning":"short wave","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"短波","answer":["たんぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"ordinal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"第","answer":["だい"]},
    {"meaning":"first, foremost, # 1","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"第一","answer":["だいいち"]},
    {"meaning":"bold, daring, audacious","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大胆","answer":["だいたん"]},
    {"meaning":"feces, excrement, shit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大便","answer":["だいべん"]},
    {"meaning":"pay by proxy, act for another, speak for another","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"代弁","answer":["だいべん"]},
    {"meaning":"libretto, scenario","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"台本","answer":["だいほん"]},
    {"meaning":"substitution","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代用","answer":["だいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"break in the deadlock","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打開","answer":["だかい"]},
    {"meaning":"compromise, giving in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妥協","answer":["だきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妥結","answer":["だけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. blow, shock, strike, damage, 2. batting (baseball)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"打撃","answer":["だげき"]},
    {"meaning":"poor work, rubbish","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"駄作","answer":["ださく"]},
    {"meaning":"escape","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脱出","answer":["だっしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape from, to get out","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脱する","answer":["だっする"]},
    {"meaning":"secession","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脱退","answer":["だったい"]},
    {"meaning":"sluggish, feel heavy, languid, dull","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怠い","answer":["だるい"]},
    {"meaning":"1. platform, podium, rostrum, 2. (arch) mandala","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"壇","answer":["だん"]},
    {"meaning":"unity, union, combination","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"団結","answer":["だんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"declaration, affirmation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断言","answer":["だんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"firmly, absolutely, definitely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断然","answer":["だんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"gradually, by degrees","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"段々","answer":["だんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"master (of house), husband (informal)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"旦那","answer":["だんな"]},
    {"meaning":"cross section","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断面","answer":["だんめん"]},
    {"meaning":"elasticity, flexibility","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弾力","answer":["だんりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"public order","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治安","answer":["ちあん"]},
    {"meaning":"to approach, to get near, to get acquainted with, to get closer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近付く","answer":["ちかづく"]},
    {"meaning":"to change","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違える","answer":["ちがえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pledge, to promise, to swear","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"契る","answer":["ちぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"animal husbandry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"畜産","answer":["ちくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"beast, brute, damn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"畜生","answer":["ちくしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"accumulation, accumulate, store","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蓄積","answer":["ちくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"intelligence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知性","answer":["ちせい"]},
    {"meaning":"milk, breast, loop","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乳","answer":["ちち"]},
    {"meaning":"father and mother,parents","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"父母","answer":["ふぼ","ちちはは"]},
    {"meaning":"to be shortened, to be contracted, to shrink","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縮まる","answer":["ちぢまる"]},
    {"meaning":"suffocation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"窒息","answer":["ちっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"order, regularity, system, method","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"秩序","answer":["ちつじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"embarkation, launch","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着手","answer":["ちゃくしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"colouring, coloring","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着色","answer":["ちゃくしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"sit down, seat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"着席","answer":["ちゃくせき"]},
    {"meaning":"attention","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着目","answer":["ちゃくもく"]},
    {"meaning":"landing, alighting, touch down","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着陸","answer":["ちゃくりく"]},
    {"meaning":"start of (construction) work","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"着工","answer":["ちゃっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"living room (Japanese style)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"茶の間","answer":["ちゃのま"]},
    {"meaning":"tea ceremony","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"茶の湯","answer":["ちゃのゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"daytime,during the day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"昼間","answer":["ひるま","ちゅうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"somersault, looping-the-loop","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宙返り","answer":["ちゅうがえり"]},
    {"meaning":"relay, hook-up","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"中継","answer":["ちゅうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"advice, warning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"忠告","answer":["ちゅうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"middle finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中指","answer":["なかゆび","ちゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"slander, libel, defamation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"中傷","answer":["ちゅうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"fidelity, faithfulness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"忠実","answer":["ちゅうじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"centre, pivot, mainstay, nucleus, backbone, central figure, pillar, key man","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"中枢","answer":["ちゅうすう"]},
    {"meaning":"lottery, raffle, drawing (of lots)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抽選","answer":["ちゅうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"interruption, suspension, break","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中断","answer":["ちゅうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"poisoning","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"中毒","answer":["ちゅうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"go-between, matchmaker","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仲人","answer":["ちゅうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"lunch, midday meal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"昼飯","answer":["ちゅうはん"]},
    {"meaning":"neutrality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中立","answer":["ちゅうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"neutralize, counteract","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"中和","answer":["ちゅうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"guts, bowels, intestines","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"腸","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"butterfly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蝶","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"super-, ultra-, hyper-","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"超","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"government office","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"庁","answer":["ちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"signature, sign, sealing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"調印","answer":["ちょういん"]},
    {"meaning":"the sense of hearing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"聴覚","answer":["ちょうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"chief, (government) secretary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長官","answer":["ちょうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"lecture attendance, auditing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"聴講","answer":["ちょうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"collection, levy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徴収","answer":["ちょうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"stethoscope","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"聴診器","answer":["ちょうしんき"]},
    {"meaning":"challenge, defiance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"挑戦","answer":["ちょうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"very long, great length","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"長大","answer":["ちょうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"arbitration, conciliation, mediation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"調停","answer":["ちょうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"long (e.g. novel film)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"長編","answer":["ちょうへん"]},
    {"meaning":"district of a town, city block (of irregular size)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"丁目","answer":["ちょうめ"]},
    {"meaning":"cooking","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調理","answer":["ちょうり"]},
    {"meaning":"harmony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調和","answer":["ちょうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"confrontation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直面","answer":["ちょくめん"]},
    {"meaning":"literary work, book","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著書","answer":["ちょしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"savings","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貯蓄","answer":["ちょちく"]},
    {"meaning":"intuition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直感","answer":["ちょっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"well-known, noted, celebrated","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"著名","answer":["ちょめい"]},
    {"meaning":"medical treatment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"治療","answer":["ちりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"wages","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"賃金","answer":["ちんぎん"]},
    {"meaning":"precipitation, settlement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沈殿","answer":["ちんでん"]},
    {"meaning":"sinking, foundering","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沈没","answer":["ちんぼつ"]},
    {"meaning":"silence, reticence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沈黙","answer":["ちんもく"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition, display, show","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"陳列","answer":["ちんれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"gaining on, carrying out, solving (crime)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"追及","answer":["ついきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"pursuit","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"追跡","answer":["ついせき"]},
    {"meaning":"next, secondly, subsequently","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次いで","answer":["ついで"]},
    {"meaning":"exile, banishment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追放","answer":["ついほう"]},
    {"meaning":"to spend, to devote, to waste","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"費やす","answer":["ついやす"]},
    {"meaning":"falling, crashing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"墜落","answer":["ついらく"]},
    {"meaning":"connoisseur, counter for letters","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通","answer":["つう"]},
    {"meaning":"feeling keenly, fully realizing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛感","answer":["つうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"common, general, usually","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通常","answer":["つうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"keen, acute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛切","answer":["つうせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"mission, simple task, doing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遣い","answer":["つかい"]},
    {"meaning":"use","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"使い道","answer":["つかいみち"]},
    {"meaning":"to serve, to work for","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"仕える","answer":["つかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to rule, to govern, to administer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"司る","answer":["つかさどる"]},
    {"meaning":"attached to, impression, sociality, appearance, furnished with, under, to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付き","answer":["つき"]},
    {"meaning":"to associate with, to keep company with, to get on with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付き合う","answer":["つきあう"]},
    {"meaning":"every month, common","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"月並み","answer":["つきなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be used up, to be run out, to be exhausted, to be consumed, to come to an end","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尽きる","answer":["つきる"]},
    {"meaning":"a joint, joining point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"継ぎ目","answer":["つぎめ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. to breathe, 2. to tell (lies), 3. to vomit, to disgorge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"吐く","answer":["つく","はく"]},
    {"meaning":"to exhaust, to run out, to serve (a person), to befriend","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尽くす","answer":["つくす"]},
    {"meaning":"make-up, sliced raw fish","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作り","answer":["つくり"]},
    {"meaning":"make up, structure, physique","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"造り","answer":["つくり"]},
    {"meaning":"to make,to create","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"造る","answer":["つくる"]},
    {"meaning":"to mend, to repair, to fix, to patch up, to darn, to tidy up, to adjust, to trim","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"繕う","answer":["つくろう"]},
    {"meaning":"to join, to piece together, to set (bones), to graft (trees)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"接ぐ","answer":["つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to succeed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"継ぐ","answer":["つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to add one thing to another","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付け加える","answer":["つけくわえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to inform","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"告げる","answer":["つげる"]},
    {"meaning":"on the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"途中","answer":["とちゅう","つちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to support, to become stiff, to become taut, to thrust (ones opponent), to stick to (ones opinion), to in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"突っ張る","answer":["つっぱる"]},
    {"meaning":"pipe, tube","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"筒","answer":["つつ"]},
    {"meaning":"gun","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"銃","answer":["つつ","じゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to thrust,to strike,(2) to poke","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突く","answer":["つく","つつく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be careful, to be chaste or discreet, to abstain or refrain","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"慎む","answer":["つつしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"verbal message, rumor, word","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝言","answer":["つてごと"]},
    {"meaning":"to be fit for, to be equal to, to function properly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤まる","answer":["つとまる"]},
    {"meaning":"place of work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤め先","answer":["つとめさき"]},
    {"meaning":"make an effort!, work hard!","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"努めて","answer":["つとめて"]},
    {"meaning":"tsunami, tidal wave","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"津波","answer":["つなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to invite, to solicit help participation etc","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"募る","answer":["つのる"]},
    {"meaning":"to pinch, to hold, to pick up","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"摘む","answer":["つまむ"]},
    {"meaning":"insignificant, boring, trifling","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"詰らない","answer":["つまらない"]},
    {"meaning":"intention, plan","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"積もり","answer":["つもり"]},
    {"meaning":"to get strong, to gain strength","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強まる","answer":["つよまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to strengthen, to emphasize","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強める","answer":["つよめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to extend, to stretch out, to stand in a row","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連なる","answer":["つらなる"]},
    {"meaning":"to go through","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貫く","answer":["つらぬく"]},
    {"meaning":"to link, to join, to put together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連ねる","answer":["つらねる"]},
    {"meaning":"fishing, angling","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"釣り","answer":["つり"]},
    {"meaning":"hanging bell","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"釣鐘","answer":["つりがね"]},
    {"meaning":"allowance, compensation, treatment, medical care","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手当て","answer":["てあて"]},
    {"meaning":"Body","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"体","answer":["からだ","てい"]},
    {"meaning":"offer, tender, program sponsoring, furnishing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"提供","answer":["ていきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"definition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"定義","answer":["ていぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"cooperation, tie-up, joint business, link-up","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"提携","answer":["ていけい"]},
    {"meaning":"decency, style, form, appearance, show, get-up, format","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"体裁","answer":["ていさい"]},
    {"meaning":"set meal, special (of the day)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定食","answer":["ていしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"presentation, exhibit, suggest, citation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"提示","answer":["ていじ"]},
    {"meaning":"correction, revision","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"訂正","answer":["ていせい"]},
    {"meaning":"stagnation, tie-up, congestion, retention, accumulation, falling into arrears","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"停滞","answer":["ていたい"]},
    {"meaning":"mansion, residence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"邸宅","answer":["ていたく"]},
    {"meaning":"retirement age","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定年","answer":["ていねん"]},
    {"meaning":"bank, weir","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"堤防","answer":["ていぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"too late, belated treatment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手遅れ","answer":["ておくれ"]},
    {"meaning":"number of moves, trouble","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手数","answer":["てかず"]},
    {"meaning":"contact, trail, scent, on hand, hand hold, clue, key","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手掛かり","answer":["てがかり"]},
    {"meaning":"to handle, to manage, to work with, to rear, to look after, to have experience with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手掛ける","answer":["てがける"]},
    {"meaning":"easy, simple, informal, offhand, cheap","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"手軽","answer":["てがる"]},
    {"meaning":"adaptation, accommodation, conformity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"適応","answer":["てきおう"]},
    {"meaning":"suitability","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"適宜","answer":["てきぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"aptitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適性","answer":["てきせい"]},
    {"meaning":"performance, skill, tact","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手際","answer":["てぎわ"]},
    {"meaning":"process, procedure, protocol","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手順","answer":["てじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"handcuffs, manacles","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"手錠","answer":["てじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"near, handy, familiar","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手近","answer":["てぢか"]},
    {"meaning":"iron and steel","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鉄鋼","answer":["てっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to sink in, to penetrate, to devote oneself, to believe in, to go through, to do intently and exclusively","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徹する","answer":["てっする"]},
    {"meaning":"iron scraps","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鉄片","answer":["てっぺん"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement, search (by police)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手配","answer":["てはい"]},
    {"meaning":"guidance, guide, introduction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手引き","answer":["てびき"]},
    {"meaning":"model, pattern","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手本","answer":["てほん"]},
    {"meaning":"preparations, arrangements","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手回し","answer":["てまわし"]},
    {"meaning":"on hand, at hand, at home","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手元","answer":["てもと"]},
    {"meaning":"to reflect, to throw back light","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"照り返す","answer":["てりかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"ignition, lighting, set fire to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点火","answer":["てんか"]},
    {"meaning":"revolution, rotation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"転回","answer":["てんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"convert, divert","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"転換","answer":["てんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"moving, changing residence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"転居","answer":["てんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"transfer, transmission","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"転勤","answer":["てんきん"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection, examination, checking","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"点検","answer":["てんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"change schools","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転校","answer":["てんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"paradise, heaven, Kingdom of Heaven","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"天国","answer":["てんごく"]},
    {"meaning":"genius, prodigy, natural gift","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天才","answer":["てんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"natural calamity, disaster","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"天災","answer":["てんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition, display","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"展示","answer":["てんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"ceiling, ceiling price","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"天井","answer":["てんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn, to shift, to alter, to distract","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転じる","answer":["てんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"dotted line, perforated line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"点線","answer":["てんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"heavenly body","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"天体","answer":["てんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"rolling about, moving from place to place, being passed around repeatedly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転転","answer":["てんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"change of post","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"転任","answer":["てんにん"]},
    {"meaning":"view, outlook, prospect","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"展望","answer":["てんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"fall, degradation, slump","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"転落","answer":["てんらく"]},
    {"meaning":"exit and entrance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出入り口","answer":["でいりぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"able man, tumour, growth, boil, ulcer, abcess, rash, pimple","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出来物","answer":["できもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to be out of, to have no more at hand","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出切る","answer":["できる"]},
    {"meaning":"to happen to meet, to come across","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出くわす","answer":["でくわす"]},
    {"meaning":"irresponsible utterance, nonsense, nonsensical, random, haphazard, unsystematic","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出鱈目","answer":["でたらめ"]},
    {"meaning":"adjustment, touch up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出直し","answer":["でなおし"]},
    {"meaning":"country, rural districts","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"田園","answer":["でんえん"]},
    {"meaning":"source of electricity, power (button on TV etc.)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"電源","answer":["でんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"tradition, legend, folklore","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝説","answer":["でんせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"electric line","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"電線","answer":["でんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"transmission (e.g. news), communication, delivery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝達","answer":["でんたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"ancestral, hereditary, imported, transmitted, handed down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝来","answer":["でんらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to enquire, to seek information","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"問い合わせる","answer":["といあわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"wholesale store","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"問屋","answer":["といや"]},
    {"meaning":"to ask, to question, to charge (i.e. with a crime), to accuse, without regard to (neg)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"問う","answer":["とう"]},
    {"meaning":"place, section, building","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"棟","answer":["とう"]},
    {"meaning":"et cetera,etc.,and the like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"等","answer":["など","とう"]},
    {"meaning":"pottery, ceramics","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"陶器","answer":["とうき"]},
    {"meaning":"grade, class","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"等級","answer":["とうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"debate, discussion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"討議","answer":["とうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"attendance (at school)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"登校","answer":["とうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"integration, unification, synthesis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"統合","answer":["とうごう"]},
    {"meaning":"(corporate) bankruptcy, insolvency","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"倒産","answer":["とうさん"]},
    {"meaning":"investment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投資","answer":["とうし"]},
    {"meaning":"rule, reign, government, governing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"統治","answer":["とうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"regulation, control","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"統制","answer":["とうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"being elected, winning the prize","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当選","answer":["とうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"flight, desertion, escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃走","answer":["とうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"command, lead, generalship, leadership","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"統率","answer":["とうそつ"]},
    {"meaning":"reaching, attaining, arrival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"到達","answer":["とうたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(cannot) possibly","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"到底","answer":["とうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"clashing of swords, felling of trees, ringing of an ax","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"丁々","answer":["とうとう","ちょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"throw, investment, making (an electrical circuit)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投入","answer":["とうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"the one concerned, the said person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当人","answer":["とうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃亡","answer":["とうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"hibernation, winter sleep","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冬眠","answer":["とうみん"]},
    {"meaning":"registration, register, entry, record","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"登録","answer":["とうろく"]},
    {"meaning":"debate, discussion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"討論","answer":["とうろん"]},
    {"meaning":"to go far off","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠ざかる","answer":["とおざかる"]},
    {"meaning":"detour, roundabout way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠回り","answer":["とおまわり"]},
    {"meaning":"to happen to pass by","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通りかかる","answer":["とおりかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"sometimes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時折","answer":["ときおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to pause, to be interrupted","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"跡切れる","answer":["とぎれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to explain, to advocate, to preach, to persuade","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"説く","answer":["とく"]},
    {"meaning":"special skill","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"特技","answer":["とくぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"specialty, special product","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"特産","answer":["とくさん"]},
    {"meaning":"feature (e.g. newspaper), special edition, report","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"特集","answer":["とくしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"score, points made, marks obtained, runs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"得点","answer":["とくてん"]},
    {"meaning":"send specially, special envoy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"特派","answer":["とくは"]},
    {"meaning":"characteristic (of), peculiar (to)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"特有","answer":["とくゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"to sharpen, to grind, to scour, to hone, to polish, to wash (rice)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"研ぐ","answer":["とぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"thorn, splinter, spine, biting words","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"刺","answer":["とげ"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish, to achieve, to carry out","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遂げる","answer":["とげる"]},
    {"meaning":"floor","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"床","answer":["ゆか","とこ"]},
    {"meaning":"by the way, even if, no matter what","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所で","answer":["ところで"]},
    {"meaning":"age, marriageable age, age of puberty, adolescence, for some years","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年頃","answer":["としごろ"]},
    {"meaning":"old people, the aged","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"年寄り","answer":["としより"]},
    {"meaning":"closing up, fastening the doors","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"戸締り","answer":["とじまり"]},
    {"meaning":"en route, half way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"途上","answer":["とじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop, to cease, to come to an end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"途絶える","answer":["とだえる"]},
    {"meaning":"special permission, patent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"特許","answer":["とっきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"privilege, special right","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"特権","answer":["とっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"handle, grip, knob","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取っ手","answer":["とって"]},
    {"meaning":"breaking through, breakthrough, penetration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突破","answer":["とっぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"suddenly, all of a sudden","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"突如","answer":["とつじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to put in order, to get ready, to arrange, to adjust","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整える","answer":["ととのえる"]},
    {"meaning":"report, notification, registration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"届け","answer":["とどけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stagnate, to be delayed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滞る","answer":["とどこおる"]},
    {"meaning":"to come to a halt","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"止まる","answer":["とまる","とどまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to fasten,to turn off,to detain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留める","answer":["とめる","とどめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to stop something","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"止める","answer":["とめる","やめる","とどめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to recite, to chant, to call upon","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"唱える","answer":["となえる"]},
    {"meaning":"feudal lord","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"殿様","answer":["とのさま"]},
    {"meaning":"curtain, bunting, act (in play)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幕","answer":["とばり","まく"]},
    {"meaning":"curtain","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"帳","answer":["とばり"]},
    {"meaning":"door, opening","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扉","answer":["とびら"]},
    {"meaning":"walking, going on foot","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"徒歩","answer":["とほ"]},
    {"meaning":"meagre, scarce, limited, destitute, hard up, scanty, poor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"乏しい","answer":["とぼしい"]},
    {"meaning":"wealth, fortune","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"富","answer":["とみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be rich, to become rich","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"富む","answer":["とむ"]},
    {"meaning":"working together, (husband and wife) earning a living together","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"共稼ぎ","answer":["ともかせぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"light","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灯","answer":["ひ","ともしび"]},
    {"meaning":"to accompany, to bring with, to be accompanied by, to be involved in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"伴う","answer":["ともなう"]},
    {"meaning":"dual income","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共働き","answer":["ともばたらき"]},
    {"meaning":"to seize, to grasp, to capture, to arrest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕らえる","answer":["とらえる"]},
    {"meaning":"at once, first of all, for the time being","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取りあえず","answer":["とりあえず"]},
    {"meaning":"treatment, service, handling, management","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"取り扱い","answer":["とりあつかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to treat, to handle, to deal in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"取り扱う","answer":["とりあつかう"]},
    {"meaning":"torii (Shinto shrine archway)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"鳥居","answer":["とりい"]},
    {"meaning":"swap, exchange","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"取り替え","answer":["とりかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to tackle, to wrestle with, to engage in a bout, to come to grips with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り組む","answer":["とりくむ"]},
    {"meaning":"control, management, supervision","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"取り締まり","answer":["とりしまり"]},
    {"meaning":"to manage, to control, to supervise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"取り締まる","answer":["とりしまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to investigate, to examine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り調べる","answer":["とりしらべる"]},
    {"meaning":"to collect, to extort, to appoint, to promote","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り立てる","answer":["とりたてる"]},
    {"meaning":"to act as an agent for, to announce (someone), to convey (a message)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り次ぐ","answer":["とりつぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove, to take away, to set apart","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り除く","answer":["とりのぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"transactions, dealings, business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り引き","answer":["とりひき"]},
    {"meaning":"to surround, to circle, to enclose","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"取り巻く","answer":["とりまく"]},
    {"meaning":"to mix, to put together","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"取り混ぜる","answer":["とりまぜる"]},
    {"meaning":"to take back, to regain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り戻す","answer":["とりもどす"]},
    {"meaning":"to order, to send away for","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り寄せる","answer":["とりよせる"]},
    {"meaning":"especially, above all","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"副","answer":["とりわけ"]},
    {"meaning":"trunk, body, frame","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"胴","answer":["どう"]},
    {"meaning":"the same, the said, ibid.","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同","answer":["どう"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement, consent, same meaning, same opinion, approval","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同意","answer":["どうい"]},
    {"meaning":"mobilization","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"動員","answer":["どういん"]},
    {"meaning":"agreement, same opinion, same feeling, sympathy, concurrence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同感","answer":["どうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"motive, incentive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"動機","answer":["どうき"]},
    {"meaning":"the same grade, same class","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"同級","answer":["どうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"living together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同居","answer":["どうきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"trend, tendency, movement, attitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"動向","answer":["どうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"fellow, companion, comrade","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"同士","answer":["どうし"]},
    {"meaning":"same mind, comrade, kindred soul","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"同志","answer":["どうし"]},
    {"meaning":"sympathy, compassion, sympathize, pity, feel for","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同情","answer":["どうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"dojo, hall used for martial arts training, mandala","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"道場","answer":["どうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"please, kindly, by all means","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"何卒","answer":["どうぞ","なにとぞ"]},
    {"meaning":"pleased to meet you","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"どうぞ宜しく","answer":["どうぞよろしく"]},
    {"meaning":"sympathy, agree with, alignment, tuning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同調","answer":["どうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"equality, equal, same rights, same rank","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同等","answer":["どうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"magnificent, grand, impressive","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"堂々","answer":["どうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"introduction, bringing in, leading in","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"導入","answer":["どうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"enclosure (e.g. in a letter)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"同封","answer":["どうふう"]},
    {"meaning":"alliance, union, league","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"同盟","answer":["どうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"disturbance, unrest, shaking, trembling, pitching, rolling, oscillation, agitation, excitement, commotion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"動揺","answer":["どうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"power, motive power, dynamic force","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"動力","answer":["どうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"dictatorship, despotism","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独裁","answer":["どくさい"]},
    {"meaning":"reader","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"読者","answer":["どくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"original, peculiar, characteristic","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独自","answer":["どくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"monopoly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独占","answer":["どくせん"]},
    {"meaning":"originality","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独創","answer":["どくそう"]},
    {"meaning":"where, what place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"何処","answer":["どこ"]},
    {"meaning":"present,souvenir","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"土産","answer":["みやげ","どさん"]},
    {"meaning":"foundation, base, basis","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"土台","answer":["どだい"]},
    {"meaning":"embankment, bank","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"土手","answer":["どて"]},
    {"meaning":"who?","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"何方","answer":["どなた"]},
    {"meaning":"to shout, to yell","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"怒鳴る","answer":["どなる"]},
    {"meaning":"which, what","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"何の","answer":["どの"]},
    {"meaning":"arena","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"土俵","answer":["どひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"public works","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"土木","answer":["どぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"lapse of memory, forget for a moment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"度忘れ","answer":["どわすれ"]},
    {"meaning":"thickheadedness, stolidity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鈍感","answer":["どんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"cabinet, (government) ministry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"内閣","answer":["ないかく"]},
    {"meaning":"internal organs, intestines, viscera","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"内臓","answer":["ないぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"interior, inside, internal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内部","answer":["ないぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"civil war, insurrection, rebellion, domestic conflict","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"内乱","answer":["ないらん"]},
    {"meaning":"inland","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内陸","answer":["ないりく"]},
    {"meaning":"rice seedling","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"苗","answer":["なえ"]},
    {"meaning":"furthermore, still, yet, more, still more, greater, further, less","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尚","answer":["なお"]},
    {"meaning":"sink","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流し","answer":["ながし"]},
    {"meaning":"long, drawn-out, very long","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"長々","answer":["ながなが"]},
    {"meaning":"to strike, to hit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"殴る","answer":["なぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"to sigh, to lament, to grieve","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嘆く","answer":["なげく"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw down, to abandon, to sacrifice, to throw out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投げ出す","answer":["なげだす"]},
    {"meaning":"mild, calm, gentle, quiet, harmonious","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和やか","answer":["なごやか"]},
    {"meaning":"remains, traces, memory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"名残","answer":["なごり"]},
    {"meaning":"sympathy, compassion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情け","answer":["なさけ"]},
    {"meaning":"tender-hearted, compassionate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情け深い","answer":["なさけぶかい"]},
    {"meaning":"famous, celebrated, well-known","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"名高い","answer":["なだかい"]},
    {"meaning":"avalanche","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"雪崩","answer":["なだれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to become emotionally attached","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"懐く","answer":["なつく"]},
    {"meaning":"to name (someone)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"名付ける","answer":["なづける"]},
    {"meaning":"casual, unconcerned","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"何気ない","answer":["なにげない"]},
    {"meaning":"at any rate, anyhow, anyway, in any case","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"何しろ","answer":["なにしろ"]},
    {"meaning":"name plate, name tag","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"名札","answer":["なふだ"]},
    {"meaning":"smelling of fish or blood, fish or meat","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"生臭い","answer":["なまぐさい"]},
    {"meaning":"lukewarm, halfhearted","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"生温い","answer":["なまぬるい"]},
    {"meaning":"lead (the metal)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鉛","answer":["なまり"]},
    {"meaning":"to become less capable, to grow dull, to become blunt, to weaken","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"鈍る","answer":["なまる","にぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"average, medium, common, ordinary","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並み","answer":["なみ"]},
    {"meaning":"smoothness, glassiness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滑らか","answer":["なめらか"]},
    {"meaning":"seductive, melancholy, languid","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"悩ましい","answer":["なやましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to afflict, to torment, to harass, to molest","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"悩ます","answer":["なやます"]},
    {"meaning":"trouble(s), worry, distress, anguish, agony, problem","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"悩み","answer":["なやみ"]},
    {"meaning":"equilibrium,balance,average,mean","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"平均","answer":["へいきん","ならし"]},
    {"meaning":"to accustom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣らす","answer":["ならす"]},
    {"meaning":"and","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並びに","answer":["ならびに"]},
    {"meaning":"to conclude, to consist of, to be practical (logical feasible viable), to hold true","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成り立つ","answer":["なりたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"as much as possible","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成るべく","answer":["なるべく"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣れ","answer":["なれ"]},
    {"meaning":"south","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"南","answer":["みなみ","なん"]},
    {"meaning":"load, baggage, cargo","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荷","answer":["に"]},
    {"meaning":"to resemble closely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"似通う","answer":["にかよう"]},
    {"meaning":"bad","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪い","answer":["わるい","にくい"]},
    {"meaning":"hatred","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"憎しみ","answer":["にくしみ"]},
    {"meaning":"blood relationship, blood relative","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"肉親","answer":["にくしん"]},
    {"meaning":"the body, the flesh","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"肉体","answer":["にくたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to run away, to escape from","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃げ出す","answer":["にげだす"]},
    {"meaning":"westering sun","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"西日","answer":["にしび"]},
    {"meaning":"day and night, always","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"日夜","answer":["にちや"]},
    {"meaning":"daily allowance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日当","answer":["にっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"packing, baling, crating","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"荷造り","answer":["にづくり"]},
    {"meaning":"to carry on shoulder, to bear (burden), to shoulder (gun)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"担う","answer":["になう"]},
    {"meaning":"in spite of, nevertheless","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"にも拘らず","answer":["にもかかわらず"]},
    {"meaning":"obtaining, coming to hand","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入手","answer":["にゅうしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"winning a prize or place (in a contest)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"入賞","answer":["にゅうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"bathe, bathing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"入浴","answer":["にゅうよく"]},
    {"meaning":"urine","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尿","answer":["にょう"]},
    {"meaning":"recognition, cognizance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"認識","answer":["にんしき"]},
    {"meaning":"conception, pregnancy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妊娠","answer":["にんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"humanity, empathy, kindness, sympathy, human nature, common sense, customs and manners","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人情","answer":["にんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"duty, function, office, mission, task","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"任務","answer":["にんむ"]},
    {"meaning":"appointment, nomination, ordination, commission, designation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"任命","answer":["にんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"to omit, to leave out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抜かす","answer":["ぬかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to slip out, to sneak away, to excel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抜け出す","answer":["ぬけだす"]},
    {"meaning":"stealing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"盗み","answer":["ぬすみ"]},
    {"meaning":"swamp, bog, pond, lake","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沼","answer":["ぬま"]},
    {"meaning":"value, worth, price, dignity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値打ち","answer":["ねうち"]},
    {"meaning":"to put to bed, to lay down, to ferment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寝かせる","answer":["ねかせる"]},
    {"meaning":"screwdriver","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"ねじ回し","answer":["ねじまわし"]},
    {"meaning":"boiling water","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"熱湯","answer":["ねっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"zeal, enthusiasm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱意","answer":["ねつい"]},
    {"meaning":"temperature","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"熱量","answer":["ねつりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"stickyness, viscosity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"粘り","answer":["ねばり"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sticky, to be adhesive, to persevere, to persist, to stick to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"粘る","answer":["ねばる"]},
    {"meaning":"price reduction, discount","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値引き","answer":["ねびき"]},
    {"meaning":"making necessary arrangements","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"根回し","answer":["ねまわし"]},
    {"meaning":"sleepy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"眠たい","answer":["ねむたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to knead, to work over, to polish up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"練る","answer":["ねる"]},
    {"meaning":"sense, idea, thought, feeling, desire, concern, attention, care","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"念","answer":["ねん"]},
    {"meaning":"yearbook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"年鑑","answer":["ねんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"name of an era, year number","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"年号","answer":["ねんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"burning, combustion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"燃焼","answer":["ねんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"pupil in .... year, student in .... year","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年生","answer":["ねんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"seniority","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年長","answer":["ねんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"fuel","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"燃料","answer":["ねんりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"annual tree ring","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"年輪","answer":["ねんりん"]},
    {"meaning":"brain, memory","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"脳","answer":["のう"]},
    {"meaning":"farming, agriculture","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農耕","answer":["のうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"farm (agriculture)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農場","answer":["のうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"agricultural land","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"農地","answer":["のうち"]},
    {"meaning":"payment, supply","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"納入","answer":["のうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to let loose, to set free, to let escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃す","answer":["のがす"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃れる","answer":["のがれる"]},
    {"meaning":"row of houses","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"軒並み","answer":["のきなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"desirable, hoped for","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"望ましい","answer":["のぞましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to look out on, to face, to deal with, to attend (function)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"臨む","answer":["のぞむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to capture, to occupy, to usurp","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗っ取る","answer":["のっとる"]},
    {"meaning":"futures, credit (buying), stretching, total","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"延べ","answer":["のべ"]},
    {"meaning":"to gulp down, to swallow deeply, to understand, to take in, to catch on to, to learn, to digest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飲み込む","answer":["のみこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(n) transfer (trains, buses, etc.)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乗り換え","answer":["のりかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to board, to embark on, to get into (a car), to ship (passengers), to man (a ship), to help (someone) int","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗り込む","answer":["のりこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"edge (of a sword)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刃","answer":["は"]},
    {"meaning":"clique, faction, school","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"派","answer":["は"]},
    {"meaning":"grasp, catch, understanding","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"把握","answer":["はあく"]},
    {"meaning":"lung","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"肺","answer":["はい"]},
    {"meaning":"annullment, disposal, abandon, scrap, discarding, repeal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"廃棄","answer":["はいき"]},
    {"meaning":"distribution (eg. films rice)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配給","answer":["はいきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"spouse, wife, husband","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配偶者","answer":["はいぐうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"Dear (so and so)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拝啓","answer":["はいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"background, scenery, setting, circumstance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背景","answer":["はいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"back, rear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背後","answer":["はいご"]},
    {"meaning":"ashtray","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"灰皿","answer":["はいざら","はいさら"]},
    {"meaning":"abolition, repeal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"廃止","answer":["はいし"]},
    {"meaning":"borrowing","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"拝借","answer":["はいしゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"exclusion, removal, rejection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"排除","answer":["はいじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"drainage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"排水","answer":["はいすい"]},
    {"meaning":"defeat, losing a war","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"敗戦","answer":["はいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement (of resources), disposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配置","answer":["はいち"]},
    {"meaning":"distribution","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"配布","answer":["はいふ"]},
    {"meaning":"consideration, concern, forethought","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"配慮","answer":["はいりょ"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement, array (programming)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配列","answer":["はいれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine, to look attractive, to look pretty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"映える","answer":["はえる"]},
    {"meaning":"destruction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"破壊","answer":["はかい"]},
    {"meaning":"cemetery, graveyard","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"墓地","answer":["はかち","ぼち"]},
    {"meaning":"fleeting, transient, short-lived, momentary, vain, fickle, miserable, empty, ephemeral","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果ない","answer":["はかない"]},
    {"meaning":"to consult with, to confer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"諮る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to plot, to attempt, to plan, to take in, to deceive, to devise, to design, to refer A to B","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"図る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"revocation, annulment, breaking (e.g. treaty)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"破棄","answer":["はき"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for nights of a stay","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"泊","answer":["はく"]},
    {"meaning":"persecution","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"迫害","answer":["はくがい"]},
    {"meaning":"feebleness, weakness, weak","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"薄弱","answer":["はくじゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"confession","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"白状","answer":["はくじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"dispatch, send","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"派遣","answer":["はけん"]},
    {"meaning":"to encourage, to cheer, to raise (the voice)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"励ます","answer":["はげます"]},
    {"meaning":"to be zealous, to brace oneself, to endeavour, to strive, to make an effort","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"励む","answer":["はげむ"]},
    {"meaning":"pillar, post","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"柱","answer":["はしら"]},
    {"meaning":"bridge building, mediation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"橋渡し","answer":["はしわたし"]},
    {"meaning":"shame, embarrassment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恥","answer":["はじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to flip, to snap","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弾く","answer":["はじく","ひく"]},
    {"meaning":"to feel shy, to be bashful, to blush","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恥じらう","answer":["はじらう"]},
    {"meaning":"to feel ashamed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恥じる","answer":["はじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to spring, to bound, to bounce, to be stimulated, to be encouraged, to get lively, to treat oneself to, to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弾む","answer":["はずむ"]},
    {"meaning":"damage","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"破損","answer":["はそん"]},
    {"meaning":"as was expected, really","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果たして","answer":["はたして"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish, to fulfill, to carry out, to achieve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果たす","answer":["はたす"]},
    {"meaning":"barefoot","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裸足","answer":["はだし"]},
    {"meaning":"excavation, exhumation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"発掘","answer":["はっくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"outbreak, spring forth, occurrence, incidence, origin","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発生","answer":["はっせい"]},
    {"meaning":"starting, inauguration","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発足","answer":["はっそく"]},
    {"meaning":"first, new","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"初","answer":["はつ"]},
    {"meaning":"departure, beginning, counter for gunshots","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発","answer":["はつ"]},
    {"meaning":"(physical) growth, development","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発育","answer":["はついく"]},
    {"meaning":"burgeoning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"発芽","answer":["はつが"]},
    {"meaning":"utterance, speech, proposal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発言","answer":["はつげん"]},
    {"meaning":"attack (disease)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発病","answer":["はつびょう"]},
    {"meaning":"something heard for the first time","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"初耳","answer":["はつみみ"]},
    {"meaning":"the end, the extremity, the limit(s), the result","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果て","answer":["はて"]},
    {"meaning":"to end, to be finished, to be exhausted, to die, to perish","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果てる","answer":["はてる"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion, conference","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話し合い","answer":["はなしあい"]},
    {"meaning":"very, greatly, exceedingly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"甚だ","answer":["はなはだ"]},
    {"meaning":"brilliant, magnificent, spectacular","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"華々しい","answer":["はなばなしい"]},
    {"meaning":"(flower) petal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"花びら","answer":["はなびら"]},
    {"meaning":"gay, showy, brilliant, gorgeous, florid","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"華やか","answer":["はなやか"]},
    {"meaning":"beach, seashore","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"浜","answer":["はま"]},
    {"meaning":"beach, foreshore","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"浜辺","answer":["はまべ"]},
    {"meaning":"dentifrice, toothpaste","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"歯磨","answer":["はみがき"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow, to cultivate, to wear beard","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生やす","answer":["はやす"]},
    {"meaning":"to hasten, to quicken, to expedite, to precipitate, to accelerate","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"早める","answer":["はやめる"]},
    {"meaning":"fashionable,fad,in vogue,prevailing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流行","answer":["りゅうこう","はやり"]},
    {"meaning":"anger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"腹立ち","answer":["はらだち"]},
    {"meaning":"open field, empty lot, plain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原っぱ","answer":["はらっぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"paper patch, paper backing, poster","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"張り紙","answer":["はりがみ"]},
    {"meaning":"far, far-away, distant, remote, far off","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遥か","answer":["はるか"]},
    {"meaning":"explosion, rupture, break off","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"破裂","answer":["はれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"group, party, section (mil)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"班","answer":["はん"]},
    {"meaning":"seal, stamp, monogram signature, judgment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判","answer":["はん","ばん"]},
    {"meaning":"edition","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"版","answer":["はん"]},
    {"meaning":"prospering, prosperity, thriving, flourishing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"繁栄","answer":["はんえい"]},
    {"meaning":"antipathy, revolt, animosity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反感","answer":["はんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"art print","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"版画","answer":["はんが"]},
    {"meaning":"echo, reverberation, repercussion, reaction, influence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反響","answer":["はんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"judicial decision, judgement, sentence, decree","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判決","answer":["はんけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"counterattack, counteroffensive, counterblow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"反撃","answer":["はんげき"]},
    {"meaning":"reflection, reverberation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"反射","answer":["はんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"breed, multiply, increase, propagation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"繁殖","answer":["はんしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"prosperity, flourishing, thriving","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"繁盛","answer":["はんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be inconsistent with, to oppose, to contradict, to transgress, to rebel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反する","answer":["はんする"]},
    {"meaning":"judgement, decision, award, verdict","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判定","answer":["はんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"reaction, response","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"反応","answer":["はんのう"]},
    {"meaning":"remnant, fragment, incomplete set, fraction, odd sum, incompleteness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"半端","answer":["はんぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"repelling, rebound, recover, oppose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反発","answer":["はんぱつ"]},
    {"meaning":"insurrection, mutiny, rebellion, revolt, uprising","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"反乱","answer":["はんらん"]},
    {"meaning":"bacteria, germ(s)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"ばい菌","answer":["ばいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"reparations, indemnity, compensation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"賠償","answer":["ばいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"diameter, magnification","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"倍率","answer":["ばいりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"obscure, vague, equivocal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漠然","answer":["ばくぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"bomb","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"爆弾","answer":["ばくだん"]},
    {"meaning":"blast, explosion, blow up","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"爆破","answer":["ばくは"]},
    {"meaning":"disclosure, exposure, revelation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暴露","answer":["ばくろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to appear in disguise, to take the form of, to change for the worse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"化ける","answer":["ばける"]},
    {"meaning":"(divine) punishment, curse, retribution","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"罰","answer":["ばち","ばつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to disseminate, to scatter, to give money freely","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"散蒔く","answer":["ばらまく"]},
    {"meaning":"ten thousand","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"万","answer":["まん","ばん"]},
    {"meaning":"all people, everybody, 10000 people","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"万人","answer":["ばんじん"]},
    {"meaning":"all-purpose, almighty, omnipotent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"万能","answer":["ばんのう"]},
    {"meaning":"cardinal number suffix","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番目","answer":["ばんめ"]},
    {"meaning":"cost, expense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"費","answer":["ひ"]},
    {"meaning":"waiting room","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"控室","answer":["ひかえしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to draw in, to hold back, to make notes, to be temperate in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"控える","answer":["ひかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"pessimism, disappointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"悲観","answer":["ひかん"]},
    {"meaning":"head, small animal counter, roll of cloth","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"匹","answer":["ひき"]},
    {"meaning":"to withdraw, to leave, to pull out, to retire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き上げる","answer":["ひきあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to lead, to spearhead (a group), to command (troops)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"率いる","answer":["ひきいる"]},
    {"meaning":"to undertake, to take up, to take over, to be responsible for, to guarantee, to contract (disease)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き受ける","answer":["ひきうける"]},
    {"meaning":"to cause","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き起こす","answer":["ひきおこす"]},
    {"meaning":"to pull down, to lower, to reduce, to withdraw","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き下げる","answer":["ひきさげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to seduce, to drag along, to pull, to prolong, to support","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引きずる","answer":["ひきずる"]},
    {"meaning":"to take charge of, to take over, to retire to a private place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き取る","answer":["ひきとる"]},
    {"meaning":"rejection, negation, voting down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"否決","answer":["ひけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"delinquency, misconduct","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"非行","answer":["ひこう"]},
    {"meaning":"normally, habitually","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日頃","answer":["ひごろ"]},
    {"meaning":"long, long-continued, old (story)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"久しい","answer":["ひさしい"]},
    {"meaning":"after a long time","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"久し振り","answer":["ひさしぶり"]},
    {"meaning":"misery","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"悲惨","answer":["ひさん"]},
    {"meaning":"(private) secretary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"秘書","answer":["ひしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"specific gravity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"比重","answer":["ひじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"secret, private, surreptitious","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"密か","answer":["ひそか"]},
    {"meaning":"to soak, to dip, to drench","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"浸す","answer":["ひたす"]},
    {"meaning":"earnestly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一向","answer":["ひたすら"]},
    {"meaning":"left-handedness, sake drinker, left-hander","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"左利き","answer":["ひだりきき"]},
    {"meaning":"1. to hang (something) on (something), to throw on (clothes), 2. to hook, to catch, to trap, to ensnar","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ掛ける","answer":["ひっかける"]},
    {"meaning":"required (subject)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"必修","answer":["ひっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"comparing with, match, rival, equal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"匹敵","answer":["ひってき"]},
    {"meaning":"eighth sign of Chinese zodiac (The Ram 1pm-3pm south-southwest June)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未","answer":["ひつじ"]},
    {"meaning":"inevitable, necessary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必然","answer":["ひつぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"puffy, a breath, a pause, an effort","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一息","answer":["ひといき"]},
    {"meaning":"personality, character, personal appearance, gentility","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"人柄","answer":["ひとがら"]},
    {"meaning":"hostage, prisoner","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人質","answer":["ひとじち"]},
    {"meaning":"a line, earnestly, blindly, straightforwardly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一筋","answer":["ひとすき"]},
    {"meaning":"by itself, automatically, naturally","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一人でに","answer":["ひとりでに"]},
    {"meaning":"cruel, awful, severe, very bad, serious, terrible, heavy, violent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酷い","answer":["ひどい"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed date, appointed day","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日取り","answer":["ひどり"]},
    {"meaning":"sunny place, in the sun","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日向","answer":["ひなた"]},
    {"meaning":"taking refuge, finding shelter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"避難","answer":["ひなん"]},
    {"meaning":"the Japanese flag","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"日の丸","answer":["ひのまる"]},
    {"meaning":"spark","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"火花","answer":["ひばな"]},
    {"meaning":"every day, daily, day after day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日々","answer":["ひび"]},
    {"meaning":"shriek, scream","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"悲鳴","answer":["ひめい"]},
    {"meaning":"encyclopedia","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"百科事典","answer":["ひゃっかじてん"]},
    {"meaning":"encyclopedia","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"百科辞典","answer":["ひゃっかじてん"]},
    {"meaning":"to banter, to make fun of, to jeer at, to cool, to refrigerate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷やかす","answer":["ひやかす"]},
    {"meaning":"sunburn","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"日焼け","answer":["ひやけ"]},
    {"meaning":"label, ballot, ticket, sign","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"票","answer":["ひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"motto, slogan, catchword","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"標語","answer":["ひょうご"]},
    {"meaning":"flat, even, level, simple, plain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平たい","answer":["ひらたい"]},
    {"meaning":"ratio, proportion, percentage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"比率","answer":["ひりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"manure, fertilizer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"肥料","answer":["ひりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"proportion","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"比例","answer":["ひれい"]},
    {"meaning":"fatigue, weariness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疲労","answer":["ひろう"]},
    {"meaning":"poverty, lack","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"貧困","answer":["ひんこん"]},
    {"meaning":"quality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"品質","answer":["ひんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"brand, kind, description","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"品種","answer":["ひんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"poor, meagre, insubstantial","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"貧弱","answer":["ひんじゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"frequency","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"頻繁","answer":["ひんぱん"]},
    {"meaning":"beauty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美","answer":["び"]},
    {"meaning":"smile","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"微笑","answer":["びしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"art, fine arts","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美術","answer":["びじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"depiction, description, portrayal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"描写","answer":["びょうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"minuscule amount, extremely small quantity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"微量","answer":["びりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sensibility, susceptibility, sensitive (to), well attuned to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"敏感","answer":["びんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"poverty, destitute, poor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貧乏","answer":["びんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"sudden, abrupt, unexpected, unforeseen","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不意","answer":["ふい"]},
    {"meaning":"seal","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"封","answer":["ふう"]},
    {"meaning":"blockade, freezing (funds)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"封鎖","answer":["ふうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"custom","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"風習","answer":["ふうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"1. manners, customs, 2. sex service, sex industry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"風俗","answer":["ふうぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"natural features, topography, climate, spiritual features","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"風土","answer":["ふうど"]},
    {"meaning":"to deepen, to heighten, to intensify","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深める","answer":["ふかめる"]},
    {"meaning":"ominous, sinister, bad luck, ill omen, inauspiciousness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"不吉","answer":["ふきつ"]},
    {"meaning":"recession, depression, slump","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"不況","answer":["ふきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"good fortune","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"福","answer":["ふく"]},
    {"meaning":"restoration, restitution, rehabilitation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"復旧","answer":["ふくきゅう","ふっきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"composite, complex","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"複合","answer":["ふくごう"]},
    {"meaning":"welfare, well-being","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"福祉","answer":["ふくし"]},
    {"meaning":"mask, veil, disguise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"覆面","answer":["ふくめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to get cross, to get sulky, to swell (out), to expand, to be inflated, to distend, to bulge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"膨れる","answer":["ふくれる"]},
    {"meaning":"business recession, hard times, depression, gloom, sullenness, cheerlessness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不景気","answer":["ふけいき"]},
    {"meaning":"to age","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"老ける","answer":["ふける"]},
    {"meaning":"edict, ordinance, proclamation","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"布告","answer":["ふこく"]},
    {"meaning":"wealthy person, millionaire","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"富豪","answer":["ふごう"]},
    {"meaning":"debt, liabilities","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"負債","answer":["ふさい"]},
    {"meaning":"absence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不在","answer":["ふざい"]},
    {"meaning":"injury, wound","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"負傷","answer":["ふしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"incomplete understanding, doubt, question, distrust, suspicion, strangeness, infidelity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"不審","answer":["ふしん"]},
    {"meaning":"dullness, depression, slump, stagnation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"不振","answer":["ふしん"]},
    {"meaning":"irregularity, unseasonableness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不順","answer":["ふじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"attached, belonging, affiliated, annexed, associated, subordinate, incidental, dependent, auxiliary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"付属","answer":["ふぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"burden, charge, responsibility","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"負担","answer":["ふたん"]},
    {"meaning":"bad condition, not to work out (ie a deal), disagreement, break-off, disorder, slump, out of form","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不調","answer":["ふちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"revival (e.g. musical), restoration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"復活","answer":["ふっかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"revival, renaissance, reconstruction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"復興","answer":["ふっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"boiling, seething","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"沸騰","answer":["ふっとう"]},
    {"meaning":"Buddha,merciful person,Buddhist image,the dead","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仏","answer":["ほとけ","ふつ"]},
    {"meaning":"suddenly, casually, accidentally, incidentally, unexpectedly, unintentionally","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不図","answer":["ふと"]},
    {"meaning":"injustice, impropriety, unreasonableness, undeservedness, unfair, invalid","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不当","answer":["ふとう"]},
    {"meaning":"real estate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不動産","answer":["ふどうさん"]},
    {"meaning":"(proceeding to) new appointment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"赴任","answer":["ふにん"]},
    {"meaning":"decay, depravity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"腐敗","answer":["ふはい"]},
    {"meaning":"bad reputation, disgrace, unpopularity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"不評","answer":["ふひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"inconvenience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不便","answer":["ふべん","ふびん"]},
    {"meaning":"dissatisfaction, discontent, disapproval, objection, complaint, protest, disagreement","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不服","answer":["ふふく"]},
    {"meaning":"universality, ubiquity, omnipresence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"普遍","answer":["ふへん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be based on, to have origin in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"踏まえる","answer":["ふまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"sentence","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文","answer":["ぶん","ふみ"]},
    {"meaning":"unknown, obscure, indistinct, uncertain, ambiguous, ignorant, lack of wisdom, anonymous, unidentified","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不明","answer":["ふめい"]},
    {"meaning":"support, maintenance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扶養","answer":["ふよう"]},
    {"meaning":"pretence, show, appearance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振り","answer":["ふり"]},
    {"meaning":"outset, starting point, drawing or issuing (draft)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振り出し","answer":["ふりだし"]},
    {"meaning":"badness, delinquent, inferiority, failure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不良","answer":["ふりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"buoyancy, floating power","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"浮力","answer":["ふりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"appendix, supplement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"付録","answer":["ふろく"]},
    {"meaning":"indignation, resentment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"憤慨","answer":["ふんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"losing something","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紛失","answer":["ふんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"spewing, gushing, spouting, eruption, effusion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"噴出","answer":["ふんしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"dispute, trouble, strife","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紛争","answer":["ふんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"hard struggle, strenuous effort","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奮闘","answer":["ふんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"fine powder","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"粉末","answer":["ふんまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"department, part, category, counter for copies of a newspaper or magazine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部","answer":["ぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"subordinate person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部下","answer":["ぶか"]},
    {"meaning":"insult, contempt, slight","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"侮辱","answer":["ぶじょく"]},
    {"meaning":"arms, armament, armed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"武装","answer":["ぶそう"]},
    {"meaning":"goods, materials","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物資","answer":["ぶっし"]},
    {"meaning":"body, object","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物体","answer":["ぶったい"]},
    {"meaning":"public discussion (criticism)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物議","answer":["ぶつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to knock, to run into, to nail on, to strike hard, to hit and attack","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打付ける","answer":["ぶつける"]},
    {"meaning":"Buddhist image (statue)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"仏像","answer":["ぶつぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"class, group, category, department, field, branch","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"部門","answer":["ぶもん"]},
    {"meaning":"armed might, military power, the sword, force","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"武力","answer":["ぶりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"cultural assets, cultural property","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"文化財","answer":["ぶんかざい"]},
    {"meaning":"written language, literary language","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文語","answer":["ぶんご"]},
    {"meaning":"document, writing, letter, note, records, archives","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文書","answer":["ぶんしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"arms, weapons, ordinance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"兵器","answer":["へいき"]},
    {"meaning":"shut mouth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉口","answer":["へいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"(going) side by side, concurrent, abreast, at the same time, occurring together, parallel, parallelism","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平行","answer":["へいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"closing, closure, shutdown, lockout, unsociable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"閉鎖","answer":["へいさ"]},
    {"meaning":"soldier","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"兵士","answer":["へいし"]},
    {"meaning":"normal, usual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平常","answer":["へいじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"square (e.g. metre), square","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平方","answer":["へいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement, parallel, abreast","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"並列","answer":["へいれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass, to elapse, to experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経る","answer":["へる"]},
    {"meaning":"compilation, editing, completed poem, book, part of book","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"編","answer":["へん"]},
    {"meaning":"side, left radical of a character, inclining, inclining toward, biased","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"偏","answer":["へん"]},
    {"meaning":"change, reform, revolution, upheaval, (the) Reformation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変革","answer":["へんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"return, restoration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"返還","answer":["へんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"prejudice, narrow view","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"偏見","answer":["へんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"repayment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"返済","answer":["へんさい"]},
    {"meaning":"change, transition, vicissitudes","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"変遷","answer":["へんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"reply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"返答","answer":["へんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"change, fluctuation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変動","answer":["へんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"explanation, justification, defence, excuse","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弁解","answer":["べんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"convenience, accommodation, advantage, expedience","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"便宜","answer":["べんぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"defense, pleading, advocacy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弁護","answer":["べんご"]},
    {"meaning":"next word, compensation, reparation, indemnity, reimbursement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弁償","answer":["べんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion, debate, argument","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弁論","answer":["べんろん"]},
    {"meaning":"ear (of plant), head (of plant)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"穂","answer":["ほ"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing, nurturing, rearing, lactation, suckling","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保育","answer":["ほいく"]},
    {"meaning":"imitate, follow, emulate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"倣","answer":["ほう"]},
    {"meaning":"bill (law)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"法案","answer":["ほうあん"]},
    {"meaning":"collapse, decay (physics), crumbling, breaking down, caving in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"崩壊","answer":["ほうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"law, jurisprudence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"法学","answer":["ほうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"abandonment, renunciation, abdication (responsibility right)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"放棄","answer":["ほうき"]},
    {"meaning":"treasured article or vessel, outstanding individual","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宝器","answer":["ほうき"]},
    {"meaning":"feudalistic","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"封建","answer":["ほうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"abundant harvest, bumper crop","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"豊作","answer":["ほうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"plan, policy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"方策","answer":["ほうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"attendance, service","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奉仕","answer":["ほうし"]},
    {"meaning":"form, method, system","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方式","answer":["ほうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"radiation, emission","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"放射","answer":["ほうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"radioactivity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"放射能","answer":["ほうしゃのう"]},
    {"meaning":"remuneration, recompense, reward, toll","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"報酬","answer":["ほうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"release, emit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放出","answer":["ほうしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to inform, to report","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"報じる","answer":["ほうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to inform, to report","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"報ずる","answer":["ほうずる"]},
    {"meaning":"leave as is, leave to chance, leave alone, neglect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放置","answer":["ほうち"]},
    {"meaning":"courtroom","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"法廷","answer":["ほうてい"]},
    {"meaning":"information, report","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"報道","answer":["ほうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"reward, prize","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"褒美","answer":["ほうび"]},
    {"meaning":"to bury, to inter, to entomb, to consign to oblivion, to shelve","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"葬る","answer":["ほうむる"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw into","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放り込む","answer":["ほうりこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw out, to fire, to expel, to give up, to abandon, to neglect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放り出す","answer":["ほうりだす"]},
    {"meaning":"saturation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飽和","answer":["ほうわ"]},
    {"meaning":"retaining warmth, keeping heat in, heat insulation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保温","answer":["ほおん"]},
    {"meaning":"capture, seizure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"捕獲","answer":["ほかく"]},
    {"meaning":"charge, custody, safekeeping, deposit, storage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保管","answer":["ほかん"]},
    {"meaning":"supply, supplying, replenishment","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"補給","answer":["ほきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"compensation, reinforcement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"補強","answer":["ほきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"insurance, guarantee","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保険","answer":["ほけん"]},
    {"meaning":"whaling, whale fishing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕鯨","answer":["ほげい"]},
    {"meaning":"to boast of, to be proud of","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誇る","answer":["ほこる"]},
    {"meaning":"care, protection, shelter, guardianship, favor, patronage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保護","answer":["ほご"]},
    {"meaning":"dried washing (clothes)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"干し物","answer":["ほしもの"]},
    {"meaning":"conservative, maintaining","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保守","answer":["ほしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"guarantee, security, assurance, pledge, warranty","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保障","answer":["ほしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"compensation, reparation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"補償","answer":["ほしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"supplementation, supplement, replenishment, replenishing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"補充","answer":["ほじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"assistance, support, aid, auxiliary","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"補助","answer":["ほじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"pavement, road surface","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"舗装","answer":["ほそう"]},
    {"meaning":"supplement, complement","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"補足","answer":["ほそく"]},
    {"meaning":"fit, spasm","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発作","answer":["ほっさ"]},
    {"meaning":"vicinity,nearby","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"辺り","answer":["あたり","ほとり"]},
    {"meaning":"to unfasten","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解く","answer":["とく","ほどく"]},
    {"meaning":"to donate, to give, to conduct, to apply, to perform","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"施す","answer":["ほどこす"]},
    {"meaning":"day care worker in a kindergarten nursery school etc.","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保母","answer":["ほぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"health preservation, recuperation, recreation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保養","answer":["ほよう"]},
    {"meaning":"constable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"捕吏","answer":["ほり"]},
    {"meaning":"prisoner (of war)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"捕虜","answer":["ほりょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be ruined, to go under, to perish, to be destroyed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滅びる","answer":["ほろびる"]},
    {"meaning":"to destroy, to overthrow, to wreck, to ruin","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滅ぼす","answer":["ほろぼす"]},
    {"meaning":"propriety, fundamental rules","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"本格","answer":["ほんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"main building","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本館","answer":["ほんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"seriousness, truth, sanctity","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本気","answer":["ほんき"]},
    {"meaning":"essence, true nature, reality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"本質","answer":["ほんしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"substance, real form, object of worship","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"本体","answer":["ほんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"real intention, motive","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本音","answer":["ほんね"]},
    {"meaning":"mere, only, just","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本の","answer":["ほんの"]},
    {"meaning":"instinct","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"本能","answer":["ほんのう"]},
    {"meaning":"home, habitat, center, best place, genuine","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"本場","answer":["ほんば"]},
    {"meaning":"text (of document), body (of letter)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"本文","answer":["ほんぶん"]},
    {"meaning":"real name","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本名","answer":["ほんみょう"]},
    {"meaning":"defense, protection, self-defense","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"防衛","answer":["ぼうえい"]},
    {"meaning":"fire prevention, fire fighting, fire proof","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"防火","answer":["ぼうか"]},
    {"meaning":"disturbance, obstruction, hindrance, jamming, interference","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妨害","answer":["ぼうがい"]},
    {"meaning":"spinning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紡績","answer":["ぼうせき"]},
    {"meaning":"expansion, swelling, increase, growth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"膨脹","answer":["ぼうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"beginning, start, outset","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冒頭","answer":["ぼうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"insurrection, rebellion, revolt, riot, uprising","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暴動","answer":["ぼうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"storm, windstorm, gale","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暴風","answer":["ぼうふう"]},
    {"meaning":"violence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"暴力","answer":["ぼうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"fund-raising, collection of funds","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"募金","answer":["ぼきん"]},
    {"meaning":"pastor, minister, clergyman","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"牧師","answer":["ぼくし"]},
    {"meaning":"alma mater","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"母校","answer":["ぼこう"]},
    {"meaning":"forfeited","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"没収","answer":["ぼっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"ruin, fall, collapse","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"没落","answer":["ぼつらく"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for flat objects (e.g. sheets of paper)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"枚","answer":["まい"]},
    {"meaning":"buried property, treasure trove","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"埋蔵","answer":["まいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"to dance, to flutter about, to revolve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"舞う","answer":["まう"]},
    {"meaning":"just above, right overhead","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真上","answer":["まうえ"]},
    {"meaning":"advance sale, booking","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"前売り","answer":["まえうり"]},
    {"meaning":"preface, introduction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"前置き","answer":["まえおき"]},
    {"meaning":"in advance, beforehand, previously","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"前もって","answer":["まえもって"]},
    {"meaning":"to entrust, to leave to a person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"任す","answer":["まかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to defeat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"負かす","answer":["まかす"]},
    {"meaning":"to give board to, to provide meals, to pay","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"賄う","answer":["まかなう"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn, to bend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"曲がる","answer":["まがる"]},
    {"meaning":"volume","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"巻","answer":["まき"]},
    {"meaning":"confusing, misleading, equivocal, ambiguous","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紛らわしい","answer":["まぎらわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be diverted, to slip into","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紛れる","answer":["まぎれる"]},
    {"meaning":"membrane, film","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"膜","answer":["まく"]},
    {"meaning":"sincerity, devotion","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真心","answer":["まこころ","まごころ"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, faith, fidelity, sincerity, trust, confidence, reliance, devotion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誠","answer":["まこと"]},
    {"meaning":"truly, actually, really","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真に","answer":["まことに"]},
    {"meaning":"to excel, to surpass, to outrival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝る","answer":["まさる"]},
    {"meaning":"extra, additional, less objectionable, better, preferable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増し","answer":["まし"]},
    {"meaning":"right under, directly below","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真下","answer":["ました"]},
    {"meaning":"to mix, to converse with, to cross (swords)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交える","answer":["まじえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to cross, to intersect, to associate with, to mingle with, to interest, to join","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交わる","answer":["まじわる"]},
    {"meaning":"anaesthesia","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"麻酔","answer":["ますい"]},
    {"meaning":"unappetising, unpleasant (taste appearance situation), ugly, unskilful, awkward, bungling, unwise, untime","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不味い","answer":["まずい"]},
    {"meaning":"wink, twinkling (of stars), flicker (of light)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"瞬き","answer":["またたき"]},
    {"meaning":"appointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待ち合わせ","answer":["まちあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to make a mistake, to be incorrect, to be mistaken","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"間違う","answer":["まちがう"]},
    {"meaning":"looking forward to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待ち遠しい","answer":["まちどおしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to look anxiously for, to wait eagerly for","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"待ち望む","answer":["まちのぞむ"]},
    {"meaning":"closing years (period days), last stage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"末期","answer":["まっき"]},
    {"meaning":"in two equal parts","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ二つ","answer":["まっぷたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape from, to be rescued from, to avoid, to evade, to avert, to elude, to be exempted, to be relieved","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"免れる","answer":["まぬかれる"]},
    {"meaning":"invitation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"招き","answer":["まねき"]},
    {"meaning":"occasionally, frequently","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"間々","answer":["まま"]},
    {"meaning":"eyebrow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"眉","answer":["まゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"completely","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"丸々","answer":["まるまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to make round, to round off, to roll up, to curl up, to seduce, to cajole, to explain away","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"丸める","answer":["まるめる"]},
    {"meaning":"full moon","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満月","answer":["まんげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"unanimous, whole audience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満場","answer":["まんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"middle, centre, mid-way","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真ん中","answer":["まんなか"]},
    {"meaning":"right in front, under the nose","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真ん前","answer":["まんまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"perfectly circular","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"真ん丸い","answer":["まんまるい"]},
    {"meaning":"formal marriage interview","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見合い","answer":["みあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to exchange glances, to postpone, to suspend operations, to refrain from performing an action","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見合わせる","answer":["みあわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"to overlook, to fail to notice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見落とす","answer":["みおとす"]},
    {"meaning":"savage land, backward region, uncivilized","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未開","answer":["みかい"]},
    {"meaning":"taste, palate, sense of taste","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"味覚","answer":["みかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to (happen to) see, to notice, to catch sight of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見掛ける","answer":["みかける"]},
    {"meaning":"new moon,crescent moon","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"三日月","answer":["みかづき","みかずき"]},
    {"meaning":"viewpoint","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見方","answer":["みかた"]},
    {"meaning":"unsightly, ugly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見苦しい","answer":["みぐるしい"]},
    {"meaning":"hope, prospects, expectation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見込み","answer":["みこみ"]},
    {"meaning":"unmarried","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未婚","answer":["みこん"]},
    {"meaning":"miserable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"惨め","answer":["みじめ"]},
    {"meaning":"inexperience, unripeness, raw, unskilled, immature, inexperienced","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"未熟","answer":["みじゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"shabby, seedy","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見すぼらしい","answer":["みすぼらしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to show off, to flaunt","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見せびらかす","answer":["みせびらかす"]},
    {"meaning":"show, exhibition","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見せ物","answer":["みせもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to satisfy, to ingratiate, to fill, to fulfill","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満たす","answer":["みたす"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw out of order, to disarrange, to disturb","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乱す","answer":["みだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to get confused, to be disordered, to be disturbed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"乱れる","answer":["みだれる"]},
    {"meaning":"not yet known","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未知","answer":["みち"]},
    {"meaning":"to be guided, to be shown","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"導く","answer":["みちびく"]},
    {"meaning":"crowd, close formation, dense","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"密集","answer":["みっしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"related, connected, close, intimate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"密接","answer":["みっせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"density","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"密度","answer":["みつど"]},
    {"meaning":"estimation, quotation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見積り","answer":["みつもり"]},
    {"meaning":"not yet fixed, undecided, pending","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未定","answer":["みてい"]},
    {"meaning":"perspective, unobstructed view, outlook, forecast, prospect, insight","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見通し","answer":["みとおし"]},
    {"meaning":"source, origin","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"源","answer":["みなもと"]},
    {"meaning":"peak, ridge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"峰","answer":["みね"]},
    {"meaning":"to miss, to overlook, to leave at large","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見逃す","answer":["みのがす"]},
    {"meaning":"view","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見晴らし","answer":["みはらし"]},
    {"meaning":"enquiry, expression of sympathy, expression of concern","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見舞","answer":["みまい"]},
    {"meaning":"pulse","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脈","answer":["みゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"lingering affection, attachment, regret(s), reluctance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"未練","answer":["みれん"]},
    {"meaning":"to look out over, to survey (scene), to take an extensive view of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見渡す","answer":["みわたす"]},
    {"meaning":"democratic, the head of the nation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"民主","answer":["みんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"private home providing lodging for travelers","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"民宿","answer":["みんしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"people, race, nation, racial customs, folk customs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"民族","answer":["みんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"people, race, nation, racial customs, folk customs","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"民俗","answer":["みんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"six","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"六","answer":["ろく","む"]},
    {"meaning":"direction, situation, exposure, aspect, suitability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向き","answer":["むき"]},
    {"meaning":"for ~, oriented towards ~","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向け","answer":["むけ"]},
    {"meaning":"son-in-law","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"婿","answer":["むこ"]},
    {"meaning":"ending, conclusion, union","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結び","answer":["むすび"]},
    {"meaning":"connection, relation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結び付き","answer":["むすびつき"]},
    {"meaning":"to be connected or related, to join together","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結び付く","answer":["むすびつく"]},
    {"meaning":"to combine, to join, to tie on, to attach with a knot","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結び付ける","answer":["むすびつける"]},
    {"meaning":"vacant, futile, vain, void, empty, ineffective, lifeless","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空しい","answer":["むなしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to swarm, to gather","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"群がる","answer":["むらがる"]},
    {"meaning":"noted product","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"名産","answer":["めいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"name","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"名称","answer":["めいしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"a hit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命中","answer":["めいちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"register of names","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"名簿","answer":["めいぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"honor, credit, prestige","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"名誉","answer":["めいよ"]},
    {"meaning":"clarity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"明瞭","answer":["めいりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"bright, clear, cheerful","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"明朗","answer":["めいろう"]},
    {"meaning":"weight","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"目方","answer":["めかた"]},
    {"meaning":"blessing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恵み","answer":["めぐみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to bless, to show mercy to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恵む","answer":["めぐむ"]},
    {"meaning":"brilliant, splendid, striking, remarkable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目覚しい","answer":["めざましい"]},
    {"meaning":"to wake up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目覚める","answer":["めざめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to call, to send for, to put on, to wear, to take (a bath), to ride in, to buy, to eat, to drink, to catch (a","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"召す","answer":["めす"]},
    {"meaning":"absurd, unreasonable, excessive, messed up, spoiled, wreaked","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滅茶苦茶","answer":["めちゃくちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"look, expression of the eyes, eyes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目付き","answer":["めつき"]},
    {"meaning":"downfall, ruin, collapse, destruction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滅亡","answer":["めつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"scale, gradations","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"目盛り","answer":["めもり"]},
    {"meaning":"interview","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"面会","answer":["めんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"exemption, exoneration, discharge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"免除","answer":["めんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"face, honour, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"面目","answer":["めんぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"to create, to establish","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"設ける","answer":["もうける"]},
    {"meaning":"to propose, to suggest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し入れる","answer":["もうしいれる"]},
    {"meaning":"application, entry, request, subscription, offer, proposal, overture, challenge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し込み","answer":["もうしこみ"]},
    {"meaning":"proposal, request, claim, report, notice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申出","answer":["もうしで"]},
    {"meaning":"to report to, to tell, to suggest, to submit, to request, to make an offer, to come forward with informati","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し出る","answer":["もうしでる"]},
    {"meaning":"blind spot","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盲点","answer":["もうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"violent, vehement, rage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"猛烈","answer":["もうれつ"]},
    {"meaning":"catalogue, catalog, list","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"目録","answer":["もくろく"]},
    {"meaning":"a plan, a scheme, a project, a program, intention, goal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"目論見","answer":["もくろみ"]},
    {"meaning":"model, dummy, maquette","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"模型","answer":["もけい"]},
    {"meaning":"groping (for)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"模索","answer":["もさく"]},
    {"meaning":"1. hold, charge, keep possession, in charge, 2. wear, durability, life, draw, 3. usage (suff)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"持ち","answer":["もち"]},
    {"meaning":"hot topic, talk of the town","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"持ち切り","answer":["もちきり"]},
    {"meaning":"too good, more than one deserves, wasteful, sacrilegious, unworthy of","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物体ない","answer":["もったいない"]},
    {"meaning":"to entertain, to make welcome","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"持て成す","answer":["もてなす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be well liked, to be popular","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"持てる","answer":["もてる"]},
    {"meaning":"basis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基","answer":["もとい","もと"]},
    {"meaning":"storeroom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物置き","answer":["ものおき"]},
    {"meaning":"curiosity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"物好き","answer":["ものずき"]},
    {"meaning":"unsatisfied, unsatisfactory","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物足りない","answer":["ものたりない"]},
    {"meaning":"already, now","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最早","answer":["もはや"]},
    {"meaning":"exemplar, exemplification, exemplum, model, example","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"模範","answer":["もはん"]},
    {"meaning":"imitation, copying","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"模倣","answer":["もほう"]},
    {"meaning":"to hold (a meeting), to give (a dinner), to feel, to show signs of, to develop symptoms of, to feel (sick","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"催す","answer":["もよおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to let leak, to reveal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漏らす","answer":["もらす"]},
    {"meaning":"to rouse, to swell, to rise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盛り上がる","answer":["もりあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"to leak, to run out","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漏る","answer":["もる"]},
    {"meaning":"to leak out, to escape, to come through, to shine through, to filter out, to be omitted","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漏れる","answer":["もれる"]},
    {"meaning":"problem, question","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"問","answer":["もん"]},
    {"meaning":"arrow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"矢","answer":["や"]},
    {"meaning":"question mark","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"哉","answer":["や"]},
    {"meaning":"fields, outskirts, open air, suburbs","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"野外","answer":["やがい"]},
    {"meaning":"walking around at night,night train,night travel","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜行","answer":["やこう","やぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"post, managerial position, official position","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役職","answer":["やくしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be useful, to be helpful, to serve the purpose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役立つ","answer":["やくだつ"]},
    {"meaning":"town hall","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役場","answer":["やくば"]},
    {"meaning":"bedding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夜具","answer":["やぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"mansion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"屋敷","answer":["やしき"]},
    {"meaning":"Shinto shrine","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"社","answer":["やしろ"]},
    {"meaning":"ambition, aspiration, designs, treachery","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"野心","answer":["やしん"]},
    {"meaning":"easy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"易い","answer":["やすい"]},
    {"meaning":"cheap-looking, tawdry, insignificant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"安っぽい","answer":["やすっぽい"]},
    {"meaning":"to rest, to suspend, to give relief","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"休める","answer":["やすめる"]},
    {"meaning":"wild","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"野生","answer":["やせい"]},
    {"meaning":"midnight,dead of night","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜中","answer":["よなか","やちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"servant, fellow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奴","answer":["やっこ"]},
    {"meaning":"to beat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"やっ付ける","answer":["やっつける"]},
    {"meaning":"opposition party","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"野党","answer":["やとう"]},
    {"meaning":"illness, disease","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"病","answer":["やまい"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall ill, to be ill","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"病む","answer":["やむ"]},
    {"meaning":"cannot be helped, unavoidable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"止むを得ない","answer":["やむをえない"]},
    {"meaning":"to carry through, to achieve, to complete","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遣り通す","answer":["やりとおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"やり遂げる","answer":["やりとげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to do, to have sexual intercourse, to kill, to give (to inferiors animals etc.), to dispatch (a letter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遣る","answer":["やる"]},
    {"meaning":"to soften, to moderate, to relieve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和らげる","answer":["やわらげる"]},
    {"meaning":"predominance, ascendancy, superiority","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優位","answer":["ゆうい"]},
    {"meaning":"depression, melancholy, dejection, gloom","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"憂鬱","answer":["ゆううつ"]},
    {"meaning":"beneficial, profitable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"有益","answer":["ゆうえき"]},
    {"meaning":"supremacy, predominance, being superior to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優越","answer":["ゆうえつ"]},
    {"meaning":"bravery, heroism, gallantry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勇敢","answer":["ゆうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"organic","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有機","answer":["ゆうき"]},
    {"meaning":"evening, (evening) twilight","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夕暮れ","answer":["ゆうぐれ"]},
    {"meaning":"financing, loan","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"融資","answer":["ゆうし"]},
    {"meaning":"to own, to be endowed with","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有する","answer":["ゆうする"]},
    {"meaning":"lending (money), accommodation, adaptability, versatility, finance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"融通","answer":["ゆうずう"]},
    {"meaning":"superiority, superior power, predominance, preponderance","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"優勢","answer":["ゆうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"preference, priority","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優先","answer":["ゆうせん"]},
    {"meaning":"guidance, leading, induction, introduction, incitement, inducement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誘導","answer":["ゆうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"grace, refinement, elegance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優美","answer":["ゆうび"]},
    {"meaning":"good prospects, full of hope, promising","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有望","answer":["ゆうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"nomadism","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遊牧","answer":["ゆうぼく"]},
    {"meaning":"sunset","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"夕焼け","answer":["ゆうやけ"]},
    {"meaning":"1. influence, prominence, 2. potent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有力","answer":["ゆうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"ghost, specter, apparition, phantom","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幽霊","answer":["ゆうれい"]},
    {"meaning":"temptation, allurement, lure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誘惑","answer":["ゆうわく"]},
    {"meaning":"to shake, to jolt, to rock, to swing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"揺さぶる","answer":["ゆさぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"to point at","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指差す","answer":["ゆびさす"]},
    {"meaning":"bow (and arrow)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弓","answer":["ゆみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to swing, to sway, to shake, to tremble","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"揺らぐ","answer":["ゆらぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to become loose, to slacken","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緩む","answer":["ゆるむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to loosen, to slow down","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緩める","answer":["ゆるめる"]},
    {"meaning":"lenient","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緩やか","answer":["ゆるやか"]},
    {"meaning":"world, society, age, generation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世","answer":["よ"]},
    {"meaning":"good","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好い","answer":["よい"]},
    {"meaning":"primary factor, main cause","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要因","answer":["よういん"]},
    {"meaning":"solution (liquid)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"溶液","answer":["ようえき"]},
    {"meaning":"business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"用件","answer":["ようけん"]},
    {"meaning":"protection, nursing, protective care","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"養護","answer":["ようご"]},
    {"meaning":"blank form","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用紙","answer":["ようし"]},
    {"meaning":"style, form, pattern","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様式","answer":["ようしき"]},
    {"meaning":"to demand, to require, to take","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要する","answer":["ようする"]},
    {"meaning":"claim, demand, request, application","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"要請","answer":["ようせい"]},
    {"meaning":"training, development","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"養成","answer":["ようせい"]},
    {"meaning":"aspect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様相","answer":["ようそう"]},
    {"meaning":"articles, supplies, parts","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用品","answer":["ようひん"]},
    {"meaning":"western style","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"洋風","answer":["ようふう"]},
    {"meaning":"directions, rules of use","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"用法","answer":["ようほう"]},
    {"meaning":"demand for, request","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要望","answer":["ようぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"leisure, leisure time, spare time","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"余暇","answer":["よか"]},
    {"meaning":"presentiment, premonition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予感","answer":["よかん"]},
    {"meaning":"side show, entertainment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"余興","answer":["よきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"deposit, bank account","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"預金","answer":["よきん"]},
    {"meaning":"check, restraint, oppression, suppression","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抑圧","answer":["よくあつ"]},
    {"meaning":"bathroom, bath","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"浴室","answer":["よくしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"suppression","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抑制","answer":["よくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"greedy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欲深い","answer":["よくふかい"]},
    {"meaning":"desire, appetite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欲望","answer":["よくぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"to send, to forward","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄こす","answer":["よこす"]},
    {"meaning":"sumo grand champion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"横綱","answer":["よこづな"]},
    {"meaning":"good or bad, merits or demerits, quality, suitability","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"善し悪し","answer":["よしあし"]},
    {"meaning":"expectation, anticipation, prediction, forecast","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予想","answer":["よそう"]},
    {"meaning":"place, room, margin, scope","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余地","answer":["よち"]},
    {"meaning":"government party, (ruling) party in power, government","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"与党","answer":["よとう"]},
    {"meaning":"to challenge, to call somebody to halt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼び止める","answer":["よびとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"staying up late, keeping late hours, sitting up late at night, nighthawk","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夜更かし","answer":["よふかし"]},
    {"meaning":"late at night","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夜更け","answer":["よふけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to read out loud (and clearly), to call a roll","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"読み上げる","answer":["よみあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to lean against, to recline on, to lean on, to rely on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄り掛かる","answer":["よりかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"well, properly, suitably, best regards, please remember me","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宜しく","answer":["よろしく"]},
    {"meaning":"to abate, to weaken, to be emaciated, to be dejected, to be perplexed","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱まる","answer":["よわまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to weaken","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱める","answer":["よわめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to weaken, to be troubled, to be downcast, to be emaciated, to be dejected, to be perplexed, to impair","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"弱る","answer":["よわる"]},
    {"meaning":"attendance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"来場","answer":["らいじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"dairy (farm)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酪農","answer":["らくのう"]},
    {"meaning":"fall, drop, come down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落下","answer":["らっか"]},
    {"meaning":"optimism","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"楽観","answer":["らっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"abuse, misuse, misappropriation, using to excess","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"濫用","answer":["らんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"theory, reason","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"理屈","answer":["りくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"intelligence","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"利根","answer":["りこん"]},
    {"meaning":"interest (bank)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利子","answer":["りし"]},
    {"meaning":"profit, returns","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"利潤","answer":["りじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"reason, sense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理性","answer":["りせい"]},
    {"meaning":"interest (bank)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利息","answer":["りそく"]},
    {"meaning":"solid body","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立体","answer":["りったい"]},
    {"meaning":"legislation, lawmaking","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"立法","answer":["りっぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"advantage, point in favor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利点","answer":["りてん"]},
    {"meaning":"abbreviation, acronym","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"略語","answer":["りゃくご"]},
    {"meaning":"pillage, plunder, looting, robbery","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"略奪","answer":["りゃくだつ"]},
    {"meaning":"styleof, method of, manner of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流","answer":["りゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"circulation of money or goods, flow of water or air, distribution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流通","answer":["りゅうつう"]},
    {"meaning":"finish, completion, understanding","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"了","answer":["りょう"]},
    {"meaning":"material, charge, rate, fee","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"料","answer":["りょう"]},
    {"meaning":"area, domain, territory, field, region, regime","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"領域","answer":["りょういき"]},
    {"meaning":"comprehension, consent, understanding, roger (on the radio)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"了解","answer":["りょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"territorial waters","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"領海","answer":["りょうかい"]},
    {"meaning":"both extremities, north and south poles, positive and negative poles","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"両極","answer":["りょうきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"favorable, satisfactory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"良好","answer":["りょうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"good sense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"良識","answer":["りょうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"good quality, superior quality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"良質","answer":["りょうしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"acknowledgement, understanding (e.g. please be understanding of the mess during our renovation)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"了承","answer":["りょうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"conscience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"良心","answer":["りょうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"territory, dominion","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"領地","answer":["りょうち"]},
    {"meaning":"dominion, territory, possession","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"領土","answer":["りょうど"]},
    {"meaning":"compatibility, coexistence, standing together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"両立","answer":["りょうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"passenger (transport)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"旅客","answer":["りょかく"]},
    {"meaning":"passport","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"旅券","answer":["りょけん"]},
    {"meaning":"personal history, background, career, log","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"履歴","answer":["りれき"]},
    {"meaning":"theory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理論","answer":["りろん"]},
    {"meaning":"ring,hoop,circle","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"輪","answer":["わ","りん"]},
    {"meaning":"forestry","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"林業","answer":["りんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"analogous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"類似","answer":["るいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"analogy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"類推","answer":["るいすい"]},
    {"meaning":"cruelty, coldheartedness, relentless, ruthless","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冷酷","answer":["れいこく"]},
    {"meaning":"cold storage, refrigeration","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"冷蔵","answer":["れいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"coolness, indifference","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冷淡","answer":["れいたん"]},
    {"meaning":"love, love-making, passion, emotion, affections","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"恋愛","answer":["れんあい"]},
    {"meaning":"consecutive holidays","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連休","answer":["れんきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"every day, prolonged","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連日","answer":["れんじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"colleagues, company, a lot","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連中","answer":["れんじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"solidarity","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"連帯","answer":["れんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"commonwealth, federation of states","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"連邦","answer":["れんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"league, union, alliance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"連盟","answer":["れんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"senility, senile decay","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"老衰","answer":["ろうすい"]},
    {"meaning":"reading aloud, recitation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"朗読","answer":["ろうどく"]},
    {"meaning":"waste, extravagance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"浪費","answer":["ろうひ"]},
    {"meaning":"labour, effort, toil, trouble","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"労力","answer":["ろうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"discussion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論議","answer":["ろんぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"logic","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論理","answer":["ろんり"]},
    {"meaning":"sum, harmony, peace","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和","answer":["わ"]},
    {"meaning":"selfishness, egoism, wilfulness, disobedience, whim","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"我がまま","answer":["わがまま"]},
    {"meaning":"frame, slide","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"枠","answer":["わく"]},
    {"meaning":"planet","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"惑星","answer":["わくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"art, technique","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"技","answer":["わざ"]},
    {"meaning":"troublesome, annoying, complicated","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"煩わしい","answer":["わずらわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"migratory bird, bird of passage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"渡り鳥","answer":["わたりどり"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese style","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和風","answer":["わふう"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese text, sentence in Japanese","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"和文","answer":["わぶん"]},
    {"meaning":"comparatively","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割合に","answer":["わりあいに"]},
    {"meaning":"allotment, assignment, allocation, quota, rationing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割り当て","answer":["わりあて"]},
    {"meaning":"to cut in, to thrust oneself into, to wedge oneself in, to muscle in on, to interrupt, to disturb","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割り込む","answer":["わりこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"division (math)","kanjiLevel":2,"question":"割り算","answer":["わりざん"]},
    {"meaning":"discount, reduction, rebate, tenths discounted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割引き","answer":["わりびき"]},
    {"meaning":"bad fellow, rascal, ruffian, scoundrel","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪者","answer":["わるもの"]},
    {"meaning":"romanization, Roman letters","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"ローマ字","answer":["ローマじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to meet,to encounter (undesirable nuance)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遭う","answer":["あう"]},
    {"meaning":"to fan,to flap","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扇ぐ","answer":["あおぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to lift,to fry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"揚げる","answer":["あげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to raise,to fly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"挙げる","answer":["あげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to long for,to yearn after,to admire","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"憧れる","answer":["あこがれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to warm up,to get warm","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暖まる","answer":["あたたまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to warm,to heat","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暖める","answer":["あたためる"]},
    {"meaning":"compression,condensation,pressure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"圧縮","answer":["あっしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"suspicious,dubious,doubtful","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怪しい","answer":["あやしい"]},
    {"meaning":"coarse,rough","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"粗い","answer":["あらい"]},
    {"meaning":"unexpectedly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"案外","answer":["あんがい"]},
    {"meaning":"meaning,significance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"意義","answer":["いぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"once,tentatively,in outline,for the time being","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一応","answer":["いちおう"]},
    {"meaning":"simultaneous,all at once","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一斉","answer":["いっせい"]},
    {"meaning":"once,for a moment,one morning,temporarily","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一旦","answer":["いったん"]},
    {"meaning":"water well","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"井戸","answer":["いど"]},
    {"meaning":"latitude (nav.)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緯度","answer":["いど"]},
    {"meaning":"cousin (female)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従姉妹","answer":["いとこ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be proud,to swagger","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"威張る","answer":["いばる"]},
    {"meaning":"to hate,to dislike","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嫌がる","answer":["いやがる"]},
    {"meaning":"to attack,to avenge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"討つ","answer":["うつ"]},
    {"meaning":"resentment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恨み","answer":["うらみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to curse,to feel bitter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恨む","answer":["うらむ"]},
    {"meaning":"party,banquet","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宴会","answer":["えんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"aid,assistance,help,reinforcement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応援","answer":["おうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"to answer,to respond,to meet,to satisfy,to accept","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応ずる","answer":["おうずる"]},
    {"meaning":"reception","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応接","answer":["おうせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"receiving,dealing with","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応対","answer":["おうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"(col) round trip,coming and going,return ticket","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"往復","answer":["おうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"application,put to practical use","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応用","answer":["おうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"about,roughly,as a rule,approximately","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大凡","answer":["おおよそ"]},
    {"meaning":"part of word written in kana","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"送り仮名","answer":["おくりがな"]},
    {"meaning":"to neglect,to be off guard,to be feeling better","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怠る","answer":["おこたる"]},
    {"meaning":"to obtain,to reap,to pay,to supply,to accept","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"納める","answer":["おさめる"]},
    {"meaning":"regrettable,disappointing,precious","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"惜しい","answer":["おしい"]},
    {"meaning":"bow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"御辞儀","answer":["おじぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"(hon) aunt","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"伯母さん","answer":["おばさん"]},
    {"meaning":"to sell wholesale,grated (vegetables)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"卸す","answer":["おろす"]},
    {"meaning":"grace,favor,blessing,benefit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恩恵","answer":["おんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"mosquito","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蚊","answer":["か"]},
    {"meaning":"intro,outline,general remarks","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"概論","answer":["がいろん"]},
    {"meaning":"on the contrary,rather,all the more,instead","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"却って","answer":["かえって"]},
    {"meaning":"hedge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"垣根","answer":["かきね"]},
    {"meaning":"aerial,overhead,fiction,fanciful","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"架空","answer":["かくう"]},
    {"meaning":"expansion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拡充","answer":["かくじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"expansion,extension,enlargement,escape (ESC)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拡張","answer":["かくちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"probability","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"確率","answer":["かくりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"excess,over-","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"過剰","answer":["かじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"hard (esp. wood),steadfast,honorable,stuffy writing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"堅い","answer":["かたい"]},
    {"meaning":"katakana","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"片仮名","answer":["かたかな"]},
    {"meaning":"lump,mass,clod,cluster","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"塊","answer":["かたまり"]},
    {"meaning":"musical instrument","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"楽器","answer":["がっき"]},
    {"meaning":"grade in school","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"学級","answer":["がっきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"parenthesis,brackets","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"括弧","answer":["かっこ"]},
    {"meaning":"activity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"活躍","answer":["かつやく"]},
    {"meaning":"assumption,supposition,hypothesis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仮定","answer":["かてい"]},
    {"meaning":"(n) alias,pseudonym,pen name (かめい), syllabary (かな)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仮名","answer":["かな","かめい"]},
    {"meaning":"kana orthography,syllabary spelling","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"仮名遣い","answer":["かなづかい"]},
    {"meaning":"bell,chime","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鐘","answer":["かね"]},
    {"meaning":"to hold (position),to serve,to be unable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"兼ねる","answer":["かねる"]},
    {"meaning":"song,ballad","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"歌謡","answer":["かよう"]},
    {"meaning":"shell,husk,hull,chaff","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"殻","answer":["から"]},
    {"meaning":"to be thirsty","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"渇く","answer":["かわく"]},
    {"meaning":"money order,exchange","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"為替","answer":["かわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"deep emotion,impression,inspiration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"感激","answer":["かんげき"]},
    {"meaning":"appreciation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鑑賞","answer":["かんしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"misunderstanding,wrong guess","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勘違い","answer":["かんちがい"]},
    {"meaning":"sign,signboard,doorplate,poster","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"看板","answer":["かんばん"]},
    {"meaning":"nursing (a patient)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"看病","answer":["かんびょう"]},
    {"meaning":"instrument","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"器械","answer":["きかい"]},
    {"meaning":"utensil","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"器具","answer":["きぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"ceremony,rite,ritual,service","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"儀式","answer":["ぎしき"]},
    {"meaning":"standard,basis,criteria,norm","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基準","answer":["きじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"foundation,basis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基礎","answer":["きそ"]},
    {"meaning":"base","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基地","answer":["きち"]},
    {"meaning":"foundation,basis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基盤","answer":["きばん"]},
    {"meaning":"shame,very kind of you,sorry to trouble","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恐縮","answer":["きょうしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"to destroy,to pull down,to make change (money)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"崩す","answer":["くずす"]},
    {"meaning":"to collapse,to crumble","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"崩れる","answer":["くずれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to break,to smash","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"砕く","answer":["くだく"]},
    {"meaning":"to break,to be broken","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"砕ける","answer":["くだける"]},
    {"meaning":"lips","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"唇","answer":["くちびる"]},
    {"meaning":"punctuation marks","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"句読点","answer":["くとうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"to serve sake","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酌む","answer":["くむ"]},
    {"meaning":"regrettable,mortifying,vexing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"悔しい","answer":["くやしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to mourn","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"悔やむ","answer":["くやむ"]},
    {"meaning":"country,district","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"郡","answer":["ぐん"]},
    {"meaning":"fluorescent lamp,person who is slow to react","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蛍光灯","answer":["けいこうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"continuation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"継続","answer":["けいぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"system,family line,geological formation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"系統","answer":["けいとう"]},
    {"meaning":"sudden increase","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"激増","answer":["げきぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"month (last third of)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"下旬","answer":["げじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cut down little by little,to take a percentage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"削る","answer":["けずる"]},
    {"meaning":"masterpiece,best work,boner,blunder","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"傑作","answer":["けっさく"]},
    {"meaning":"modesty,humility","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"謙虚","answer":["けんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"manuscript,copy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"原稿","answer":["げんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"training","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"研修","answer":["けんしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"strict,rigour,severe,firm","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"厳重","answer":["げんじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"microscope","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"顕微鏡","answer":["けんびきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Go (board game of capturing territory)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"碁","answer":["ご"]},
    {"meaning":"to ask,to request","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"請う","answer":["こう"]},
    {"meaning":"high class,high grade","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"高級","answer":["こうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"school building","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"校舎","answer":["こうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"the public","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"公衆","answer":["こうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"achievements,merit,meritorious service,meritorious deed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"功績","answer":["こうせき"]},
    {"meaning":"junior (at work or school)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"後輩","answer":["こうはい"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn,to scorch,to singe,to char","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"焦がす","answer":["こがす"]},
    {"meaning":"to burn,to be burned","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"焦げる","answer":["こげる"]},
    {"meaning":"personal expenses,pocket money,spending money,incidental expenses,allowance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"小遣い","answer":["こづかい"]},
    {"meaning":"old book,classics,classic","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"古典","answer":["こてん"]},
    {"meaning":"Koto (Japanese harp)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"琴","answer":["こと"]},
    {"meaning":"speech,expression,wording","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"言葉遣い","answer":["ことばづかい"]},
    {"meaning":"your pardon,declining (something),dismissal,permission","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"御免","answer":["ごめん"]},
    {"meaning":"pleasure,amusement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"娯楽","answer":["ごらく"]},
    {"meaning":"(hon) look,inspection,try","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"御覧","answer":["ごらん"]},
    {"meaning":"navy blue,deep blue","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紺","answer":["こん"]},
    {"meaning":"menu,program,schedule","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"献立","answer":["こんだて"]},
    {"meaning":"request,demand,claim,urge (action),press for","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"催促","answer":["さいそく"]},
    {"meaning":"calamity,misfortune","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"災難","answer":["さいなん"]},
    {"meaning":"sewing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裁縫","answer":["さいほう"]},
    {"meaning":"to tear,to split","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裂く","answer":["さく"]},
    {"meaning":"index,indices","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"索引","answer":["さくいん"]},
    {"meaning":"elimination,cancellation,deletion,erasure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"削除","answer":["さくじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"作製","answer":["さくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"tatami room","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"座敷","answer":["ざしき"]},
    {"meaning":"to insert,to put in,to graft,to wear in belt","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"挿す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine,to strike","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"射す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"photographing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"撮影","answer":["さつえい"]},
    {"meaning":"to disturb,to prevent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妨げる","answer":["さまたげる"]},
    {"meaning":"acidity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酸性","answer":["さんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"self-defense","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"自衛","answer":["じえい"]},
    {"meaning":"chairmanship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"司会","answer":["しかい"]},
    {"meaning":"site","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"敷地","answer":["しきち"]},
    {"meaning":"urgent,pressing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"至急","answer":["しきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to spread out,to lay out","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"敷く","answer":["しく"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow thick,to luxuriate,to be luxurious","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"茂る","answer":["しげる"]},
    {"meaning":"magnet","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"磁石","answer":["じしゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"attitude,posture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"姿勢","answer":["しせい"]},
    {"meaning":"writing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"執筆","answer":["しっぴつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to tie,to bind","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縛る","answer":["しばる"]},
    {"meaning":"(the) ground","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"地盤","answer":["じばん"]},
    {"meaning":"paper money,notes,bills","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紙幣","answer":["しへい"]},
    {"meaning":"to press,to wring,to squeeze","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"絞る","answer":["しぼる"]},
    {"meaning":"full name,identity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"氏名","answer":["しめい"]},
    {"meaning":"closing,cut-off,end,deadline,Closed,No Entrance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"締切","answer":["しめきり"]},
    {"meaning":"to shut up","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"締め切る","answer":["しめきる"]},
    {"meaning":"faucet,tap","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蛇口","answer":["じゃぐち"]},
    {"meaning":"(train) conductor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"車掌","answer":["しゃしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"repair,mending","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修繕","answer":["しゅうぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"inauguration,assumption of office","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"就任","answer":["しゅうにん"]},
    {"meaning":"idiom,idiomatic phrase,kanji compound","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"熟語","answer":["じゅくご"]},
    {"meaning":"reduction,curtailment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縮小","answer":["しゅくしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"official tour,business trip","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"出張","answer":["しゅっちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(telephone) receiver","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"受話器","answer":["じゅわき"]},
    {"meaning":"circulation,rotation,cycle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"循環","answer":["じゅんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"police,policeman","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"巡査","answer":["じゅんさ"]},
    {"meaning":"order,sequence,procedure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"順序","answer":["じゅんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"pure,true,genuine,unmixed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"純粋","answer":["じゅんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese chess","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"将棋","answer":["しょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"advanced level,high grade,senior","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"上級","answer":["じょうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"first 10 days of month","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"上旬","answer":["じょうじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"focus,point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"焦点","answer":["しょうてん"]},
    {"meaning":"elementary level","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"初級","answer":["しょきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"assistant professor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"助教授","answer":["じょきょうじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"first 10 days of the month","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"初旬","answer":["しょじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"tableware","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"食器","answer":["しょっき"]},
    {"meaning":"juice,sap,soup,broth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"汁","answer":["しる"]},
    {"meaning":"amateur,novice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素人","answer":["しろうと"]},
    {"meaning":"bullet train (very high speed),shinkansen","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"新幹線","answer":["しんかんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"application,request,petition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"申請","answer":["しんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"diagnosis","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"診断","answer":["しんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"penetration,invasion,raid,aggression,trespass","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"侵入","answer":["しんにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"vinegar","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酢","answer":["す"]},
    {"meaning":"cooking,culinary arts","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"炊事","answer":["すいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"hydrogen","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"水素","answer":["すいそ"]},
    {"meaning":"vertical,perpendicular","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"垂直","answer":["すいちょく"]},
    {"meaning":"presumption,assumption,estimation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"推定","answer":["すいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"picture book","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"図鑑","answer":["ずかん"]},
    {"meaning":"Japanese cedar","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"杉","answer":["すぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"likes and dislikes,taste","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"好き嫌い","answer":["すききらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be(come) transparent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"透き通る","answer":["すきとおる"]},
    {"meaning":"bell","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鈴","answer":["すず"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"棄てる","answer":["すてる"]},
    {"meaning":"obedient,meek,docile,unaffected","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素直","answer":["すなお"]},
    {"meaning":"ink","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"墨","answer":["すみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to clear (e.g. weather),to become transparent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"澄む","answer":["すむ"]},
    {"meaning":"sumo wrestling","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"相撲","answer":["すもう"]},
    {"meaning":"measurement,size,dimension","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"寸法","answer":["すんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacture,production","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"製作","answer":["せいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"integer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整数","answer":["せいすう"]},
    {"meaning":"adjustment,completion,consolidation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整備","answer":["せいび"]},
    {"meaning":"Christian Era,anno domini (A.D.)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"西暦","answer":["せいれき"]},
    {"meaning":"earthenware,crockery,china","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"瀬戸物","answer":["せともの"]},
    {"meaning":"to draw near,to press","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"迫る","answer":["せまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to attack,to assault","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"攻める","answer":["せめる"]},
    {"meaning":"stopper,cork,stopcock","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"栓","answer":["せん"]},
    {"meaning":"detergent,washing material","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"洗剤","answer":["せんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"folding fan","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扇子","answer":["せんす"]},
    {"meaning":"pointed end,tip,fine point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"先端","answer":["せんたん"]},
    {"meaning":"propaganda,publicity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宣伝","answer":["せんでん"]},
    {"meaning":"electric fan","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扇風機","answer":["せんぷうき"]},
    {"meaning":"storehouse,warehouse,godown","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"倉庫","answer":["そうこ"]},
    {"meaning":"production,literary creation,work","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"創作","answer":["そうさく"]},
    {"meaning":"funeral","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"葬式","answer":["そうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"zoori (Japanese footwear),sandals","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"草履","answer":["ぞうり"]},
    {"meaning":"to belong to,to come under,to be affiliated with,to be subject to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"属する","answer":["ぞくする"]},
    {"meaning":"character,qualities,genius","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素質","answer":["そしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stray (turn) from subject,to get lost,to go astray","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"逸れる","answer":["それる"]},
    {"meaning":"abacus","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"算盤","answer":["そろばん"]},
    {"meaning":"system,organization","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"体系","answer":["たいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"counter-plan,counter-measure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"対策","answer":["たいさく"]},
    {"meaning":"gymnastics,physical exercises,calisthenics","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"体操","answer":["たいそう"]},
    {"meaning":"waterfall","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滝","answer":["たき"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil,to cook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"炊く","answer":["たく"]},
    {"meaning":"to store,to lay in stock","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蓄える","answer":["たくわえる"]},
    {"meaning":"free of charge,mere,sole,only,usual,common","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"只","answer":["ただ"]},
    {"meaning":"but,however,provided that","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"但し","answer":["ただし"]},
    {"meaning":"derailment,digression","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脱線","answer":["だっせん"]},
    {"meaning":"valid,proper,right,appropriate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妥当","answer":["だとう"]},
    {"meaning":"fresh water","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"淡水","answer":["たんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"to swear,to vow,to take an oath,to pledge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誓う","answer":["ちかう"]},
    {"meaning":"to shrink,to be contracted","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縮む","answer":["ちぢむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to shorten,to reduce,to boil down,to shrink","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縮める","answer":["ちぢめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be wavy,to be curled","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縮れる","answer":["ちぢれる"]},
    {"meaning":"second third of a month","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"中旬","answer":["ちゅうじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"abstract","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抽象","answer":["ちゅうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"carving,engraving,sculpture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"彫刻","answer":["ちょうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"regulation,adjustment,tuning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"調整","answer":["ちょうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"regulation,adjustment,control","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"調節","answer":["ちょうせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"diameter","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"直径","answer":["ちょっけい"]},
    {"meaning":"passbook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"通帳","answer":["つうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"interpretation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"通訳","answer":["つうやく"]},
    {"meaning":"to dip in,to soak","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"浸ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"rope","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"綱","answer":["つな"]},
    {"meaning":"to balance,to be in harmony,to suit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"釣り合う","answer":["つりあう"]},
    {"meaning":"established price","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"定価","answer":["ていか"]},
    {"meaning":"unevenness,roughness,ruggedness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"凸凹","answer":["でこぼこ"]},
    {"meaning":"notebook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"手帳","answer":["てちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"gun","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鉄砲","answer":["てっぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"develop,expansion (opposite of compression)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"展開","answer":["てんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"contagion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"伝染","answer":["でんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"unity,consolidation,uniformity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"統一","answer":["とういつ"]},
    {"meaning":"ridge,(mountain) pass,difficult part","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"峠","answer":["とうげ"]},
    {"meaning":"scattering,a scatter,dispersion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"統計","answer":["とうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"transparency,cleanness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"透明","answer":["とうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"special,unique","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"特殊","answer":["とくしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"cupboard,locker,closet,wardrobe","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"戸棚","answer":["とだな"]},
    {"meaning":"to be prepared,to be in order,to be put in order,to be arranged","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整う","answer":["ととのう"]},
    {"meaning":"to jump,to fly,to leap","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"跳ぶ","answer":["とぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to comfort,to console","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"慰める","answer":["なぐさめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to accomplish,to do","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"為す","answer":["なす"]},
    {"meaning":"dear,desired,missed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"懐かしい","answer":["なつかしい"]},
    {"meaning":"obliqueness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"斜め","answer":["ななめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil,to cook,to be cooked","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"煮える","answer":["にえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to become muddy,to get impure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"濁る","answer":["にごる"]},
    {"meaning":"rainbow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"虹","answer":["にじ"]},
    {"meaning":"wife","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"女房","answer":["にょうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil,to cook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"煮る","answer":["にる"]},
    {"meaning":"to sew","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縫う","answer":["ぬう"]},
    {"meaning":"efficiency","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"能率","answer":["のうりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to place on (something),to take on board,to give a ride","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"載せる","answer":["のせる"]},
    {"meaning":"to appear (in print),to be recorded","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"載る","answer":["のる"]},
    {"meaning":"haiku poetry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"俳句","answer":["はいく"]},
    {"meaning":"nausea,sickness in the stomach","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"吐き気","answer":["はきけ"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"斜","answer":["はす"]},
    {"meaning":"a bowl,a pot","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鉢","answer":["はち"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition,demonstration,utilization,display","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"発揮","answer":["はっき"]},
    {"meaning":"firing,shooting,discharge,catapult","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"発射","answer":["はっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"showy,loud,gay,flashy,gaudy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"派手","answer":["はで"]},
    {"meaning":"extreme,excessive,terrible","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"甚だしい","answer":["はなはだしい"]},
    {"meaning":"bride","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"花嫁","answer":["はなよめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to jump,to leap","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"跳ねる","answer":["はねる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be in high spirits,to be full of vigor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"張り切る","answer":["はりきる"]},
    {"meaning":"radius","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"半径","answer":["はんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn over,to overturn,to knock over,to upset,to turn inside out","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"引っ繰り返す","answer":["ひっくりかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be overturned,to be upset,to topple over,to be reversed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"引っ繰り返る","answer":["ひっくりかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"pupil (of eye)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"瞳","answer":["ひとみ"]},
    {"meaning":"a soliloquy,a monologue,speaking to oneself","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独り言","answer":["ひとりごと"]},
    {"meaning":"sign,mark","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"標識","answer":["ひょうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"standard,level","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"標準","answer":["ひょうじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"example,specimen","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"標本","answer":["ひょうほん"]},
    {"meaning":"criticism,critique","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"評論","answer":["ひょうろん"]},
    {"meaning":"hiragana,47 syllables,the cursive syllabary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"平仮名","answer":["ひらがな"]},
    {"meaning":"diffusion,spread","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"普及","answer":["ふきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to swell,to expand,to inflate,to bulge","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"膨らます","answer":["ふくらます"]},
    {"meaning":"to expand,to swell (out),to get big,to become inflated","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"膨らむ","answer":["ふくらむ"]},
    {"meaning":"unclean,dirty,filthy,impure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"不潔","answer":["ふけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"warrior,samurai","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"武士","answer":["ぶし"]},
    {"meaning":"attached,belonging,affiliated","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"附属","answer":["ふぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"railway crossing,level crossing,starting line,scratch,crossover","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"踏切","answer":["ふみきり"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase,to add to,to augment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"殖やす","answer":["ふやす"]},
    {"meaning":",pronunciation key","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振り仮名","answer":["ふりがな"]},
    {"meaning":"to behave,to conduct oneself,to entertain (vt)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振舞う","answer":["ふるまう"]},
    {"meaning":"wrapping cloth,cloth wrapper","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"風呂敷","answer":["ふろしき"]},
    {"meaning":"eruption","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"噴火","answer":["ふんか"]},
    {"meaning":"literature,books (reference)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"文献","answer":["ぶんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"water fountain","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"噴水","answer":["ふんすい"]},
    {"meaning":"stationery","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"文房具","answer":["ぶんぼうぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"context","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"文脈","answer":["ぶんみゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"common,commonplace,ordinary,mediocre","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"平凡","answer":["へいぼん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be dented,to be indented,to yield to,to give,to sink,to collapse,to cave in,to be snubbed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"凹む","answer":["へこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"holiday house,villa","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"別荘","answer":["べっそう"]},
    {"meaning":"telescope","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"望遠鏡","answer":["ぼうえんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"huge,bulky,enormous,extensive,swelling,expansion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"膨大","answer":["ぼうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"brightness,cheerfulness,melodious","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"朗らか","answer":["ほがらか"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) farm (livestock),(2) pasture land,meadow,grazing land","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"牧場","answer":["ぼくじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"stock-farming","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"牧畜","answer":["ぼくちく"]},
    {"meaning":"health preservation,hygiene,sanitation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保健","answer":["ほけん"]},
    {"meaning":"moat,canal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"堀","answer":["ほり"]},
    {"meaning":"to carve,to engrave,to sculpture,to chisel","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"彫る","answer":["ほる"]},
    {"meaning":"Lantern Festival,Festival of the Dead,tray","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盆","answer":["ぼん"]},
    {"meaning":"basin (e.g. between mountains)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盆地","answer":["ぼんち"]},
    {"meaning":"to sow (seeds)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蒔く","answer":["まく"]},
    {"meaning":"friction,rubbing,rubdown,chafe","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"摩擦","answer":["まさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"or,otherwise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"又は","answer":["または"]},
    {"meaning":"street corner","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"街角","answer":["まちかど"]},
    {"meaning":"rare,seldom","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"稀","answer":["まれ"]},
    {"meaning":"cape (on coast)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"岬","answer":["みさき"]},
    {"meaning":"ugly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"醜い","answer":["みにくい"]},
    {"meaning":"to examine (medical)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"診る","answer":["みる"]},
    {"meaning":"folk song,popular song","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"民謡","answer":["みんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"humid,sultry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"蒸し暑い","answer":["むしあつい"]},
    {"meaning":"contradiction,inconsistency","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"矛盾","answer":["むじゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"purple colour,violet","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"紫","answer":["むらさき"]},
    {"meaning":"each,individual","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"銘々","answer":["めいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"to be blessed with,to be rich in","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恵まれる","answer":["めぐまれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to go around","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"巡る","answer":["めぐる"]},
    {"meaning":"tax exemption,duty exemption","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"免税","answer":["めんぜい"]},
    {"meaning":"bother to do,tiresome","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"面倒臭い","answer":["めんどうくさい"]},
    {"meaning":"inexcusable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"申し訳ない","answer":["もうしわけない"]},
    {"meaning":"event,festivities,function","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"催し","answer":["もよおし"]},
    {"meaning":"to translate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"訳す","answer":["やくす"]},
    {"meaning":"directing arrow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"矢印","answer":["やじるし"]},
    {"meaning":"quiet,calm,leisurely","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"悠々","answer":["ゆうゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"loose,lenient,slow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緩い","answer":["ゆるい"]},
    {"meaning":"container,vessel","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"容器","answer":["ようき"]},
    {"meaning":"gist,essentials,summary,fundamentals","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"要旨","answer":["ようし"]},
    {"meaning":"infancy,childish,infantile","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幼稚","answer":["ようち"]},
    {"meaning":"kindergarten","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"幼稚園","answer":["ようちえん"]},
    {"meaning":"wool","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"羊毛","answer":["ようもう"]},
    {"meaning":"gradually,finally,hardly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漸く","answer":["ようやく"]},
    {"meaning":"avarice,covetousness,greed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"欲張り","answer":["よくばり"]},
    {"meaning":"drunkard","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酔っ払い","answer":["よっぱらい"]},
    {"meaning":"failure,dropping out of a class","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"落第","answer":["らくだい"]},
    {"meaning":"column of text (e.g. as in a newspaper)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"欄","answer":["らん"]},
    {"meaning":"hostel,dormitory","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"寮","answer":["りょう"]},
    {"meaning":"temporary,special,extraordinary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"臨時","answer":["りんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to boil,to grow hot,to get excited,to gush forth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"湧く","answer":["わく"]},
    {"meaning":"handshake","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"握手","answer":["あくしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"warm,mild","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暖かい","answer":["あたたか(い)","あたたかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to handle,to deal with,to treat","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"扱う","answer":["あつかう"]},
    {"meaning":"hole","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"穴","answer":["あな"]},
    {"meaning":"defect,flaw,blemish,weak point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"粗","answer":["あら"]},
    {"meaning":"storm,tempest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嵐","answer":["あらし"]},
    {"meaning":"bubble,foam,froth,head on beer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"泡","answer":["あわ"]},
    {"meaning":"helpless,pity,sorrow,grief","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"哀れ","answer":["あわれ"]},
    {"meaning":"plan,suffix meaning draft","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"案","answer":["あん"]},
    {"meaning":"information,guidance,leading","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"案内","answer":["あんない"]},
    {"meaning":"will,volition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"意志","answer":["いし"]},
    {"meaning":"maintenance,preservation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"維持","answer":["いじ"]},
    {"meaning":"strangeness,abnormality,disorder","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異常","answer":["いじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to come,to arrive","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"至る","answer":["いたる"]},
    {"meaning":"a moment,an instant","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一瞬","answer":["いっしゅん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) coincidence,agreement,(2) conformity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一致","answer":["いっち"]},
    {"meaning":"cousin (male)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従兄弟","answer":["いとこ"]},
    {"meaning":"rice-plant","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"稲","answer":["いね"]},
    {"meaning":"universe,cosmos,space","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宇宙","answer":["うちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to attack,to defeat,to destroy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"撃つ","answer":["うつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to sue (a person),to resort to,to appeal to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"訴える","answer":["うったえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to snatch away","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奪う","answer":["うばう"]},
    {"meaning":"plum,plum-tree,lowest (of a three-tier ranking system)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"梅","answer":["うめ"]},
    {"meaning":"happy,glad,pleasant","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嬉しい","answer":["うれしい"]},
    {"meaning":"handle,grip","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"柄","answer":["え","がら"]},
    {"meaning":"influence,effect","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"影響","answer":["えいきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"satellite","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衛星","answer":["えいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to draw,to paint,to sketch,to depict,to describe","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"描く","answer":["えがく","かく"]},
    {"meaning":"assistance,aid,support","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"援助","answer":["えんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"musical performance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"演奏","answer":["えんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"diffidence,restraint,reserve","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"遠慮","answer":["えんりょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to respond,to satisfy,to accept,to comply with,to apply for","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"応じる","answer":["おうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"to cover,to hide,to conceal,to wrap,to disguise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"覆う","answer":["おおう"]},
    {"meaning":"hill,height,knoll,rising ground","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"丘","answer":["おか"]},
    {"meaning":"open sea","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"沖","answer":["おき"]},
    {"meaning":"pollution,contamination","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"汚染","answer":["おせん"]},
    {"meaning":"calm,gentle,quiet","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"穏やか","answer":["おだやか"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall behind,to be inferior to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"劣る","answer":["おとる"]},
    {"meaning":"to exert,to cause,to exercise","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"及ぼす","answer":["およぼす"]},
    {"meaning":"favour,obligation,debt of gratitude","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"恩","answer":["おん"]},
    {"meaning":"warmth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"温暖","answer":["おんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"explanation,interpretation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"解釈","answer":["かいしゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"betterment,improvement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"改善","answer":["かいぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"price,value,cost","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"価格","answer":["かかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine,to glitter,to sparkle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"輝く","answer":["かがやく"]},
    {"meaning":"resolution,resignation,readiness,preparedness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"覚悟","answer":["かくご"]},
    {"meaning":"magnification,enlargement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拡大","answer":["かくだい"]},
    {"meaning":"shade,shadow,other side","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"影","answer":["かげ"]},
    {"meaning":"conflagration,fire","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"火災","answer":["かさい"]},
    {"meaning":"to earn income,to labor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"稼ぐ","answer":["かせぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"sword,saber,knife,engraving tool","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刀","answer":["かたな"]},
    {"meaning":"value,worth,merit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"価値","answer":["かち"]},
    {"meaning":"share,stock,stump (of tree)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"株","answer":["かぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"patience,endurance,perseverance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"我慢","answer":["がまん"]},
    {"meaning":"to cut (hair),to mow (grass),to harvest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刈る","answer":["かる"]},
    {"meaning":"perception,intuition,the sixth sense","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勘","answer":["かん"]},
    {"meaning":"environment,circumstance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"環境","answer":["かんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"welcome,reception","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"歓迎","answer":["かんげい"]},
    {"meaning":"thanks,gratitude","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"感謝","answer":["かんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"calculation,counting,consideration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勘定","answer":["かんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"supervision,control,superintendence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"監督","answer":["かんとく"]},
    {"meaning":"memory,recollection,remembrance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"記憶","answer":["きおく"]},
    {"meaning":"enterprise,undertaking","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"企業","answer":["きぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"humour,temper,mood","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"機嫌","answer":["きげん"]},
    {"meaning":"precious,valuable","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貴重","answer":["きちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"foundation,basis,standard","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基本","answer":["きほん"]},
    {"meaning":"strange,queer,curious","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奇妙","answer":["きみょう"]},
    {"meaning":"duty,obligation,responsibility","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"義務","answer":["ぎむ"]},
    {"meaning":"class, grade, rank,school class, grade","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"級","answer":["きゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"holiday,day off,furlough","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"休暇","answer":["きゅうか"]},
    {"meaning":"rest,break,recess,intermission","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"休憩","answer":["きゅうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"sudden,precipitous,radical","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"急激","answer":["きゅうげき"]},
    {"meaning":"relief,aid,rescue","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"救助","answer":["きゅうじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"skillful,handy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"器用","answer":["きよう"]},
    {"meaning":"manners","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"行儀","answer":["ぎょうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"teaching,instruction,professor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"教授","answer":["きょうじゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"to hate,to dislike,to loathe","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嫌う","answer":["きらう"]},
    {"meaning":"money,cash","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"金銭","answer":["きんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"metal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"金属","answer":["きんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"tension,mental strain,nervousness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"緊張","answer":["きんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"muscle,sinew","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"筋肉","answer":["きんにく"]},
    {"meaning":"monetary circulation,credit situation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"金融","answer":["きんゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"sentence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"句","answer":["く"]},
    {"meaning":"odour,scent,smell,stench","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"臭い","answer":["くさい"]},
    {"meaning":"chain","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鎖","answer":["くさり"]},
    {"meaning":"to rot,to go bad","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"腐る","answer":["くさる"]},
    {"meaning":"a habit (often a bad habit),peculiarity","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"癖","answer":["くせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to repeat,to do something over again","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"繰り返す","answer":["くりかえす"]},
    {"meaning":"to go mad,to get out of order","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"狂う","answer":["くるう"]},
    {"meaning":"knowing very well,detailed,full,accurate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"詳しい","answer":["くわしい"]},
    {"meaning":"notice,bulletin","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"掲示","answer":["けいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"criminal case,(police) detective","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刑事","answer":["けいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"contract,compact,agreement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"契約","answer":["けいやく"]},
    {"meaning":"injury (to animate object),hurt","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怪我","answer":["けが"]},
    {"meaning":"result,consequence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結果","answer":["けっか"]},
    {"meaning":"after all,eventually","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結局","answer":["けっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"conclusion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結論","answer":["けつろん"]},
    {"meaning":"health,sound,wholesome","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"健康","answer":["けんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"inspection (e.g. customs, factory),examination","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"検査","answer":["けんさ"]},
    {"meaning":"consideration,examination,investigation,study,scrutiny","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"検討","answer":["けんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"constitution","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"憲法","answer":["けんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"high price","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"高価","answer":["こうか"]},
    {"meaning":"wonderful,gorgeous,splendor,pomp,extravagance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"豪華","answer":["ごうか"]},
    {"meaning":"attack,strike,offensive,criticism,censure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"攻撃","answer":["こうげき"]},
    {"meaning":"contribution,services","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"貢献","answer":["こうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"consideration,taking into account","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"考慮","answer":["こうりょ"]},
    {"meaning":"home town,birthplace,old village,historic village","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"故郷","answer":["こきょう","ふるさと"]},
    {"meaning":"subjugation,conquest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"克服","answer":["こくふく"]},
    {"meaning":"grain,cereal,corn","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"穀物","answer":["こくもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"break-down,failure,accident,out of order","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"故障","answer":["こしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to differ,to vary,to disagree","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"異なる","answer":["ことなる"]},
    {"meaning":"trial,judgement","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裁判","answer":["さいばん"]},
    {"meaning":"helping,serving","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盛り","answer":["さかり"]},
    {"meaning":"cherry blossom,cherry tree","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"桜","answer":["さくら"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to avoid (physical contact ),(2) to ward off,to avert","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"避ける","answer":["さける","よける"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to invite,to ask,(2) to tempt,to lure,to induce","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誘う","answer":["さそう"]},
    {"meaning":"desert","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"砂漠","answer":["さばく"]},
    {"meaning":"monkey","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"猿","answer":["さる"]},
    {"meaning":"oxygen","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酸素","answer":["さんそ"]},
    {"meaning":"poem,verse of poetry","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"詩","answer":["し"]},
    {"meaning":"stimulus,impetus,incentive","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"刺激","answer":["しげき"]},
    {"meaning":"resources","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"資源","answer":["しげん"]},
    {"meaning":"poet","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"詩人","answer":["しじん"]},
    {"meaning":"tongue","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"舌","answer":["した"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) order,precedence,(2) circumstances,(3) immediate(ly)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"次第","answer":["しだい"]},
    {"meaning":"situation,present state of affairs","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"事態","answer":["じたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to abide (by the rules),to obey,to follow,to accompany","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"従う","answer":["したがう"]},
    {"meaning":"enforcement,enact,put into practice,carry out,operation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"実施","answer":["じっし"]},
    {"meaning":"play,drama","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"芝居","answer":["しばい"]},
    {"meaning":"lawn","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"芝生","answer":["しばふ"]},
    {"meaning":"pride,boast","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"自慢","answer":["じまん"]},
    {"meaning":"hindrance,intrusion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"邪魔","answer":["じゃま"]},
    {"meaning":"harvest,crop,ingathering","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"収穫","answer":["しゅうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"religion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宗教","answer":["しゅうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"importance,stress,serious consideration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"重視","answer":["じゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"finding employment,inauguration","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"就職","answer":["しゅうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"amendment,correction,revision,modification","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修正","answer":["しゅうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"congestion (e.g. traffic),delay,stagnation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"渋滞","answer":["じゅうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"repairing,mending","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"修理","answer":["しゅうり"]},
    {"meaning":"doctrine,rule,principle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"主義","answer":["しゅぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"claim,request,insistence,assertion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"主張","answer":["しゅちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"moment,second,instant","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"瞬間","answer":["しゅんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"scholarship","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"奨学金","answer":["しょうがくきん"]},
    {"meaning":"conditions,terms","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"条件","answer":["じょうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"symptoms,condition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"症状","answer":["しょうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"condition,situation,circumstances,state","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"状態","answer":["じょうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"jest,joke","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冗談","answer":["じょうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"collision,conflict","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"衝突","answer":["しょうとつ"]},
    {"meaning":"proof,verification","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"証明","answer":["しょうめい"]},
    {"meaning":"dining table","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"食卓","answer":["しょくたく"]},
    {"meaning":"provisions,rations","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"食糧","answer":["しょくりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"study","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"書斎","answer":["しょさい"]},
    {"meaning":"slowly,little by little,gradually,steadily,quietly","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徐々に","answer":["じょじょに"]},
    {"meaning":"seriousness,earnestness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"真剣","answer":["しんけん"]},
    {"meaning":"(religious) faith,belief,creed","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"信仰","answer":["しんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"medical examination","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"診察","answer":["しんさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"discretion,prudence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"慎重","answer":["しんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nest,rookery,breeding place,beehive,cobweb","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"巣","answer":["す"]},
    {"meaning":"recommendation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"推薦","answer":["すいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"sleep","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"睡眠","answer":["すいみん"]},
    {"meaning":"figure,shape,appearance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"姿","answer":["すがた"]},
    {"meaning":"to rescue from,to help out of","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"救う","answer":["すくう"]},
    {"meaning":"muscle,string,line","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"筋","answer":["すじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to recommend,to advise,to encourage,to offer (wine)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"勧める","answer":["すすめる"]},
    {"meaning":"already,too late","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"既に","answer":["すでに"]},
    {"meaning":"wonderful,splendid,magnificent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"素晴らしい","answer":["すばらしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to change,to be of use,to reach to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"為る","answer":["する","なる"]},
    {"meaning":"cause,reason,fault","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"所為","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"century,era","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"世紀","answer":["せいき"]},
    {"meaning":"claim,demand,application,request","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"請求","answer":["せいきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"clean","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"清潔","answer":["せいけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"success,hit","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"成功","answer":["せいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"manufacture,production","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"製造","answer":["せいぞう"]},
    {"meaning":"manufactured goods,finished goods","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"製品","answer":["せいひん"]},
    {"meaning":"sorting,arrangement,adjustment,regulation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"整理","answer":["せいり"]},
    {"meaning":"destruction,extinction","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"絶滅","answer":["ぜつめつ"]},
    {"meaning":"economising,saving","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"節約","answer":["せつやく"]},
    {"meaning":"certainly,without fail","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"是非","answer":["ぜひ"]},
    {"meaning":"good,goodness,right,virtue","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"善","answer":["ぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"major subject,special study","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"専攻","answer":["せんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"selection,choice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"選択","answer":["せんたく"]},
    {"meaning":"operation,management,processing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"操作","answer":["そうさ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) organization,(2) structure,construction,(3) tissue,(4) system","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"組織","answer":["そしき"]},
    {"meaning":"crude,rough,plain,humble","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"粗末","answer":["そまつ"]},
    {"meaning":"tedium,boredom","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"退屈","answer":["たいくつ"]},
    {"meaning":"stay,sojourn","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滞在","answer":["たいざい"]},
    {"meaning":"usually,generally","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大抵","answer":["たいてい"]},
    {"meaning":"attitude,manner","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"態度","answer":["たいど"]},
    {"meaning":"president,chief executive","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"大統領","answer":["だいとうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"arrest,apprehension,capture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"逮捕","answer":["たいほ"]},
    {"meaning":"length,height","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縦","answer":["たて"]},
    {"meaning":"bullet,shot,shell","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弾","answer":["たま"]},
    {"meaning":"birth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誕生","answer":["たんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"wisdom,wit,sagacity,sense,intelligence,advice","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"知恵","answer":["ちえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to settle in (place),to take (seat, position),to study (under teacher)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"就く","answer":["つく"]},
    {"meaning":"wings","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"翼","answer":["つばさ"]},
    {"meaning":"rainy season,rain during the rainy season","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"梅雨","answer":["つゆ","ばいう"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"釣","answer":["つり"]},
    {"meaning":"proposal,proposition,suggestion","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"提案","answer":["ていあん"]},
    {"meaning":"electrical resistance,resistance,opposition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"抵抗","answer":["ていこう"]},
    {"meaning":"presentation,submission,filing","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"提出","answer":["ていしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"philosophy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"哲学","answer":["てつがく"]},
    {"meaning":"thoroughness,completeness","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徹底","answer":["てってい"]},
    {"meaning":"all night,all night vigil,sleepless night","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"徹夜","answer":["てつや"]},
    {"meaning":"type,pattern,archetypal","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"典型","answer":["てんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"tradition,convention","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"伝統","answer":["でんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"examination paper,examination script","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"答案","answer":["とうあん"]},
    {"meaning":"morals","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"道徳","answer":["どうとく"]},
    {"meaning":"voting,poll","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"投票","answer":["とうひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"coworker,colleague,associate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"同僚","answer":["どうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"feature,characteristic","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"特徴","answer":["とくちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"peculiarity,uniqueness,characteristic","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独特","answer":["どくとく"]},
    {"meaning":"independence (e.g. Ind. Day),self-support","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独立","answer":["どくりつ"]},
    {"meaning":"just (now, at the moment, etc.)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"途端","answer":["とたん"]},
    {"meaning":"tiger","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"虎","answer":["とら"]},
    {"meaning":"scene,view,prospect,outlook","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"眺め","answer":["ながめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to view,to gaze at","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"眺める","answer":["ながめる"]},
    {"meaning":"consent,assent,understanding","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"納得","answer":["なっとく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be idle,to neglect","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"怠ける","answer":["なまける"]},
    {"meaning":"rope,hemp","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"縄","answer":["なわ"]},
    {"meaning":"to grasp,to seize,to mould sushi","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"握る","answer":["にぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"actor,actress,player,performer","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"俳優","answer":["はいゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"grave,tomb","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"墓","answer":["はか"]},
    {"meaning":"doctorate,PhD","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"博士","answer":["はかせ"]},
    {"meaning":"to wear,to put on (lower body)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"履く","answer":["はく"]},
    {"meaning":"clapping hands,applause","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"拍手","answer":["はくしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"museum","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"博物館","answer":["はくぶつかん"]},
    {"meaning":"violent,vehement,intense","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"激しい","answer":["はげしい"]},
    {"meaning":"end (e.g. of street),edge,tip,margin,point","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"端","answer":["はし"]},
    {"meaning":"flag","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"旗","answer":["はた"]},
    {"meaning":"naked,nude","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"裸","answer":["はだか"]},
    {"meaning":"to punish,to penalize","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"罰する","answer":["ばっする"]},
    {"meaning":"development,growth","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"発展","answer":["はってん"]},
    {"meaning":"to stick,to paste","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"張る","answer":["はる"]},
    {"meaning":"extent,scope,sphere,range","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"範囲","answer":["はんい"]},
    {"meaning":"opposition,resistance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"反抗","answer":["はんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"comparison","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"比較","answer":["ひかく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to pull,to draw,to stretch,to drag,(2) to pull the ball (baseball)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"引っ張る","answer":["ひっぱる"]},
    {"meaning":"alone,unmarried","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"独り","answer":["ひとり"]},
    {"meaning":"criticism,judgement,comment","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"批判","answer":["ひはん"]},
    {"meaning":"criticism,review,commentary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"批評","answer":["ひひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"secret,secrecy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"秘密","answer":["ひみつ"]},
    {"meaning":"delicate,subtle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"微妙","answer":["びみょう"]},
    {"meaning":"valuation,estimation,assessment,evaluation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"評価","answer":["ひょうか"]},
    {"meaning":"fame,reputation,popularity,arrant","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"評判","answer":["ひょうばん"]},
    {"meaning":"flute,pipe","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"笛","answer":["ふえ"]},
    {"meaning":"weapon,arms,ordinance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"武器","answer":["ぶき"]},
    {"meaning":"prices of commodities,prices (in general)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"物価","answer":["ぶっか"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to wave,to shake,to swing,(2) to sprinkle,(3) to cast (actor),to allocate (work)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"振る","answer":["ふる"]},
    {"meaning":"bath","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"風呂","answer":["ふろ"]},
    {"meaning":"wall,fence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"塀","answer":["へい"]},
    {"meaning":"box lunch","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"弁当","answer":["べんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"risk,venture,adventure","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冒険","answer":["ぼうけん"]},
    {"meaning":"pride","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誇り","answer":["ほこり"]},
    {"meaning":"guarantee,security,assurance,pledge,warranty","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保証","answer":["ほしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"preservation,conservation,storage,maintenance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"保存","answer":["ほぞん"]},
    {"meaning":"flame","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"炎","answer":["ほのお"]},
    {"meaning":"to smile","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"微笑む","answer":["ほほえむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to praise,to admire,to speak well","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"褒める","answer":["ほめる"]},
    {"meaning":"again,and","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"又","answer":["また"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) pine tree,(2) highest (of a three-tier ranking system)","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"松","answer":["まつ"]},
    {"meaning":"beans,peas","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"豆","answer":["まめ"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"密","answer":["みつ"]},
    {"meaning":"strange,unusual","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"妙","answer":["みょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to tie,to bind,to link","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結ぶ","answer":["むすぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"sprout","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"芽","answer":["め"]},
    {"meaning":"trouble,bother,annoyance","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"迷惑","answer":["めいわく"]},
    {"meaning":"rarely (with neg. verb),seldom","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滅多に","answer":["めったに"]},
    {"meaning":"license,permit,licence,certificate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"免許","answer":["めんきょ"]},
    {"meaning":"apology,excuse","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"申し訳","answer":["もうしわけ"]},
    {"meaning":"mark,objective,target","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"目標","answer":["もくひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be grounded on,to be based on,to be due to,to originate from","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"基づく","answer":["もとづく"]},
    {"meaning":"pattern,figure,design","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"模様","answer":["もよう"]},
    {"meaning":"phrase,complaint","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"文句","answer":["もんく"]},
    {"meaning":"meaning,reason,circumstances,can be deduced,situation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"訳","answer":["やく","わけ"]},
    {"meaning":"rent","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"家賃","answer":["やちん"]},
    {"meaning":"trouble,burden,care,bother","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"厄介","answer":["やっかい"]},
    {"meaning":"only,sole,unique","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"唯一","answer":["ゆいいつ"]},
    {"meaning":"superiority,excellence","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"優秀","answer":["ゆうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"pleasant,happy","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"愉快","answer":["ゆかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn over,to assign,to hand over","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"譲る","answer":["ゆずる"]},
    {"meaning":"to get drunk,to become intoxicated","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"酔う","answer":["よう"]},
    {"meaning":"element","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"要素","answer":["ようそ"]},
    {"meaning":"bride,daughter-in-law","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嫁","answer":["よめ"]},
    {"meaning":"surplus,composure,margin,room,time,allowance,scope,rope","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"余裕","answer":["よゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"(hon) good,OK,all right,fine,very well,will do,may,can","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"宜しい","answer":["よろしい"]},
    {"meaning":"profits,gains,(political, economic) interest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"利益","answer":["りえき"]},
    {"meaning":"rate,ratio,proportion,percentage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"率","answer":["りつ"]},
    {"meaning":"splendid,fine,handsome,elegant,imposing,prominent,legal,legitimate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"立派","answer":["りっぱ"]},
    {"meaning":"manners,courtesy,etiquette","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"礼儀","answer":["れいぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"we","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"我々","answer":["われわれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to apologize","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"謝る","answer":["あやまる"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to do","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"致す","answer":["いたす"]},
    {"meaning":"with utmost effort","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"一生懸命","answer":["いっしょうけんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"countryside","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"田舎","answer":["いなか"]},
    {"meaning":"young lady","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"お嬢さん","answer":["おじょうさん"]},
    {"meaning":"mirror","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鏡","answer":["かがみ"]},
    {"meaning":"wall","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"壁","answer":["かべ"]},
    {"meaning":"female nurse","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"看護婦","answer":["かんごふ"]},
    {"meaning":"steam train","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"汽車","answer":["きしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"season","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"季節","answer":["きせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"silk","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"絹","answer":["きぬ"]},
    {"meaning":"strict","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"厳しい","answer":["きびしい"]},
    {"meaning":"an interest","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"興味","answer":["きょうみ"]},
    {"meaning":"lecture","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"講義","answer":["こうぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to break","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"壊す","answer":["こわす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be broken","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"壊れる","answer":["こわれる"]},
    {"meaning":"popularity,prosperous","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"盛ん","answer":["さかん"]},
    {"meaning":"lonely","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"寂しい","answer":["さびしい","さみしい"]},
    {"meaning":"accident","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"事故","answer":["じこ"]},
    {"meaning":"dictionary","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"辞典","answer":["じてん"]},
    {"meaning":"hobby","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"趣味","answer":["しゅみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to slide,to slip","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"滑る","answer":["すべる"]},
    {"meaning":"senior","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"先輩","answer":["せんぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"to ask","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"尋ねる","answer":["たずねる"]},
    {"meaning":"shelves","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"棚","answer":["たな"]},
    {"meaning":"in order to","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"為","answer":["ため"]},
    {"meaning":"heating","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暖房","answer":["だんぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"injection","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"注射","answer":["ちゅうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"to soak,to pickle","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漬ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"to fish","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"釣る","answer":["つる"]},
    {"meaning":"polite","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"丁寧","answer":["ていねい"]},
    {"meaning":"exhibition","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"展覧会","answer":["てんらんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to weep","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"泣く","answer":["なく"]},
    {"meaning":"to step on","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"踏む","answer":["ふむ"]},
    {"meaning":"translation","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"翻訳","answer":["ほんやく"]},
    {"meaning":"comic","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"漫画","answer":["まんが"]},
    {"meaning":"to shake,to sway","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"揺れる","answer":["ゆれる"]},
    {"meaning":"air conditioning","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"冷房","answer":["れいぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"hot","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"暑い","answer":["あつい"]},
    {"meaning":"unpleasant","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嫌","answer":["いや"]},
    {"meaning":"noisy, annoying","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"煩い","answer":["うるさい"]},
    {"meaning":"pencil","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"鉛筆","answer":["えんぴつ"]},
    {"meaning":"uncle, middle aged gentleman","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"伯父さん","answer":["おじさん"]},
    {"meaning":"uncle, middle aged gentleman","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"叔父さん","answer":["おじさん"]},
    {"meaning":"Bath","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"お風呂","answer":["おふろ"]},
    {"meaning":"boxed lunch","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"お弁当","answer":["おべんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"Umbrella","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"傘","answer":["かさ"]},
    {"meaning":"a cold","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"風邪","answer":["かぜ"]},
    {"meaning":"Hate","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"嫌い","answer":["きらい"]},
    {"meaning":"splendid, enough","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結構","answer":["けっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"Marriage","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"結婚","answer":["けっこん"]},
    {"meaning":"entry hall","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"玄関","answer":["げんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"Sugar","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"砂糖","answer":["さとう"]},
    {"meaning":"to tie","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"締める","answer":["しめる"]},
    {"meaning":"lesson, class work","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"授業","answer":["じゅぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Narrow","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"狭い","answer":["せまい"]},
    {"meaning":"birthday","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"誕生日","answer":["たんじょうび"]},
    {"meaning":"to take a photo or record a film","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"撮る","answer":["とる"]},
    {"meaning":"to take off clothes","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"脱ぐ","answer":["ぬぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"pork","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"豚肉","answer":["ぶたにく"]},
    {"meaning":"bookshelves","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"本棚","answer":["ほんだな"]},
    {"meaning":"corridor","kanjiLevel":1,"question":"廊下","answer":["ろうか"]}
  ]}

